<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>mac on Damien Saunders</title>
    <link>http://damien.co/tags/mac/</link>
    <description>Recent content in mac on Damien Saunders</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2013 17:33:15 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://damien.co/tags/mac/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>HOW TO: Install Jenkins-CI on a Mac OS X with Git &amp;#038; Bitbucket</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/development/how-to-install-jenkins-ci-on-a-mac-os-x-with-git-bitbucket-8072/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Dec 2012 13:56:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/development/how-to-install-jenkins-ci-on-a-mac-os-x-with-git-bitbucket-8072/</guid>
      <description>A few notes on getting Jenkins-CI installed on your Mac and setup with Git and Bitbucket for source code management. I’ve been using Git for some time but I had problems / major issues with Jenkins and could never seem to get this working.
Issues with setting up Jenkins and Git on a Mac Here are the issues I was having … the biggest issue was the Error (unable to clone) which showed up when I created a job and added the path to the Bitbucket repo — even after I had added the SSH Key to Bitbucket.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Aperture 3 digital photo software improved integration with Flickr</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/aperture-3-digital-photo-software-improved-integration-with-flickr-2584/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jan 2011 09:04:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/aperture-3-digital-photo-software-improved-integration-with-flickr-2584/</guid>
      <description>I’ve been using Apple Aperture 3 for my digital photography and image processing for a couple of years. It’s great for importing those images for clients and quickly doing all the editing, tagging, grouping and touch-ups.
What I didn’t like about it as a workflow tool – is that it lacks proper integration with Flickr. In the 3.0 version from last year you could publish as a Set of photos to Flickr, but couldn’t just add an image to your photostream.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to install Virtualbox on a Mac</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/how-to-install-virtualbox-on-a-mac-533/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Feb 2010 14:48:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/how-to-install-virtualbox-on-a-mac-533/</guid>
      <description>This is 2 minute guide covering how to get Virtualbox and install it on your Mac. You would choose to use Virtualbox for 2 reasons
 Virtualbox is freeware in comparison to Fusion for Mac Virtualbox runs inside your Mac so you don’t have to reboot like Bootcamp  It’s been some time since I visited my favorite topic, which is using my Mac OSx Snow Leopard to run virtual operating systems like Tiny XP, Windows 7RC or Ubunutu.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best Apps for your Mac &amp;#8211; after a clean install</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/best-apps-for-your-mac-after-a-clean-install-372/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Nov 2009 15:41:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/best-apps-for-your-mac-after-a-clean-install-372/</guid>
      <description>So I have had to rebuild my Mac running OS X 10.6 Snow Leopard 3 times in the past 2 days after having problems with a t-mobile usb modem which corrupts the hard drive.Here’s the short list of my favourite, can’t live without em, just got to install them apps:
Best Apps for your Mac  ClamXav – still the best and most recommended free virus protection for your mac Adium – pronounced like stadium, this is the multi chat application for the mac Skype – for free calls to the office and home Dropbox – for sharing files between the office and clients Mac Office 2008 – word, powerpoint and to some extent excel, because all my templates are Office based and the guys in the office use PC’s.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MacOSx Converts: XNJB get your Creative audio player to charge on a Mac</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/macosx-converts-xnjb-get-your-creative-audio-player-to-charge-on-a-mac-331/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Oct 2009 15:05:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/macosx-converts-xnjb-get-your-creative-audio-player-to-charge-on-a-mac-331/</guid>
      <description>XNJB: is the app of the day for people who have used MP3 players from Creative technology. Moving to a Mac I was at a lose as to how to copy music to my Creative Zen and how to charge my Creative on my Mac.
This is where XNJB comes to the rescue and lets you copy music or charge your Creative while running Mac OSX 10.6 Snow Leopard.
XNJB should be bundled with Creative Media Players … after all these years and all the marketing hype around the Mac not having official support for Mac is sometimes a death knell or ‘dirge’ for any brand.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mac OSx Convert Tip of the Day &amp;#8211; Screenshots</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/mac-osx-convert-tip-of-the-day-screenshots-302/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Sep 2009 18:51:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/mac-osx-convert-tip-of-the-day-screenshots-302/</guid>
      <description>The snipping tool has to be one of the best features introduced into Windows Vista (except for the nasty red line around the pictures). PRT-SCRN is now a thing of the past. But what do you do when your Mac doesnt even have a PRT SCRN key? Press any key ? ? ? ?
CMD+SHIFT+4 is the combination to remember .. and then press the space bar if you want a screen shot of the current window</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Group Review: Manage your CD library collection on a Mac</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/cd-library-management-283/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Sep 2009 19:54:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/cd-library-management-283/</guid>
      <description>Now that you’ve ripped and digitised all of your CD library – what do you do with your CD’s? One idea is to create a catalogue and then you can box or put away (or recycle) your CD’s and DVD’s giving you much more space to fill with books, CD’s or other stuff.If you’re like me, I’ve been ripping all my CD’s for years and the CD and cases were just collecting dust in my room.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mac OSx Convert Tip of the Day &amp;#8211; keyboard shortcuts</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/mac-osx-convert-tip-of-the-day-keyboard-shortcuts-287/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Sep 2009 19:26:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/mac-osx-convert-tip-of-the-day-keyboard-shortcuts-287/</guid>
      <description>The Mac OSx Convert has been reading up various selections of 101 of the best (or worst) OSx tips. Many of these tips don’t address the Keyboard shortcuts … on the newer Macbooks first tip is always press the Fn key to access function keys in the top row.
Best tip of the day … here’s a long list from Apple of the Keyboard Shortcuts
http://support.apple.com/kb/HT1343</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Virtualbox 3.0.4 Mac OSx How to share folders</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/virtualbox-3-0-4-mac-osx-how-to-share-folders-274/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Aug 2009 20:07:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/virtualbox-3-0-4-mac-osx-how-to-share-folders-274/</guid>
      <description>Virtualbox 3.0.4 is a new update released earlier this month. After updating to this new version file sharing between mac os and the guest windows vista has stopped working.
Something wonderful has happened and there is a new feature that has been added … Under the Devices Menu there is a new entry for “Sharing Folders” – you can now create shared folders in realtime
However to make the shared folders work you still must use the old method of mapping a network drive and remember to type your shared folder name as</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tip from a Windows Convert: Office for Mac &amp;#8211; Excel Keyboard Shortcut</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/tip-from-a-windows-convert-office-for-mac-excel-keyboard-shortcut-269/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Aug 2009 12:12:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/tip-from-a-windows-convert-office-for-mac-excel-keyboard-shortcut-269/</guid>
      <description>I’ve been using keyboard shortcuts for Microsoft Office on Windows for years. So here I am now using Mac Office on a Macbook Pro and still trying to figure out how to get around the keyboard.Tip of the Day – Windows Excel Alt+Enter and in Mac Office Excel keyboard shortcut is Fn+Ctrl+Alt
This adds a carriage return within the current cell and its great for doing long text entry in 1 cell.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Upgrading to Virtualbox 3.0 and Mac OSx hosts</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/upgrading-to-virtualbox-3-0-and-mac-osx-hosts-222/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2009 14:45:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/upgrading-to-virtualbox-3-0-and-mac-osx-hosts-222/</guid>
      <description>Assuming you have been using Virtualbox before, then the upgrade process to Virtualbox 3 is going to be easy and smooth sailing.
For first time users of Virtualbox or in fact virtualisation who are using a Mac OSx then you should read my earlier posts on how to get going. These are:
  15 minute guide to running Windows 7 RC on a Mac and
  How to install Virtualbox on a Mac using Windows TinyXP</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>15 minute guide to Virtualbox Windows 7 RC1 and your Mac</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/15-minute-guide-to-running-windows-7-rc1-on-a-mac-180/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 May 2009 20:05:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/15-minute-guide-to-running-windows-7-rc1-on-a-mac-180/</guid>
      <description>So this follows an earlier post of mine about Virtualbox and running Windows XP on a Macbook Pro. Virtualbox is a great piece of software for running virtual operating systems on another machine (like runing Windows 7 on a Mac OSX).Today’s guide shows that you can be up n running with Windows 7 RC in about 15 minutes … thats got to be good ??
So Grab your Windows 7 RC1 ISO file from the Windows website, grab a copy of Virtualbox for Mac and get going.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tips on Changing Settings for Virtualbox on a Mac Laptop</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/tips-on-changing-settings-for-virtualbox-on-a-mac-laptop-159/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Apr 2009 20:12:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/tips-on-changing-settings-for-virtualbox-on-a-mac-laptop-159/</guid>
      <description>This covers basic settings on a Mac Laptop Intel running osx … Running Virtualbox, the freeware virtualisation software on any computer can be easy – and there are a number of internet based support forums. Getting your head around the settings for Virtualbox can be a bit harder.
Virtualbox is configurable from its GUI interface and also has a larger set of command line options, which are all covered in the userguide on the Virtualbox download site</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HOW TO install Virtualbox on Mac osx host &amp;amp; WinXp guest using TinyXP rev 09</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/resources/how-to-install-virtualbox-mac-osx-host-winxp-guest-using-tinyxp-rev-09-132/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Apr 2009 23:50:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/resources/how-to-install-virtualbox-mac-osx-host-winxp-guest-using-tinyxp-rev-09-132/</guid>
      <description>Virtualbox is a dream freeware solution for anyone – novice to geek – who wants to run different computers inside their computer … virtual so to speak. Today I’ve been tinkering with getting Virtualbox working on a Mac laptop running WinXP.
Virtualbox from Oracle Sunis a freeware, open source virtualisation application .. it comes in a number of flavours – I’ve previously used it to run WinXP guests inside WinXP hosts for testing and at work it was the only way to install things without having to go to the IT helpdesk.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>