<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Mobile Marketing on Damien Saunders</title>
    <link>https://damien1.github.io/categories/mobile-marketing/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Mobile Marketing on Damien Saunders</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 03 Sep 2012 13:21:09 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://damien1.github.io/categories/mobile-marketing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>One little sticker that changed the world of Mobile Payment NFC</title>
      <link>https://damien1.github.io/mobile-marketing/one-little-sticker-that-changed-the-world-of-mobile-payment-nfc-7720/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Sep 2012 13:21:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien1.github.io/mobile-marketing/one-little-sticker-that-changed-the-world-of-mobile-payment-nfc-7720/</guid>
      <description>Barclaysis a well known bank for all the wrong reasons lately – but a few months back they announced the launch of a sticker for your phone, wallet or just about anywhere. This sticker combines NFC (near field communications) technology with a business model that revolutionised mobile payments.
2 Models for NFC Mobile Payment A sticker that has effectively changed the world of Mobile Payments. Until PayTag was announced, there were only 2 models of Mobile Payments (and they were pretty monogamous).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Get Results from an Android Mobile Marketing Strategy</title>
      <link>https://damien1.github.io/mobile-marketing/get-results-from-an-android-mobile-marketing-strategy-5885/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2012 13:12:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien1.github.io/mobile-marketing/get-results-from-an-android-mobile-marketing-strategy-5885/</guid>
      <description>Android Mobiles are taking over the world … and that seems to be supported by the latest statistics or _trends. _If you’re thinking about mobile marketing .. and wondering ‘what is all the fuss about Android’, then this presentation is for you.
Only the latest Android Insights and Statistics  10 billion app downloads (December 2011) 200 million activated devices (November 2011) 400,000 Android Apps (December 2011)  We can only wait for the next Google I/O conference to confirm how these numbers are growing!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mobile Usage and Trends &amp;#8211; Updated with UK Statistics</title>
      <link>https://damien1.github.io/mobile-marketing/mobile-usage-and-trends-updated-with-uk-statistics-5815/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2011 19:18:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien1.github.io/mobile-marketing/mobile-usage-and-trends-updated-with-uk-statistics-5815/</guid>
      <description>Good mobile insights and statistics are hard to find unless you pay for them … that’s why I’ve just updated my Key Trends and Usage Insights to include data for the UK.
UK Mobile Trends and Insights UK total mobile users 80m (penetration is over 100% of the population)
UK smartphone penetration 46%
UK smartphone app usage 50%
Need Help? Check out my other presentations or contact me for more information.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Remember your Mobile Browser detection for iPad &amp;#038; Smartphones</title>
      <link>https://damien1.github.io/mobile-marketing/remember-your-mobile-browser-detection-for-ipad-smartphones-2589/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2011 09:21:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien1.github.io/mobile-marketing/remember-your-mobile-browser-detection-for-ipad-smartphones-2589/</guid>
      <description>So you’ve built a great website for your clients and they’re happy to see its getting lots of good traffic. Now your client wants to know how to make their website mobile.
Depending on the CMS you used to build the website – WordPressor Drupal for example, be sure to setup a mobile browser plugin that renders your website smartphone and mobile friendly.
 For anyone building a website from scratch – mobile browser detection is done in the same was as detecting say IE6.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to make your website mobile</title>
      <link>https://damien1.github.io/mobile-marketing/how-to-make-your-website-mobile-3772/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jun 2011 11:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien1.github.io/mobile-marketing/how-to-make-your-website-mobile-3772/</guid>
      <description>Smart phones are driving the usage of mobile internet and that’s not just the growth in mobile apps. Having a mobile version of your website or a mobile web app is becoming critical as your customers and potential new business use mobile search to hunt for any business.
There are 3 easy steps to get your website ready for the mobile internet:
 Make your website mobile now Assess your mobile customer’s needs Improve your mobile customer experience to generate leads  Make your website mobile today It’s easy for any brand or business to enable a mobile version of your website.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Customer Service via Web &amp;#038; Email &amp;#8211; Who didn&amp;#8217;t test your web mail form O2</title>
      <link>https://damien1.github.io/mobile-marketing/customer-service-via-web-email-who-didnt-test-your-web-mail-form-o2-3109/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2011 11:40:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien1.github.io/mobile-marketing/customer-service-via-web-email-who-didnt-test-your-web-mail-form-o2-3109/</guid>
      <description>Well hello Customer Service and Customer Management consultants … who here is reading this and is building a business case for improved customer service by moving customers to self care tools such as web forms and e-mail? Most of you reading this are probably think about it constantly. THEN DON’T DO IT unless you’ve gone and tested it and got it right.
I recently got an iPad 2 – an upgrade from my first iPad … Some nice marketing product person at O2 figured out an email with a link to reset the iPad MAC address so I can continue to use free wifi would be helpful.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>British Airways mobile app could do with its own QR Code</title>
      <link>https://damien1.github.io/mobile-marketing/british-airways-mobile-app-could-do-with-its-own-qr-code-3103/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 May 2011 13:10:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien1.github.io/mobile-marketing/british-airways-mobile-app-could-do-with-its-own-qr-code-3103/</guid>
      <description>This billboard stands out as an example – Just an example of how disconnected ‘real world’ traditional marketing is from integrated digital marketing.
Great – several airlines have now got mobile apps that allow you to seemingly, easily get from home to the airplane.
What’s wrong with this advert?   It’s only for iPhone – the image tells me straight away that here is another brand ignoring ‘other’ smartphones (or the only customers BA is helping are iOS device users)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Going Mobile &amp;#8211; I&amp;#8217;m in your face &amp;#8211; I&amp;#8217;m in your phone.</title>
      <link>https://damien1.github.io/mobile-marketing/going-mobile-im-in-your-face-im-in-your-phone-2953/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 May 2011 13:24:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien1.github.io/mobile-marketing/going-mobile-im-in-your-face-im-in-your-phone-2953/</guid>
      <description>Mobilising your web content and cross channel integrated marketing may sound like just a bunch of buzzwords to boost my SEO. But it’s not. So I’m helping you to understand the latest in mobile marketing, tools &amp;amp; techniques.
You can now visit http://damien.mobi from your smartphone and have the best experience a mobile can get. If you’re a fan of the iPad then you can also save this as a web app on your phone.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HOW-TO Get started with mobile app testing &amp;#8211; device checklist</title>
      <link>https://damien1.github.io/mobile-marketing/how-to-get-started-with-mobile-app-testing-device-checklist-2829/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Apr 2011 08:37:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien1.github.io/mobile-marketing/how-to-get-started-with-mobile-app-testing-device-checklist-2829/</guid>
      <description>Do you do mobile app testing? Then maybe you need a getting started checklist to help you with your device settings. One thing has not changed in the (nearly) 10 years since mobile internet got started – we still have to check and change device settings.
 Check .. Does the mobile operator name show in the status bar?
 if it says No Carrier it wont work  Check … you have a data connection â can you open any app or browse to a web page.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Say hello to 10,000,000,000 little downloads of mobile apps</title>
      <link>https://damien1.github.io/mobile-marketing/say-hello-to-10000000-little-downloads-of-mobile-apps-2577/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jan 2011 22:47:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien1.github.io/mobile-marketing/say-hello-to-10000000-little-downloads-of-mobile-apps-2577/</guid>
      <description>It was only earlier this week that Apple’s homepage changed to advertise the fact that a 10 billion milestone was soon to be reached.
It wouldn’t be insane to think that 10 billion app downloads is a milestone and a half – no other app store or mobile operator portal has reported such impressive download figures.
In other recent news e-marketer reckoned that we all had a collective average of 60 of these apps on our smartphones — that’s a lot of games, news, branded content and generally important little bits of code on our phones.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Digital Signage and traffic signals targets for stolen sim cards</title>
      <link>https://damien1.github.io/mobile-marketing/digital-signage-and-traffic-signals-targets-for-stolen-sim-cards-2537/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2011 13:00:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien1.github.io/mobile-marketing/digital-signage-and-traffic-signals-targets-for-stolen-sim-cards-2537/</guid>
      <description>Smart thieves in Jo’burg are making a fast buck from stolen simcards. Hundreds of lights have been damaged by thieves targeting the machines’ sim cards, which are then used to make mobile phone calls worth millions of South African rand.
Effectively any Digital Signage or Outdoor Advertising is now a target. As the advertising gets smarter and more technical – a new breed of criminals will target the computers and mobiles that power them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TV Advertising &amp;#8211; T-Mobile &amp;amp; Heathrow T5</title>
      <link>https://damien1.github.io/mobile-marketing/tv-advertising-t-mobile-heathrow-t5-1794/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Nov 2010 09:30:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien1.github.io/mobile-marketing/tv-advertising-t-mobile-heathrow-t5-1794/</guid>
      <description>I’m the type who is always overwhelmed by TV advertising– as I don’t watch ‘live’ TV or commercial TV with ads I often find myself watching adverts on the internet for the sake of it! I even occasionally, download these adverts to save them and watch them again and again and again and …Can I just say I’m against flashmobs, my new found British sensibility (*read – I’ve just handed in my UK citizenship application) does not condone such public displays – it’s embarrassing and I was overexposed to the last T-mobile flashmob thanks to my gyms in-house digital signage.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Social Networks &amp;amp; Social Gaming used most for Mobile Broadband</title>
      <link>https://damien1.github.io/mobile-marketing/social-networks-social-gaming-used-most-for-mobile-broadband-1757/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Oct 2010 09:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien1.github.io/mobile-marketing/social-networks-social-gaming-used-most-for-mobile-broadband-1757/</guid>
      <description>This news from Hutchison 3G UK shows that using social media is more important on their mobile network is interesting …. Keeping up to date with friends or regular gameplay on the move is now more important than checking emails or reading the news. 
In my opinion, Social Networking continues to dominate growth in internet usage – however, you shouldn’t assume that its all fun on the go. Social Media sites like Twitter, Facebook and LinkedInare all used for b2b leads and d2c customer service.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>50 Completely Useful stats for social media &amp;amp; mobile marketing</title>
      <link>https://damien1.github.io/mobile-marketing/50-completely-useful-stats-for-social-media-mobile-marketing-1002/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 May 2010 16:27:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien1.github.io/mobile-marketing/50-completely-useful-stats-for-social-media-mobile-marketing-1002/</guid>
      <description>To understand more about Social Media and Mobile Marketing its important to get a few facts together on current trends and insights. 50 completely useful stats for social media does just that.
Why do this? well it helps to create some drive … and helps to understand why anyone or any business needs to do more in social media and mobile marketing.
**
**</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HOW TO: Google Maps Local claim your business</title>
      <link>https://damien1.github.io/mobile-marketing/how-to-google-maps-local-claim-your-business-930/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 May 2010 08:00:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien1.github.io/mobile-marketing/how-to-google-maps-local-claim-your-business-930/</guid>
      <description>Google Maps is the first site that any business should visit before starting mobile or geospecific marketing. Google Maps Local provides a range of tools to make it easy for anyone to check their details and claim your business.
Why do you need to claim your business on Google Maps? We all know the phenomenon that is searching for something on Google from a Mobile – so as more people have Androidphones or iPhones or other smartphones, more people will use Mobile Internet for Search.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Mobile? Why Now? – short guide to mobile marketing</title>
      <link>https://damien1.github.io/mobile-marketing/why-mobile-why-now-short-guide-to-mobile-marketing-877/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Apr 2010 16:16:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien1.github.io/mobile-marketing/why-mobile-why-now-short-guide-to-mobile-marketing-877/</guid>
      <description>A short guide to mobile marketing is as short as it can get – and provides just enough insights, trends and key facts to help make the most of mobile marketing. What’s included in this is 8 quick suggestions how to include mobile marketing in your marketing strategy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>b2b Marketing &amp;#8211; how to increase your content sales and improve your content</title>
      <link>https://damien1.github.io/mobile-marketing/b2b-marketing-how-to-increase-your-content-sales-and-improve-your-content-812/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Mar 2010 23:29:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien1.github.io/mobile-marketing/b2b-marketing-how-to-increase-your-content-sales-and-improve-your-content-812/</guid>
      <description>A short guide with b2b marketing tips for improving your content sales and improve your content using mmCHANNEL’s new API.1. Got an upcoming marketing campaign? Need Content?
Now any marketing campaign can include digital content like tones, songs, games from a selection of mmCHANNEL manages.
2. Drive traffic to your website or fanpage
You can setup a content shop in your existing website using the mmCHANNEL b2bAPI with no need to build any other platforms</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3 Reasons SMS marketing will die this year</title>
      <link>https://damien1.github.io/mobile-marketing/3-reasons-sms-marketing-will-die-this-year-520/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2010 10:55:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien1.github.io/mobile-marketing/3-reasons-sms-marketing-will-die-this-year-520/</guid>
      <description>Have you had a funny feeling in your pocket lately? Have you noticed a distinct lack of marketing SMS or that you only get SMS from your bank or your mobile operator – no more unwanted SMS. Smart digital agencies and mobile marketing specialists are already moving their clients from this type of communications. There are 3 very good reasons that this year is the year SMS marketing will die. 1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>5 Essential tips for promoting your charity or cause using mobile marketing</title>
      <link>https://damien1.github.io/mobile-marketing/essential-tips-promotions-charities-mobile-451/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Feb 2010 07:44:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien1.github.io/mobile-marketing/essential-tips-promotions-charities-mobile-451/</guid>
      <description>For non-profit organisations, charities and cause related marketing the mobile can provide the best integrated marketing solution for campaigns. There are a number of tools and techniques which can be used to promote your cause or help to raise donations.
1. SMS Premium Text Donations Making donations using your mobile is as simple as sending a text to a special number. For the not so concerned and the lazy its a quick way to send a few dollars, euros or pounds to a worthy cause.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mobile Marketing Strategies &amp;#8211; Mobile CRM</title>
      <link>https://damien1.github.io/mobile-marketing/mobile-marketing-strategies-mobile-crm-442/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Feb 2010 09:47:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien1.github.io/mobile-marketing/mobile-marketing-strategies-mobile-crm-442/</guid>
      <description>**Until recently mobile devices were often overlooked by marketing managers in favour of online campaigns or traditional paper-based direct marketing. However, brands, ad agencies and telecoms operators are increasingly using mobile as part of their customer relationship management (CRM) strategy.
**
The rapid growth in smartphones spurred by the iPhone, Windows Mobile and Android has given mobile marketing a major boost. The latest devices offer fast and easy web access, often with flat-rate charges.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mobile SEO &amp;#8211; Google extends click to call to mobile search</title>
      <link>https://damien1.github.io/mobile-marketing/mobile-seo-google-extends-click-to-call-to-mobile-search-446/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Feb 2010 09:11:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien1.github.io/mobile-marketing/mobile-seo-google-extends-click-to-call-to-mobile-search-446/</guid>
      <description>In the next couple of weeks, I’ll be looking closely at Mobile Search and Mobile SEO. This week will be a round up of features on Google Mobile Search
Click to Call
Click to call has been a feature of WAP and mobile portals for sometime, however the mobile phones needed to support this action.
Google has now added Click to Call to Adword Mobile Search Results
Anyone running SEO or Adword campaigns should make sure they have configured the mobile search results as well and to now include the primary phone number for customers or clients to ring in on.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What kids do online: UK Internet Usage</title>
      <link>https://damien1.github.io/mobile-marketing/what-kids-do-online-uk-internet-usage-444/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Feb 2010 12:56:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien1.github.io/mobile-marketing/what-kids-do-online-uk-internet-usage-444/</guid>
      <description>Recent indepth report from New Media Age in the UK focused on the internet usage habits of kids.
Kids research is hard – the age group is from 7 – 13. They are already exposed to a lot of marketing, aware of trends and ‘peer pressure’, but still very much aware of having to please their parents all of the time. It’s also very difficult to ask questions about anything anti-social, illegal due to the young age and formative, questioning minds.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Looking for insights on Mobile and Retail Sector?</title>
      <link>https://damien1.github.io/mobile-marketing/looking-for-insights-on-mobile-and-retail-sector-440/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Feb 2010 17:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien1.github.io/mobile-marketing/looking-for-insights-on-mobile-and-retail-sector-440/</guid>
      <description>&amp;lt;div&amp;gt; The Whitepaper, ‘Mobile in Retail’, seeks to identify the potential for mobile to brands and retailers. It highlights 10 areas, including coupons and loyalty, where mobile is deemed to have a particular impact. The executive summary points to a number of areas of potential gain for businesses adopting mobile as a consumer engagement channel. These are increased sales; increased customer satisfaction and loyalty; and additional value to physical products and experiences through digital services.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Where to start building mobile apps for large screens &amp;#8211; mobile agencies beware</title>
      <link>https://damien1.github.io/mobile-marketing/where-to-start-building-mobile-apps-for-large-screens-mobile-agencies-beware-422/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jan 2010 15:28:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien1.github.io/mobile-marketing/where-to-start-building-mobile-apps-for-large-screens-mobile-agencies-beware-422/</guid>
      <description>Where to start with building a mobile app or going mobile has been a popular topic for some time. Many FMCG brands and agencies are requesting only quotes for mobile apps – forgetting the less popular java app or branded mobile game. At the expense of budget – haha – focusing on a mobile app can be a costly exercise starting from about 10k to 100k plus.
Marketing Agencies and their Brands need to go and reconsider their mobile strategy – and if you’ve already built a mobile app – you maybe disappointed how it looks on the larger screen devices.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to include mobile marketing into your advertising</title>
      <link>https://damien1.github.io/mobile-marketing/how-to-include-mobile-marketing-into-your-advertising-409/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jan 2010 18:02:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien1.github.io/mobile-marketing/how-to-include-mobile-marketing-into-your-advertising-409/</guid>
      <description>It’s easy to create effective mobile marketing campaigns using apps and games … this short video aims to demonstrate whats possible
Mobile Advertising and Mobile Games</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to use Competitions &amp;amp; Social Media to grow your mobile marketing</title>
      <link>https://damien1.github.io/mobile-marketing/how-to-use-competitions-social-media-to-grow-your-business-399/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jan 2010 23:18:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien1.github.io/mobile-marketing/how-to-use-competitions-social-media-to-grow-your-business-399/</guid>
      <description>Running competitions using social media is a good way for brands and businesses to create welcome visitors and friends to their sites. You can now take that competition mobile using mobile apps, games or mobile websites and you don’t have to use SMS.
Using Social Media to get your customers discovering you on their mobile Your marketing messages on social media sites like Twitter and Facebook can direct existing customers to discover your mobile website or to download a mobile app.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vote in my Mobile Marketing and Mobile Apps Poll</title>
      <link>https://damien1.github.io/mobile-marketing/vote-in-my-mobile-marketing-and-mobile-apps-poll-379/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Dec 2009 13:59:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien1.github.io/mobile-marketing/vote-in-my-mobile-marketing-and-mobile-apps-poll-379/</guid>
      <description>Take a vote … what do you do for mobile marketing and have you tried any mobile apps?
http://polls.linkedin.com/p/69091/tbhgt</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Social Media &amp;amp; Marketing Round-up of some good reading</title>
      <link>https://damien1.github.io/mobile-marketing/social-media-marketing-round-up-of-some-good-reading-375/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Dec 2009 16:36:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien1.github.io/mobile-marketing/social-media-marketing-round-up-of-some-good-reading-375/</guid>
      <description>**The problem with doing research on social media and mobile marketing is the overwhelming amount of noise you get from doing searches on Google, Delicious and Twitter.
**
Here are a few links of really useful and easy to consume ‘research’
best ‘inspirational’ video on social media
http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=sIFYPQjYhv8map of social media world
http://www.flickr.com/photos/wasabibratwurst/3128711125/sizes/l/top 100 companies by media spend</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>