<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>slideshare on Damien Saunders</title>
    <link>https://damien.co/tags/slideshare/</link>
    <description>Recent content in slideshare on Damien Saunders</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2011 09:29:56 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://damien.co/tags/slideshare/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Your ideas are wanted for my next Slideshare Presentation</title>
      <link>https://damien.co/general/your-ideas-are-wanted-for-my-next-slideshare-presentation-2508/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2011 09:29:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien.co/general/your-ideas-are-wanted-for-my-next-slideshare-presentation-2508/</guid>
      <description>Well hello Dear Reader
As you probably know – I really enjoy putting together a good presentation and publishing it on Slideshare— over the past year, I’ve averaged one presentation a month and managed to be featured on Slideshare 3 times.
So I’m looking for ideas on social media or marketing strategy or something else for my next presentation — and I’d like to have your ideas.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Slideshare Featured presentation of the day – get started with Foursquare</title>
      <link>https://damien.co/resources/slideshare-featured-presentation-of-the-day-get-started-with-foursquare-1938/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2010 11:51:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien.co/resources/slideshare-featured-presentation-of-the-day-get-started-with-foursquare-1938/</guid>
      <description>Here’s my newest Guide to getting started with Foursquareand it was selected by Slideshareas featured presentation on their homepage and on their business marketing section.The cat was definitely out of the bag on this … it’s had more than 460nearly 1000 views in one dayand a number of new favourites
Thanks to everyone for liking it!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>50 Completely Useful stats for social media &amp;amp; mobile marketing</title>
      <link>https://damien.co/mobile-marketing/50-completely-useful-stats-for-social-media-mobile-marketing-1002/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 May 2010 16:27:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien.co/mobile-marketing/50-completely-useful-stats-for-social-media-mobile-marketing-1002/</guid>
      <description>To understand more about Social Media and Mobile Marketing its important to get a few facts together on current trends and insights. 50 completely useful stats for social media does just that.
Why do this? well it helps to create some drive … and helps to understand why anyone or any business needs to do more in social media and mobile marketing.
**
**</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>