<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>multisite on Damien Saunders</title>
    <link>https://damien1.github.io/tags/multisite/</link>
    <description>Recent content in multisite on Damien Saunders</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2013 12:00:56 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://damien1.github.io/tags/multisite/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>HOW TO Get Started with WordPress Multisite &amp;#8211; build it in 5 minutes</title>
      <link>https://damien1.github.io/wordpress-multisite/get-started-with-wordpress-multisite-build-it-in-5-minutes-8659/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2013 12:00:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien1.github.io/wordpress-multisite/get-started-with-wordpress-multisite-build-it-in-5-minutes-8659/</guid>
      <description>WordPress Multisite or WordPress Network or WPMU – any of these refer to WordPress when it has been setup as a network of blogs or websites.
I’ve been using WordPress Multisite for about 3 years now – many more famous WordPress people have written about setting up WordPress Multisite, but this is my take on it.
I want to show you that it is easy to get started with WordPress Multisite in fact you can have your network of WordPress sites up in under 5 minutes (supposing you already have WordPress installed).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pros and Cons of Post Formats vs. WordPress Multisite</title>
      <link>https://damien1.github.io/blog/2012-07-17-pros-and-cons-of-post-types-vs-multiple-blogs/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jul 2012 11:41:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien1.github.io/blog/2012-07-17-pros-and-cons-of-post-types-vs-multiple-blogs/</guid>
      <description>WordPress is a flexible solution for web publishing. Post Formats were introduced a couple of years back to help users and developers to create content in one WYSIWYG Editorbut show it differently on the site. I’ll start by saying that there is quite a bit of press about why there is a general lack of support by theme developers for post formats(see one example below).
– If you have a theme which doesn’t support post formats (most don’t) then you can’t start this way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Change your WordPress Multi-Site Domain URL</title>
      <link>https://damien1.github.io/blog/2012-05-18-change-your-wordpress-multi-site-domain-url/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 May 2012 15:33:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien1.github.io/blog/2012-05-18-change-your-wordpress-multi-site-domain-url/</guid>
      <description>I’ve just finished changing my domain name URL for my WordPress multisite. After running WordPress as a network for nearly 2 years and managing a number of other WordPress sites, domain changes should be easy to do (but over time things get more complicated).
WordPress multisite adds a layer of complications – if you just want to update the domain URL for one of your blogs, then check out Domain Mapping plugins.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>