<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Migration on Damien Saunders</title>
    <link>http://damien.co/tags/migration/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Migration on Damien Saunders</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 15 Jun 2010 09:00:44 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://damien.co/tags/migration/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Startup Guide to building a website with WordPress</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/2010-06-15-startup-guide-to-building-a-website-with-wordpress-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jun 2010 09:00:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/2010-06-15-startup-guide-to-building-a-website-with-wordpress-2/</guid>
      <description>So your new business needs a website – and someone told you to build it using WordPress. Cool .. this collection of resources on WordPress for your new venture will help you:
How to migrate your website to WordPress– from experience and using a real life case study
9 essential plugins for WordPress– here’s my recommendations on WordPress plugins to get you started.
How to make a landing page template in WordPress– landing pages or static pages are great to promote a new product or service and its easy to add a landing page to WordPress</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Migrating your company website to WordPress Self Hosted</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/2010-03-08-migrating-your-company-website-to-wordpress-self-hosted-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Mar 2010 22:54:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/2010-03-08-migrating-your-company-website-to-wordpress-self-hosted-2/</guid>
      <description>WordPressis one of the most popular solutions for blogging. What people don’t know is that WordPress self hosted is the best solution for building a standalone SOHO / SME company website. We recently finished the migration of the mmCHANNEL company websitefrom an in-house developed website (using PHP, etc) to single install, self hosted WordPress installaton.There has been some times when I felt that maybe WordPress wasn’t right, but overall it’s going great and the results are visible!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>