<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>DBC Backup on Damien Saunders</title>
    <link>https://damien.co/tags/dbc-backup/</link>
    <description>Recent content in DBC Backup on Damien Saunders</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 05 Mar 2014 13:18:37 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://damien.co/tags/dbc-backup/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>DBC Backup 2 gets a significant re-write to support mysqli connector</title>
      <link>https://damien.co/blog/2014-03-05-dbc-backup-2-gets-significant-re-write-support-mysqli-connector/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Mar 2014 13:18:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien.co/blog/2014-03-05-dbc-backup-2-gets-significant-re-write-support-mysqli-connector/</guid>
      <description>DBC Backup 2 has just undergone a major update to use mysqli connector. This is a significant change as the PHP mysql connector has been flagged for removal since PHP v5.
For the first time the plugin will introduce a download function - allow a logged in admin user to download the backup file.
The new version is slated for release in the next week and is currently in stability testing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Open Letter to Users of DBC Backup (the old plugin)</title>
      <link>https://damien.co/blog/2012-12-03-open-letter-to-users-of-dbc-backup-the-old-plugin/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2012 22:09:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien.co/blog/2012-12-03-open-letter-to-users-of-dbc-backup-the-old-plugin/</guid>
      <description>So I noticed recently that Google has an index of everyone who has installed my plugin but hasn’t locked down their website. Which led me to wonder ‘If I could find these insecure sites via Google, should I warn them?’.
And so I did …
 I’m a WordPress developer in the UK and I look after a plugin called DBC-Backup-2.
I’ve always loved DBC-Backup ( a plugin you are are using on your website ), so when I found out that no one was maintaining it, I decided to ‘adopt’ DBC-Backup.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WordPress database backup plugin launched &amp;#8211; DBC Backup 2</title>
      <link>https://damien.co/blog/2012-07-11-dbc-backup-new-plugin-forked-from-the-old/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jul 2012 14:17:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien.co/blog/2012-07-11-dbc-backup-new-plugin-forked-from-the-old/</guid>
      <description>Announcing DBC Backup 2, a WordPress plugin to backup your WordPress SQL database is now available from WordPress Plugins.
DBC Backup 2 creates a SQL export and saves a compressed file to your web host server. Many web hosts provide large amounts of free space for storing your data so it makes sense to use this free space to safely store your database.
Key Features  Save time – set a Batch Job to run daily, weekly, monthly User Control – User defined path to store backups Compact – Compression of SQL exports (Gzip or Tar) saves space Safe – the export folder is ‘protected’ from prying eyes or direct downloads Save money – Uses web host to store export backups  Revival of DBC Backup The plugin is a revival of a much older plugin that I have used for a couple of years now.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>