<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>barcode on Damien Saunders</title>
    <link>http://damien.co/tags/barcode/</link>
    <description>Recent content in barcode on Damien Saunders</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 19 May 2011 13:10:47 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://damien.co/tags/barcode/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>British Airways mobile app could do with its own QR Code</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/mobile-marketing/british-airways-mobile-app-could-do-with-its-own-qr-code-3103/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 May 2011 13:10:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/mobile-marketing/british-airways-mobile-app-could-do-with-its-own-qr-code-3103/</guid>
      <description>This billboard stands out as an example – Just an example of how disconnected ‘real world’ traditional marketing is from integrated digital marketing.
Great – several airlines have now got mobile apps that allow you to seemingly, easily get from home to the airplane.
What’s wrong with this advert?   It’s only for iPhone – the image tells me straight away that here is another brand ignoring ‘other’ smartphones (or the only customers BA is helping are iOS device users)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>10 things to do with your Android and a Barcode Scanner</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/android/10-things-to-do-with-your-android-and-a-barcode-scanner-304/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Nov 2009 10:30:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/android/10-things-to-do-with-your-android-and-a-barcode-scanner-304/</guid>
      <description>There’s no better sound than the reassuring ‘Beep at the Checkout Register’. So now you have your own Android mobile phone …here’s a few barcode scanning things you can do at home or in the shops.
First you need the best Android Barcode Scanner – which now has integration with Google search on the mobile.
 Add a book to your Amazon Wishlist – just snap the barcode and save to list Catalogue your books at home using Anobiit from Anobii Catalogue your CD’s with Kooaba Look up reviews of that Wine you’ve just been drinking – Wine by the Bar is the perfect app for you Compare prices for that Electrical Gadget – Scan the Barcode and search online for it Create your own Barcode – After installing Barcode Scanner, open your Android Contacts .</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>