<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Axure on Damien Saunders</title>
    <link>http://damien.co/tags/axure/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Axure on Damien Saunders</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 28 May 2012 16:07:55 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://damien.co/tags/axure/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Axure &amp;#038; Twitter Bootstrap - Added split button drop-up (now on BitBucket)</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/customer-experience-2/axure/axure-twitter-bootstrap-added-split-button-drop-up-now-on-bitbucket-7175/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 May 2012 16:07:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/customer-experience-2/axure/axure-twitter-bootstrap-added-split-button-drop-up-now-on-bitbucket-7175/</guid>
      <description>Small but important update for my Axure Twitter Bootstrap Widget Library. It&amp;rsquo;s now got the recently added Split-Button drop-up and I&amp;rsquo;ve hosted it on BitBucket.
Linkage Download latest release from Bitbucket</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Axure - workflow for business process &amp;#038; web applications</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/customer-experience-2/axure/axure-workflow-for-business-process-web-applications-7055/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 May 2012 13:05:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/customer-experience-2/axure/axure-workflow-for-business-process-web-applications-7055/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s pretty easy to jump in the deep end with Axure and start building wireframes and hi-fi clickable prototypes. But the joy of Axure is starting low-fi (use Post-It Notes) to map a user journey and then create this process flow in Axure. Following a workflow like this means you get the customer journey mapped and you easily link your Axure wireframes to business processes.
I&amp;rsquo;ve been using Axure for more than a year and it&amp;rsquo;s now my tool of choice for mapping customer journeys and user interaction design.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Axure - more on responsive designs</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/resources/axure-more-on-responsive-designs-6657/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Apr 2012 09:43:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/resources/axure-more-on-responsive-designs-6657/</guid>
      <description>Axure is a really great tool for generating an interactive prototype and doing something more amazing with wireframes.
I&amp;rsquo;m one step closer to something resembling the current state of responsive and I&amp;rsquo;ve updated my example of responsive design …. http://share.axure.com/VLO0IZ/If you read anything about responsive or mobile design then check out Luke Wroblewski as he proposes 4 device screen widths to design for.
Using a centred layout with Axure you can cover &amp;lsquo;all&amp;rsquo; devices larger then a 1024 / 960 grid (if that&amp;rsquo;s what you use) — so that&amp;rsquo;s 2 devices.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Axure - Responsive layout &amp;#038; browser width</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/resources/axure-responsive-layout-browser-width-6548/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Apr 2012 13:33:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/resources/axure-responsive-layout-browser-width-6548/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve been playing around with scroll spy and re-creating this effect in Axure. Now, I&amp;rsquo;ve started to tackle responsive layout and browser width.
Axure is a great tool for making wireframes come to life … seriously. When you&amp;rsquo;re building a web or mobile application you&amp;rsquo;re better off with a complete clickable prototype then leaving your client guessing.
Responsive layout in Axure This is a bit more complex - but start with a Dynamic Panel and (using the newer Axure v6.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Axure Sticky Nav &amp;#038; Scroll Spy part 2</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/resources/axure-sticky-nav-scroll-spy-part-2-6286/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Mar 2012 11:00:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/resources/axure-sticky-nav-scroll-spy-part-2-6286/</guid>
      <description>I wanted another go at the scroll spy and sticky nav bar effect in Axure … which I previously wrote about. Reason being I like scroll spy and wanted to show a more complex and sensitive version.
Axure Scroll Spy, Sticky Nav &amp;amp; Pin to Browser This latest Axure scroll spy exampleshow
 Header which sticks at the top Navbar which becomes sticky when you scroll Buttons that change selected state while you scroll  Image Map Regions I&amp;rsquo;ve make a lot of use of Image Map Regions to provide &amp;lsquo;feedback&amp;rsquo; as you scroll.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Axure - Create Scroll Spy and Sticky Nav Bars like Twitter Bootstrap</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/resources/axure-create-scroll-spy-and-sticky-nav-bars-like-twitter-bootstrap-6256/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2012 10:09:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/resources/axure-create-scroll-spy-and-sticky-nav-bars-like-twitter-bootstrap-6256/</guid>
      <description>Have you seen Twitter Bootstrapand liked scrollspy javascript? Perhaps you want to use it in Axure to create floating navbars and sticky toolbars?
Are you impressed by Twitter Bootstrap? Some are, some aren&amp;rsquo;t - but I don&amp;rsquo;t know what the fuss is about - if you&amp;rsquo;ve got an amazing framework that is responsive and ready to go for your next startup - what&amp;rsquo;s not to love about it? It saves some design time and some development time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Axure Twitter Bootstrap Widget Library v0.1</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/resources/axure-twitter-bootstrap-widget-library-v0-1-6219/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Mar 2012 22:35:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/resources/axure-twitter-bootstrap-widget-library-v0-1-6219/</guid>
      <description>Twitter Bootstrap provides a great CSS framework and design philosophy making it easy to get going with your new web-based enterprise. So it only seemed natural Axure needs a widget library for Twitter Bootstrap.
Axurehas been my tool of choice for UX / UI wireframing and prototyping since July 2011. It was forced on me. Having been a fan of Omnigraffle and Balsamiq, I was resistant to change. Then I discovered the power of templates, generators and prototypes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FREE DOWNLOAD Axure Wireframe &amp;#038; Prototype for iPad</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/resources/free-download-axure-wireframe-prototype-for-ipad-4464/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Oct 2011 11:45:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/resources/free-download-axure-wireframe-prototype-for-ipad-4464/</guid>
      <description>I recently started using Axure for wire framing and creating clickable prototypes. I enjoyed it so much that I started to put together my own project for the Apple iPad with masters and a basic set of wireframes.
FREE Download iPad Axure Project Yes, it&amp;rsquo;s a free download and can be used under Creative Commons - CC-Attribution and you can use it for commercial and non-commercial projects. Just let me know please.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Using Axure for wireframes &amp;#038; user experience</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/resources/using-axure-for-wireframes-user-experience-4430/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Oct 2011 12:57:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/resources/using-axure-for-wireframes-user-experience-4430/</guid>
      <description>Recently I discovered Axure as a tool for mapping user experience - and I have to say it&amp;rsquo;s pretty damn good. Given that its also able to generate clickable prototypes along with documentation like functional specifications this is more then pretty damn good. It&amp;rsquo;s a powerful tool - but if you&amp;rsquo;re building user journeys, wire framing and process flows can be easier to do in other tools.
It&amp;rsquo;s hard to compare Axure to Balsamiq, Visio or Omnigraffle - particularly on price since Axure starts at around $580 per licence.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>