<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>web design on Damien Saunders</title>
    <link>http://damien.co/tags/web-design/</link>
    <description>Recent content in web design on Damien Saunders</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 16 Nov 2011 23:04:49 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://damien.co/tags/web-design/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Migrating your company website to WordPress Self Hosted</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/wordpress/migrating-your-company-website-to-wordpress-self-hosted-697/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Nov 2011 23:04:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/wordpress/migrating-your-company-website-to-wordpress-self-hosted-697/</guid>
      <description>WordPressis one of the most popular solutions for blogging. What people don&amp;rsquo;t know is that WordPress self hosted is the best solution for building a standalone B2B or SME company website. We recently finished the migration of the mmCHANNEL company website from an in-house developed website (using PHP, etc) to single install, self hosted WordPress installation.
There were a few times when I felt that maybe WordPress wasn&amp;rsquo;t right, but overall it&amp;rsquo;s going great and the results are visible!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Facebook Wants your Homepage</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/social-media/facebook-wants-your-homepage-2811/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Mar 2011 07:05:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/social-media/facebook-wants-your-homepage-2811/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m not one to always login to Facebook … It&amp;rsquo;s a good week if I don&amp;rsquo;t log in at all. But for about 500 million people Facebook is pretty important.
As if Facebook really needed to tell you to bookmark their site if you already go there - but this bookmarket / on-site advertising is a fresh change to the usual page prompting you to login from your mobile.
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcome 2011 time for a spring clean</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/welcome-2011-time-for-a-spring-clean-2428/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2011 10:19:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/welcome-2011-time-for-a-spring-clean-2428/</guid>
      <description>Hello 2011 — long may you last! If you&amp;rsquo;re new to my site … then Hello to you too. It&amp;rsquo;s time for a spring clean and over the next few days, I&amp;rsquo;ll be tearing everything apart on the website.
In the first stage, I have taken down the old WordPress website and replaced it with a WordPress Network or Multisite - which means I can make a network of blogs or websites … or more likely microsites for social media marketing campaigns and promotions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best iPad App for design and graphics gets better</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/best-ipad-app-for-design-and-graphics-gets-better-1857/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Nov 2010 10:59:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/best-ipad-app-for-design-and-graphics-gets-better-1857/</guid>
      <description>Sketchbook Pro, in my opinion is the best iPad app for photo editing, graphic and web design. And its new update just makes it better. The new release makes it a great all round tool for note taking, wireframe and web design.
A Power tool for notes, sketches and mockups I like to think I&amp;rsquo;m a pro digital photographer so I like my photo software to do amazing things - even if I cant.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Startup Guide to building a website with WordPress</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/2010-06-15-startup-guide-to-building-a-website-with-wordpress/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jun 2010 09:00:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/2010-06-15-startup-guide-to-building-a-website-with-wordpress/</guid>
      <description>So your new business needs a website - and someone told you to build it using WordPress. Cool .. this collection of resources on WordPress for your new venture will help you:
How to migrate your website to WordPress- from experience and using a real life case study
9 essential plugins for WordPress- here&amp;rsquo;s my recommendations on WordPress plugins to get you started.
How to make a landing page template in WordPress- landing pages or static pages are great to promote a new product or service and its easy to add a landing page to WordPress</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>App of the day: Balsamiq - wireframing and user experience design</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/2009-09-30-app-of-the-day-balsamiq-wireframing-and-user-experience-design/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Sep 2009 13:48:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/2009-09-30-app-of-the-day-balsamiq-wireframing-and-user-experience-design/</guid>
      <description>Balsamiq - I love it - the fonts and stuff can seem a bit cheesy … but I&amp;rsquo;ve take to this like a duck to water. Its much more useful than powerpoint, visio or other tools as its designed for wireframing.
Being built on Adobe Air means anyone can use it.
It&amp;rsquo;s very quick to create a UE design and while I couldn&amp;rsquo;t find a template or mockup for cell phone / mobile phone.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>