<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Essential on Damien Saunders</title>
    <link>http://damien.co/tags/essential/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Essential on Damien Saunders</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 23 Jul 2010 15:00:03 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://damien.co/tags/essential/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Essential Collection to Get Started with Foursquare</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/resources/essential-collection-to-get-started-with-foursquare-1301/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jul 2010 15:00:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/resources/essential-collection-to-get-started-with-foursquare-1301/</guid>
      <description>If you’re new to _Foursquare_ or your business is wondering how to leverage geolocation social networks in areas like sales and marketing, customer service or retention then this _essential collection_ will help you to get started.Of course, when you first started using Facebook, Foursquare, Gowalla, MySpace, etc, etc your initial experience is about ‘what does this do for me’, not ‘what can my business do with this’. If your business is new to this then take a look at my social media marketing kit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Essential Location Based Apps for Android Mobiles</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/2010-07-12-essential-location-based-apps-for-android-mobiles/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2010 09:00:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/2010-07-12-essential-location-based-apps-for-android-mobiles/</guid>
      <description>Everyone is used to taking their mobile with them, so that means location basedapps for mobiles will start to become more popular. A recent issue of Wired noted that it was thanks to Foursquare&amp;amp; Gowalla, that people are now getting more used to sharing their location. On a fun side, many of the new location based mobile apps have games or allow you to collect rewards for visiting new places. Here’s an essential list of location based apps for Androidmobile.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best Collection of Tools for Twitter you Need</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/social-media/best-collection-tool-for-twitter-you-need-1076/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jun 2010 23:16:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/social-media/best-collection-tool-for-twitter-you-need-1076/</guid>
      <description>Here’s a collection of the best tools for Twitter for any Social Media Specialist or Community Manager.
Twitter is a powerful tool for getting your message out there. Just like starting a new business, you need to have a guide that shows you how to make the most out of Twitter.** **
Managing your Tweets Tweetdeck – http://www.tweetdeck.com/
set up lots of columns and lists to watch all your Tweeting</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>