<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>iphone on Damien Saunders</title>
    <link>https://damien.co/tags/iphone/</link>
    <description>Recent content in iphone on Damien Saunders</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 20 Apr 2010 15:00:09 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://damien.co/tags/iphone/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Android Markets – Going International – advice for developers, VCs &amp;amp; startups</title>
      <link>https://damien.co/general/android-markets-going-international-advice-for-developers-vcs-startups-874/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Apr 2010 15:00:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien.co/general/android-markets-going-international-advice-for-developers-vcs-startups-874/</guid>
      <description>Developing for Android? You need to look to the bigger picture … actually this applies to anyone developing apps for mobile phones. If you want your app to be used by people that don’t speak English you need to translate it and provide some support.
There are going to be many opportunities for startups and anyone with a business model to go ‘international’ or expand abroad should check these points are covered in the marketing and product development plans.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Could it be Tesco Mobile selling iPhone? or just Tesco Supermarkets</title>
      <link>https://damien.co/general/could-it-be-tesco-mobile-selling-iphone-or-just-tesco-supermarkets-368/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Nov 2009 11:00:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien.co/general/could-it-be-tesco-mobile-selling-iphone-or-just-tesco-supermarkets-368/</guid>
      <description>Sounds like good news in the UK market ‘opening’ up to more distribution channels for the iPhone. Tesco’s annouced it plans to start selling the iPhone by the end of the year and promised to add value to the market, where prices are stagnating between O2 and Orange.
What this means is that Tesco will be just another distributor like the Carphone Warehouse — and so at first, it didn’t seem clear if customers will have a choice of O2 or Orange.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Does building an iPhone App make cents? sense?</title>
      <link>https://damien.co/general/does-building-an-iphone-make-cents-sense-348/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Nov 2009 19:36:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien.co/general/does-building-an-iphone-make-cents-sense-348/</guid>
      <description>With the boom in the number of apps in the App Store (over 100,000) and total downloads in excess of 2bn … someone has got to be making money … right?In part, the iPhone does offer a better platform for apps – it’s about to overtake RIM as the leading consumer smartphone, sold more than 34 million units and got some of the highest mobile internet usage rates we’ve seen so far.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>An Apple a Day &amp;#8230; more operators to sell iPhone</title>
      <link>https://damien.co/general/an-apple-a-day-more-operators-to-sell-iphone-325/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Sep 2009 16:00:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien.co/general/an-apple-a-day-more-operators-to-sell-iphone-325/</guid>
      <description>Following on yesterday’s news that Orange Uk will start selling iPhone … ending O2 / Telefonica’s virtual monopoly in the UK. Today, Vodafone in UK and Ireland announced their plans to sell Apple iPhones.
Good news for the operators? well ending the monopoly of iPhone was a good move. An operator with a data usage strategy will want to be selling iPhones along side other data hungry phones like RIM, Android, Symbian devices.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>