<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Release on Damien Saunders</title>
    <link>http://damien.co/tags/release/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Release on Damien Saunders</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2013 16:20:17 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://damien.co/tags/release/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>WordPress 3.4 RC2</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/2012-06-06-wordpress-3-4-rc2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jun 2012 21:03:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/2012-06-06-wordpress-3-4-rc2/</guid>
      <description>The second release candidate for the next version of WordPress 3.4 is here and the project team is hoping to go live next week.
WordPress 3.4 what you can expect WordPress 3.4 has had a couple of beta releases and 1 RC - so this is getting close to the finished product.
WordPress 3.4 has some cool features - including Theme customisation which kind of like a WordPress Getting Started Wizard.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE TIME - WordPress 3.3.1 released</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/2012-01-03-update-time-wordpress-3-3-1-released/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2012 22:41:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/2012-01-03-update-time-wordpress-3-3-1-released/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to 2012, it&amp;rsquo;s &amp;lsquo;barely&amp;rsquo; the first day of work and the WordPress team have released WordPress 3.3.1. This is a security and bug fix release which means it&amp;rsquo;s time to update as this is a mandatory update for us all.
What&amp;rsquo;s in this release?
This release is just 2 weeks after the big update to 3.3 so don&amp;rsquo;t be expecting anything new. Release 3.3.1 addresses a security issue with &amp;lsquo;cross site scripting&amp;rsquo; and 15 other maintenance fixes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WordPress 3.3 RC3 - This has to be it</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/2011-12-12-wordpress-3-3-rc3-this-has-to-be-it/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2011 09:03:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/2011-12-12-wordpress-3-3-rc3-this-has-to-be-it/</guid>
      <description>The third and final release candidate of WordPress 3.3 is here. AND … now we know that hopefully next week the real WordPress 3.3 will be here.
The release note hints that everything is ready. This version RC3 WordPress 3.3 has a few last minute bug fixes and tidy up.
If you haven&amp;rsquo;t started testing WordPress 3.3, then now is the time to check plugins, themes and familiarise yourself.
 WordPress 3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WordPress 3.3 RC2 is here</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/2011-12-08-wordpress-3-3-rc2-is-here/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2011 22:12:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/2011-12-08-wordpress-3-3-rc2-is-here/</guid>
      <description>The second release candidate for the next version of WordPress 3.3 is here.
If you develop stuff and haven&amp;rsquo;t started testing your plugins or theme, now is the time.
 WordPress 3.3 what you can expect WordPress 3.3 has already had 4 beta releases - so this RC could be the last one. From experience, this is just bug checking, tidy up and fixing last minute security things.
You can expect the real thing before Christmas!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WordPress 3.3 beta 3 is here</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/2011-11-10-wordpress-3-3-beta-3-is-here/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2011 12:33:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/2011-11-10-wordpress-3-3-beta-3-is-here/</guid>
      <description>WordPress 3.3 is on its way … the latest beta 3.3 is now available, which means you can download it and try it for yourself. This beta doesn&amp;rsquo;t add anything new, as the official post says &amp;lsquo;it&amp;rsquo;s all about making things prettier&amp;rsquo; along with lots of bug fixes.
Typically you can expect to get a release candidate after this and then the official thing will be here.
Should I update to this beta?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WordPress 3.3 enters public beta</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/2011-10-30-wordpress-3-3-enters-public-beta/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Oct 2011 17:18:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/2011-10-30-wordpress-3-3-enters-public-beta/</guid>
      <description>WordPress 3.3 is on its way … it&amp;rsquo;s entered public beta, which means you can download it and try it for yourself. Don&amp;rsquo;t try this at home if you&amp;rsquo;re new to WordPress.
WordPress 3.3 does a lot for admin and logged in users WordPress 3.3 has some cool features - including much more work on the WordPress Toolbar for logged in users, changes to backend admin pages and minor improvements for multisite admins.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WordPress 3.2 Release Candidate is here</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/social-media/wordpress-3-2-release-candidate-is-here-3-4440/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jun 2011 20:10:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/social-media/wordpress-3-2-release-candidate-is-here-3-4440/</guid>
      <description>The second release candidate for the next version of WordPress 3.2 is here. If you haven&amp;rsquo;t started testing 3.2, now is the time. Previous experience would make this the final RC before the real deal.
 Should I update to this release candidate? As this is a release candidate you shouldn&amp;rsquo;t use this on a really important live site - but it does mean it&amp;rsquo;s pretty stable and useful. You should find that most popular plugins and themes have no issues as developers have been working since RC1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WordPress 3.2 Release Candidate is here</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/2011-06-27-wordpress-3-2-release-candidate-is-here-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jun 2011 19:10:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/2011-06-27-wordpress-3-2-release-candidate-is-here-2/</guid>
      <description>The second release candidate for the next version of WordPress 3.2 is here. If you haven&amp;rsquo;t started testing 3.2, now is the time. Previous experience would make this the final RC before the real deal.
 Should I update to this release candidate? As this is a release candidate you shouldn&amp;rsquo;t use this on a really important live site - but it does mean it&amp;rsquo;s pretty stable and useful. You should find that most popular plugins and themes have no issues as developers have been working since RC1.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>