<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Marketing on Damien Saunders</title>
    <link>http://damien.co/categories/marketing/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Marketing on Damien Saunders</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2013 22:46:35 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://damien.co/categories/marketing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>DBC Backup 2  new version is ready for you</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/2013-12-14-dbc-backup-2-new-version-ready/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2013 22:46:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/2013-12-14-dbc-backup-2-new-version-ready/</guid>
      <description>DBC Backup 2 is a WordPress plugin that creates backups of your database. DBC Backup 2 has just been update to v2.3.24.
DBC Backup 2 has been completely redesigned and looks great as part of WordPress 3.8.
What&amp;rsquo;s new in DBC Backup 2 The latest version of DBC Backup 2 includes a number of significant changes
 Support for PHP 5.x - resolves issue which required a manual work around / blocked importing backup files Support for MySQL 5.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Looking for customer feedback - meetings in Australia or NZ</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/2013-11-10-looking-customer-feedback-meetings-australia-nz/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Nov 2013 15:36:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/2013-11-10-looking-customer-feedback-meetings-australia-nz/</guid>
      <description>Hi all
I&amp;rsquo;m travelling over the next 3 weeks to Australia and New Zealand and would like to meet up with customers or users of my WordPress plugins.
If you&amp;rsquo;re in Sydney or Auckland please say hi!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Visual Layouts Filtrify &amp;#038; Isotope Visual Layouts - will they work with your WordPress Theme?</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/2013-04-07-visual-layouts-filtrify-isotope-visual-layouts-with-your-wordpress-theme/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2013 20:48:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/2013-04-07-visual-layouts-filtrify-isotope-visual-layouts-with-your-wordpress-theme/</guid>
      <description>Hi Damien,
I&amp;rsquo;m about to start using your amazing plugins and was wondering if you could offer me some advice. Is it possible for me to use your filtering capability with this WordPress theme …
To be honest … I think I&amp;rsquo;m better off with just the plugins.
Thanks
 I recently received this email and thought I&amp;rsquo;d write up a few notes on my plugins. Right or Wrong … If you like the style of your theme, WordPress plugins are there to extend the function of your site.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pro Plugin - New User Guides &amp;amp; Support tools</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/2013-04-05-pro-plugin-new-user-guides-support-tools/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2013 09:52:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/2013-04-05-pro-plugin-new-user-guides-support-tools/</guid>
      <description>Until a few days ago, I&amp;rsquo;d been relying on e-mail to manage your support requests. During the past 3 months I&amp;rsquo;ve looked at different options to provide support and also publish user guides and support material - beyond what&amp;rsquo;s in the readme files.
Announcing Help &amp;amp; User Guides for Pro Plugins Anyone who has brought a Pro plugin from me, will now get access to Help
Key features of the new site include:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Make an impact using integrated marketing. Use these best WordPress plugins</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/2011-10-31-make-an-impact-using-integrated-marketing-use-these-best-wordpress-plugins/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2011 11:00:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/2011-10-31-make-an-impact-using-integrated-marketing-use-these-best-wordpress-plugins/</guid>
      <description>Integrated marketing with WordPress is easy - you only need a few plugins to have a powerful website at the heart of your digital marketing.
WordPress plugins there are thousands to choose from and they are so easy to install. I tend to be cutting edge and try new plugins a lot , but here are some of the best plugins to improve WordPress for social media and digital marketing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Social Media Marketing with WordPress needs a good theme</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/2011-07-04-social-media-marketing-with-wordpress-needs-a-good-theme/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jul 2011 15:02:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/2011-07-04-social-media-marketing-with-wordpress-needs-a-good-theme/</guid>
      <description>Get a good theme - it&amp;rsquo;s all about the instant appeal that any visitor has when they first land on your site. WordPress has many themes suited for social media marketing with a magazine layout, a featured panel and ready to go marketing plugins.
Why WordPress? WordPress is one of the world’s most popular solutions for blogging
If you’re reading and researching Why WordPress - you’ll probably see many articles focus on three words - Free, Simple &amp;amp; Easy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lithuanian Youth love to use the Internet</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/lithuanian-youth-love-to-use-the-internet-1383/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Aug 2010 10:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/lithuanian-youth-love-to-use-the-internet-1383/</guid>
      <description>In Lithuania the usage of the internet is reaching saturation point. A 2009 official report shows 95% of young people aged 16-24 with internet access**.**
Lithuania has one of the highest per capita access to broadband ratios due to small land mass and population of just under 4 million. It&amp;rsquo;s also atypical of &amp;lsquo;westernised&amp;rsquo; European markets and the Lithuanian youth are no different - wanting mobile phones, good clothes, good education and a future with a good job (most likely in London).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>