<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Marketing on Damien Saunders</title>
    <link>https://damien1.github.io/categories/marketing/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Marketing on Damien Saunders</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2013 22:46:35 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://damien1.github.io/categories/marketing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>DBC Backup 2  new version is ready for you</title>
      <link>https://damien1.github.io/blog/2013-12-14-dbc-backup-2-new-version-ready/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2013 22:46:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien1.github.io/blog/2013-12-14-dbc-backup-2-new-version-ready/</guid>
      <description>DBC Backup 2 is a WordPress plugin that creates backups of your database. DBC Backup 2 has just been update to v2.3.24.
DBC Backup 2 has been completely redesigned and looks great as part of WordPress 3.8.
What&amp;rsquo;s new in DBC Backup 2 The latest version of DBC Backup 2 includes a number of significant changes
 Support for PHP 5.x - resolves issue which required a manual work around / blocked importing backup files Support for MySQL 5.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Looking for customer feedback - meetings in Australia or NZ</title>
      <link>https://damien1.github.io/blog/2013-11-10-looking-customer-feedback-meetings-australia-nz/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Nov 2013 15:36:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien1.github.io/blog/2013-11-10-looking-customer-feedback-meetings-australia-nz/</guid>
      <description>Hi all
I&amp;rsquo;m travelling over the next 3 weeks to Australia and New Zealand and would like to meet up with customers or users of my WordPress plugins.
If you&amp;rsquo;re in Sydney or Auckland please say hi!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Visual Layouts Filtrify &amp;#038; Isotope Visual Layouts &amp;#8211; will they work with your WordPress Theme?</title>
      <link>https://damien1.github.io/blog/2013-04-07-visual-layouts-filtrify-isotope-visual-layouts-with-your-wordpress-theme/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2013 20:48:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien1.github.io/blog/2013-04-07-visual-layouts-filtrify-isotope-visual-layouts-with-your-wordpress-theme/</guid>
      <description>I recently received this email and thought I’d write up a few notes on my plugins. Right or Wrong … If you like the style of your theme, WordPress plugins are there to extend the function of your site. This means you don’t have to replace your existing theme just to get a new feature.
 Want to get a cool theme instead? If you do like the style / grid layout that I’m showing and want to replace your theme … then checkout the WooThemes range of themes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pro Plugin &amp;#8211; New User Guides &amp;amp; Support tools</title>
      <link>https://damien1.github.io/blog/2013-04-05-pro-plugin-new-user-guides-support-tools/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2013 09:52:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien1.github.io/blog/2013-04-05-pro-plugin-new-user-guides-support-tools/</guid>
      <description>Until a few days ago, I’d been relying on e-mail to manage your support requests. During the past 3 months I’ve looked at different options to provide support and also publish user guides and support material – beyond what’s in the readme files.
Announcing Help &amp;amp; User Guides for Pro Plugins Anyone who has brought a Pro plugin from me, will now get access to Help &amp;amp; User Docsjust visit http://docs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1 minute video &amp;#8211; Isotope Visual Layouts WordPress plugin</title>
      <link>https://damien1.github.io/blog/2013-03-18-1-minute-video-isotope-visual-layouts-wordpress-plugin/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2013 11:57:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien1.github.io/blog/2013-03-18-1-minute-video-isotope-visual-layouts-wordpress-plugin/</guid>
      <description>Just been on a bit of a testing mission this weekend … I’ve put together this 1 minute screen recording of my WordPress plugin Isotope Visual Layouts.
The video is taken from my Selenium based testing and goes from plugin install, checking plugin options, adding a page, viewing the results and finally deleting the plugin.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Isotope Visual Layouts lite &amp;#8211; gets an update &amp;amp; a new name</title>
      <link>https://damien1.github.io/blog/2013-02-22-isotope-visual-layouts-lite-gets-an-update-a-new-name/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2013 11:00:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien1.github.io/blog/2013-02-22-isotope-visual-layouts-lite-gets-an-update-a-new-name/</guid>
      <description>WordPress is a great tool for Websites, Blogs, Ecommerce and pretty much anything else … Which is why Isotope Visual Layouts is such a great plugin. Now you can easily change your website without changing your theme.
How to Update / Upgrade Isotope Visual Layouts lite – slightly newer name – has just had an update to v2 and if you already have it installed, you can get an update / upgrade from your Admin Plugin page (see image below).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Visual Layouts plugin for WordPress featuring Freetile</title>
      <link>https://damien1.github.io/blog/2012-11-12-visual-layouts-plugin-for-wordpress-featuring-freetile/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Nov 2012 11:39:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien1.github.io/blog/2012-11-12-visual-layouts-plugin-for-wordpress-featuring-freetile/</guid>
      <description>Visual Layoutsmy latest plugin for WordPress is here … and you can download it now.
Visual Layouts is a WordPress Plugin using Freetile.js to add visual animation and effects to your website.  3 Key Features of Visual Layouts  It’s Easy to install and no coding is required. Choose from 7 colour styles and it works with any posts, custom posts or pages. Choose to include or exclude the feature image  How to Download &amp;amp; Install Visual Layouts?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Make an impact using integrated marketing. Use these best WordPress plugins</title>
      <link>https://damien1.github.io/blog/2011-10-31-make-an-impact-using-integrated-marketing-use-these-best-wordpress-plugins/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2011 11:00:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien1.github.io/blog/2011-10-31-make-an-impact-using-integrated-marketing-use-these-best-wordpress-plugins/</guid>
      <description>Integrated marketing with WordPress is easy – you only need a few plugins to have a powerful website at the heart of your digital marketing.
WordPress plugins there are thousands to choose from and they are so easy to install. I tend to be cutting edge and try new plugins a lot , but here are some of the best plugins to improve WordPress for social media and digital marketing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Startup Guide to building a website with WordPress</title>
      <link>https://damien1.github.io/blog/2010-06-15-startup-guide-to-building-a-website-with-wordpress-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jun 2010 09:00:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien1.github.io/blog/2010-06-15-startup-guide-to-building-a-website-with-wordpress-2/</guid>
      <description>So your new business needs a website – and someone told you to build it using WordPress. Cool .. this collection of resources on WordPress for your new venture will help you:
How to migrate your website to WordPress– from experience and using a real life case study
9 essential plugins for WordPress– here’s my recommendations on WordPress plugins to get you started.
How to make a landing page template in WordPress– landing pages or static pages are great to promote a new product or service and its easy to add a landing page to WordPress</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>