<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>retail on Damien Saunders</title>
    <link>http://damien.co/tags/retail/</link>
    <description>Recent content in retail on Damien Saunders</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 13 Dec 2010 09:22:43 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://damien.co/tags/retail/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Ideas using Foursquare for Cafes &amp;amp; Restaurants</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/social-media/foursquare/ideas-using-foursquare-for-cafes-restaurants-2237/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Dec 2010 09:22:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/social-media/foursquare/ideas-using-foursquare-for-cafes-restaurants-2237/</guid>
      <description>To market to market to buy me a Foursquare… for Cafes &amp;amp; Restaurants it’s the time of the year when your customers maybe thinking of Christmas comforts to have at home so get them in your store now. Last week I started a new series focused on Ideas using Foursquarefor social media marketing with guides that will help increase customer satisfaction and improve retention. Today, will be looking at how can use social media marketing to offer some tasty food tidbits that leave your customers wanting to come back for seconds.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Case Study How to get 100 people in your retail store at the same time</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/resources/case-study-how-to-get-100-people-in-your-retail-store-at-the-same-time-1932/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2010 09:30:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/resources/case-study-how-to-get-100-people-in-your-retail-store-at-the-same-time-1932/</guid>
      <description>Regular followers of my work, will have seen an earlier case study on Foursquare marketing for retail and I’ve recently been updating this. So this week there are a couple of posts on the Swarm Badge Party that was organised in Latvia.Client Brief Bite Latvija just opened a new technical advice and support centre dedicated to questions about mobile broadband, device configuration and helping people get the most from their mobile.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Looking for insights on Mobile and Retail Sector?</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/mobile-marketing/looking-for-insights-on-mobile-and-retail-sector-440/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Feb 2010 17:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/mobile-marketing/looking-for-insights-on-mobile-and-retail-sector-440/</guid>
      <description>&amp;lt;div&amp;gt; The Whitepaper, ‘Mobile in Retail’, seeks to identify the potential for mobile to brands and retailers. It highlights 10 areas, including coupons and loyalty, where mobile is deemed to have a particular impact. The executive summary points to a number of areas of potential gain for businesses adopting mobile as a consumer engagement channel. These are increased sales; increased customer satisfaction and loyalty; and additional value to physical products and experiences through digital services.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UK album retail sales dip 11% for 2007</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/uk-album-retail-sales-dip-11-for-2007-68/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jan 2008 12:14:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/uk-album-retail-sales-dip-11-for-2007-68/</guid>
      <description>Album unbundling, copyright theft and difficult retail conditions contributed to a drop in album sales of 10.8% in 2007 say the British Phonographic Industry.The continued growth of download sales helped the singles market grow by 29.3% during 2007, which became the third biggest year on record for the format.Change = -10.8%Source: BPI website</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>