<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>insights on Damien Saunders</title>
    <link>http://damien.co/tags/insights/</link>
    <description>Recent content in insights on Damien Saunders</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2013 20:39:24 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://damien.co/tags/insights/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>2012 Website Statistics - Content Strategy is not buzz words like SEO</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/2012-website-statistics-awesome-8541/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2013 20:39:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/2012-website-statistics-awesome-8541/</guid>
      <description>2012 was the biggest year to date for web site visitors - and with good reason! So Thank You to everyone who came, read and left (and came back, again).
55,266 unique visitors clocked up 5.1 million seconds of visit duration but more importantly pages / visit and average visit duration also grew.
So what happened in 2012? Search Engine Optimisation (SEO) didn&amp;rsquo;t work out … but having a content strategy did.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Key trends in mobile usage from the UK</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/2012-07-18-key-trends-in-mobile-usage-from-the-uk/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jul 2012 15:23:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/2012-07-18-key-trends-in-mobile-usage-from-the-uk/</guid>
      <description>Mobile usage in the UK is on the increase. That&amp;rsquo;s all sounding good so far.
The latest communications report from Ofcom has shown a year on year growth of 1.6 million mobiles and the biggest growth in postpaid subscribers due to more customers taking out contracts for smartphones.
Want to download this for free? Read to the end of the presentation and copy the discount coupon code.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Social Gaming is on the decline? Blame cannibalisation by mobile and OTT</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/insights-blog/why-social-gaming-decline-blame-cannibalisation-mobile-ott-7316/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jun 2012 14:22:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/insights-blog/why-social-gaming-decline-blame-cannibalisation-mobile-ott-7316/</guid>
      <description>Social Gaming is on the decline - not terminal decline, just platform cannibalisation. Well mostly. Some Social Gamers just go off and play other newer games. The big reason for the decline in social game, I believe is the rise of free games in App Stores like Android Play and iTunes App Store. These App Stores provide a direct to user channel for promotion of games.
5 reasons Social Gaming is on the decline There are 5 reasons this is happening</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Get Results from an Android Mobile Marketing Strategy</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/mobile-marketing/get-results-from-an-android-mobile-marketing-strategy-5885/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2012 13:12:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/mobile-marketing/get-results-from-an-android-mobile-marketing-strategy-5885/</guid>
      <description>Android Mobiles are taking over the world … and that seems to be supported by the latest statistics or _trends. _If you&amp;rsquo;re thinking about mobile marketing .. and wondering &amp;lsquo;what is all the fuss about Android&amp;rsquo;, then this presentation is for you.
Only the latest Android Insights and Statistics  10 billion app downloads (December 2011) 200 million activated devices (November 2011) 400,000 Android Apps (December 2011)  We can only wait for the next Google I/O conference to confirm how these numbers are growing!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>4 reasons to choose Google Analytics for your business</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/marketing-consultant-2/4-reasons-to-choose-google-analytics-for-your-business-4932/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2011 16:13:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/marketing-consultant-2/4-reasons-to-choose-google-analytics-for-your-business-4932/</guid>
      <description>Google Analytics is one of the web’s most popular tools for reporting on activity and trends for just about any website. Your online and offline marketing activities need meaningful analytics data to create actionable insights. In summary, website analytics has benefits for sales, marketing and product development - in fact most areas of your business.
Why Choose Google Analytics? It&amp;rsquo;s easy to see why Google Analytics is so popular, because it&amp;rsquo;s free, but here are my top 4</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Could we do better? Short Web Survey from KISS Insights</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/2011-06-15-what-could-we-do-better-add-a-subtle-web-survey/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jun 2011 11:03:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/2011-06-15-what-could-we-do-better-add-a-subtle-web-survey/</guid>
      <description>What could we do to make this site more useful? That&amp;rsquo;s a good question … and thanks to Kiss Insights its really easy to ask this of your website visitors.
It&amp;rsquo;s only one answer &amp;amp; takes one second Web surveys should not be a bore and they should not be too long. We&amp;rsquo;re all so busy now and being asked to spend 15 mins on a survey is pointless.
I guess that&amp;rsquo;s what makes the KISS approach so powerful - keep it short and simple.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Understand your website visitors with live web stats with GoSquared</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/marketing-consultant-2/understand-your-website-visitors-with-live-web-stats-with-gosquared-3532/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2011 11:02:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/marketing-consultant-2/understand-your-website-visitors-with-live-web-stats-with-gosquared-3532/</guid>
      <description>I just started to use GoSquared this week - If you&amp;rsquo;ve got a high traffic website (well any website really) and want some real-time web analytics or insights - then you better get started with a FREE GoSquared account today. Using GoSquared I can watch as visitors come and go.
Free Web Analytics &amp;amp; insights  GoSquared monitors and analyses your website&amp;rsquo;s traffic in real-time - and you can watch all the action in the LiveStats console - which is like a 3 part Heads-Up Display.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Every Important Stat can be drawn in a 2&amp;#215;2 Grid</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/insights-blog/every-important-stat-can-be-drawn-in-a-2x2-grid-2800/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Mar 2011 09:10:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/insights-blog/every-important-stat-can-be-drawn-in-a-2x2-grid-2800/</guid>
      <description>Nolan Chart - XKCD
Just to prove a point - the 2×2 grid is the best way to show-off pretty much interesting statistic or insight</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DotCom Bubble Burst? Latest Internet Startup Valuations</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/social-media/dotcom-bubble-burst-latest-internet-startup-valuations-2789/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2011 09:50:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/social-media/dotcom-bubble-burst-latest-internet-startup-valuations-2789/</guid>
      <description>Startup Valuations got you feeling low? Maybe its time to buy into the dotcom bubble before it bursts. So ride the social media marketing wave …
via Guardian.co.uk
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gartner predicts App Store Revenue Forecast to Surpass $15 Billion in 2011</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/insights-blog/gartner-predicts-app-store-revenue-forecast-to-surpass-15-billion-in-2011-2656/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2011 07:53:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/insights-blog/gartner-predicts-app-store-revenue-forecast-to-surpass-15-billion-in-2011-2656/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve been on the lookout for this prediction … in 2010 Gartner predicted Worldwide Mobile App Revenues of xx Billion … for 2011 the prediction is for this to exceed $15 billion
2010 Where are the results! Given that Apple, Android, RIM, Nokia and a whole stack of operators and 3rd parties run mobile app stores - it&amp;rsquo;s extremely difficult to find out how good Gartner is at forecasts. Or is this just a large number guestimate?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>5,000,000 users on Foursquare now focus on activity &amp;amp; retention</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/social-media/foursquare/5000000-users-on-foursquare-now-focus-on-activity-retention-2212/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Dec 2010 13:00:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/social-media/foursquare/5000000-users-on-foursquare-now-focus-on-activity-retention-2212/</guid>
      <description>Foursquare this week should break through the 5 million users mark and it has taken about 8 weeks to add an extra million. While Foursquare is still the most popular of the location based social networks (anyone using SCVNGR??) other services are making a better play at location marketing.Slow down in the rate of new users The latest RJ Metrics graphic for Foursquare convincingly shows the decline in the week on week growth of new users.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NEWS: Price Grabber research says we spend more on the mobile</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/news-releases/news-price-grabber-research-says-we-spend-more-on-the-mobile-1347/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jul 2010 09:00:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/news-releases/news-price-grabber-research-says-we-spend-more-on-the-mobile-1347/</guid>
      <description>Finally some proof that Mobile Internet usage is profoundlyshaking up the way consumers shop, according to new research from PriceGrabber.co.uk. Of the 908 online shoppers that were asked about their mobile shopping habits, 66 percent owned a Smartphone or another Web-enabled phone. Of the consumers who shop from their mobile, nearly half (48 percent) claim that the convenience of having the Internet with them wherever they go is their number one reason for smart shopping.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Comparison of Digital Music Retailers in Europe</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/comparison-of-digital-music-retailers-in-europe-246/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Aug 2009 17:28:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/comparison-of-digital-music-retailers-in-europe-246/</guid>
      <description>Comment: There are a number of digital music retailers working around Europe, here is Damien Saunders&amp;rsquo; summary of a few of the bigger services (catalogue greater than 1 million tracks).
&amp;lt;td width=&amp;quot;75&amp;quot;&amp;gt; Countries &amp;lt;/td&amp;gt; &amp;lt;td width=&amp;quot;75&amp;quot;&amp;gt; MP3 to buy &amp;lt;/td&amp;gt; &amp;lt;td width=&amp;quot;79&amp;quot;&amp;gt; Subscription &amp;lt;/td&amp;gt; &amp;lt;td width=&amp;quot;75&amp;quot;&amp;gt; Catalogue Size &amp;lt;/td&amp;gt; &amp;lt;td width=&amp;quot;75&amp;quot;&amp;gt; 3rd Party API &amp;lt;/td&amp;gt; &amp;lt;td width=&amp;quot;75&amp;quot;&amp;gt; PC Software &amp;lt;/td&amp;gt;  &amp;lt;td width=&amp;quot;75&amp;quot;&amp;gt; UK &amp;lt;/td&amp;gt; &amp;lt;td width=&amp;quot;75&amp;quot;&amp;gt; Yes &amp;lt;/td&amp;gt; &amp;lt;td width=&amp;quot;79&amp;quot;&amp;gt; No &amp;lt;/td&amp;gt; &amp;lt;td width=&amp;quot;75&amp;quot;&amp;gt; 3.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>