<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Inbound Marketing on Damien Saunders</title>
    <link>https://damien1.github.io/tags/inbound-marketing/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Inbound Marketing on Damien Saunders</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 16 Nov 2011 23:04:49 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://damien1.github.io/tags/inbound-marketing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Migrating your company website to WordPress Self Hosted</title>
      <link>https://damien1.github.io/wordpress/migrating-your-company-website-to-wordpress-self-hosted-697/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Nov 2011 23:04:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien1.github.io/wordpress/migrating-your-company-website-to-wordpress-self-hosted-697/</guid>
      <description>WordPressis one of the most popular solutions for blogging. What people don’t know is that WordPress self hosted is the best solution for building a standalone B2B or SME company website. We recently finished the migration of the mmCHANNEL company website from an in-house developed website (using PHP, etc) to single install, self hosted WordPress installation.
There were a few times when I felt that maybe WordPress wasn’t right, but overall it’s going great and the results are visible!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best WordPress plugins for social media marketing</title>
      <link>https://damien1.github.io/wordpress/best-wordpress-plugins-for-social-media-marketing-2319/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jan 2011 09:20:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien1.github.io/wordpress/best-wordpress-plugins-for-social-media-marketing-2319/</guid>
      <description>Social Media Marketing plugins for WordPress – you only need a few to have a powerful integrated marketing website.
WordPress plugins there are millions(?) to choose from and they are so easy to install. I tend to be cutting edge and change my plugins often, but here are some of the best plugins to improve WordPress for social media and digital marketing.
The point here is that writing original content can be easy – but your great works need to be found.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>