<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>location on Damien Saunders</title>
    <link>https://damien.co/tags/location/</link>
    <description>Recent content in location on Damien Saunders</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 19 May 2011 13:10:47 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://damien.co/tags/location/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>British Airways mobile app could do with its own QR Code</title>
      <link>https://damien.co/mobile-marketing/british-airways-mobile-app-could-do-with-its-own-qr-code-3103/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 May 2011 13:10:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien.co/mobile-marketing/british-airways-mobile-app-could-do-with-its-own-qr-code-3103/</guid>
      <description>This billboard stands out as an example – Just an example of how disconnected ‘real world’ traditional marketing is from integrated digital marketing.
Great – several airlines have now got mobile apps that allow you to seemingly, easily get from home to the airplane.
What’s wrong with this advert?   It’s only for iPhone – the image tells me straight away that here is another brand ignoring ‘other’ smartphones (or the only customers BA is helping are iOS device users)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Easy Guide to Social Media Marketing &amp;amp; Location</title>
      <link>https://damien.co/resources/easy-guide-to-social-media-marketing-location-1316/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jul 2010 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien.co/resources/easy-guide-to-social-media-marketing-location-1316/</guid>
      <description>This easy guide to social media &amp;amp; location marketingwas something I published only to SlideShare – a new channel which has great potential for B2B digital marketing. This guide sums up key activities to get you started and is a bit of motivation that you can share with office colleagues. Key points include:
 Claim your Business on Foursquare Claim your Entry on Google Maps Create an Email Newsletter Create a Facebook Website Cross Promote using Twitter, Facebook and your website  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Foursquare most popular location checkin game in London</title>
      <link>https://damien.co/social-media/foursquare-most-popular-location-checkin-tool-in-london-1173/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jul 2010 09:00:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien.co/social-media/foursquare-most-popular-location-checkin-tool-in-london-1173/</guid>
      <description>Foursquare is still the UK’s most popular location based check-in game to play on your mobile. I’ve said it before that Foursquare would come out on tops over Gowalla and Brightkite.
These maps (thanks to Checkin Mania) indicate the difference in the number of locations that users have submitted to each service. The growth from crowd sourced locations and points of interest reflects in the growth of that services usage (ie the most popular service gets the most contributions from users) The point of reference is London Borough Market – one of the more famous places in London to visit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2 Must have Android Apps from Google</title>
      <link>https://damien.co/general/2-must-have-android-apps-from-google-for-your-htc-magic-or-g1-226/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2009 18:11:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien.co/general/2-must-have-android-apps-from-google-for-your-htc-magic-or-g1-226/</guid>
      <description>Looking for somewhere to go …. Maybe you need to waste some time or want to find something else to try on your Google Android G1 or HTC Magic.
Google obviously has embedded a lot things into the phone – but here are 2 apps that were not installed on the Android phone when you open the box.
Places DirectoryPrice FREE Downloads &amp;gt;250,000
updated — 21 Sept –– Even before augmented reality became a buzzword … Google Places Directory was already bringing Google Maps together with GPS / Location Based Services.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>