<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>b2b marketing on Damien Saunders</title>
    <link>http://damien.co/tags/b2b-marketing/</link>
    <description>Recent content in b2b marketing on Damien Saunders</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 30 Nov 2010 09:48:33 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://damien.co/tags/b2b-marketing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Have you tried LinkedIn lately?</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/social-media/have-you-tried-linkedin-lately-2033/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Nov 2010 09:48:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/social-media/have-you-tried-linkedin-lately-2033/</guid>
      <description>LinkedInhas been the business social networkof choice for many and its nearly 10 years old, but younger upstarts have such a mass that its time to look at what LinkedIn can offer to social media marketing, especially for b2b marketing.
There is value in personally knowing your connection When LinkedIn first launched it was not much more than a way to list your work history and connect with business colleagues. It was even important that you had the email address of someone before you could add them – which meant at least you had their business card as people wouldn’t accept requests to connect if they couldn’t remember how they met you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>b2b Marketing &amp;#8211; how to increase your content sales and improve your content</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/mobile-marketing/b2b-marketing-how-to-increase-your-content-sales-and-improve-your-content-812/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Mar 2010 23:29:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/mobile-marketing/b2b-marketing-how-to-increase-your-content-sales-and-improve-your-content-812/</guid>
      <description>A short guide with b2b marketing tips for improving your content sales and improve your content using mmCHANNEL’s new API.1. Got an upcoming marketing campaign? Need Content? Now any marketing campaign can include digital content like tones, songs, games from a selection of mmCHANNEL manages.
2. Drive traffic to your website or fanpage You can setup a content shop in your existing website using the mmCHANNEL b2bAPI with no need to build any other platforms</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>