<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Get Started on Damien Saunders</title>
    <link>http://damien.co/tags/get-started/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Get Started on Damien Saunders</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 May 2011 11:16:19 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://damien.co/tags/get-started/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Are you on top of your Social Media Marketing Strategy for 2011?</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/strategy/are-you-on-top-of-your-social-media-marketing-strategy-for-2011-3125/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2011 11:16:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/strategy/are-you-on-top-of-your-social-media-marketing-strategy-for-2011-3125/</guid>
      <description>You&amp;rsquo;re never too late to start your 2011 Social Media Marketing Strategy - This year has gone so fast and I missed starting my Marketing Strategy on 1/1/11. For many marketing people and businesses, developing your strategy is something usually done in the first 3 months of your financial year or calendar year.
If this is the approach your business currently takes, then realise that you&amp;rsquo;re leaving just 75% of the year to deliver 100% of what you set out to achieve.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Get started with WordPress for your business website &amp;#038; b2b marketing</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/2010-11-29-get-started-with-wordpress-for-your-business-website-b2b-marketing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2010 16:00:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/2010-11-29-get-started-with-wordpress-for-your-business-website-b2b-marketing/</guid>
      <description>Do you need a new website? Want to get started with Social Media Marketingand Blogging? Have you been enjoying the visual wonder of this website and blog that was built using WordPress?Now you can have your own custom built WordPressto your needs by me.Get your own WordPress business blog &amp;amp; website I&amp;rsquo;m offering free coaching in WordPress to get you started &amp;lsquo;immediately&amp;rsquo;.
Right now you can choose from 2 options which all include hosting and your own domain name.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>