<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Themes on Damien Saunders</title>
    <link>https://damien.co/tags/themes/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Themes on Damien Saunders</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2013 20:48:56 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://damien.co/tags/themes/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Visual Layouts Filtrify &amp;#038; Isotope Visual Layouts &amp;#8211; will they work with your WordPress Theme?</title>
      <link>https://damien.co/blog/2013-04-07-visual-layouts-filtrify-isotope-visual-layouts-with-your-wordpress-theme/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2013 20:48:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien.co/blog/2013-04-07-visual-layouts-filtrify-isotope-visual-layouts-with-your-wordpress-theme/</guid>
      <description>I recently received this email and thought I’d write up a few notes on my plugins. Right or Wrong … If you like the style of your theme, WordPress plugins are there to extend the function of your site. This means you don’t have to replace your existing theme just to get a new feature.
 Want to get a cool theme instead? If you do like the style / grid layout that I’m showing and want to replace your theme … then checkout the WooThemes range of themes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pros and Cons of Post Formats vs. WordPress Multisite</title>
      <link>https://damien.co/blog/2012-07-17-pros-and-cons-of-post-types-vs-multiple-blogs/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jul 2012 11:41:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien.co/blog/2012-07-17-pros-and-cons-of-post-types-vs-multiple-blogs/</guid>
      <description>WordPress is a flexible solution for web publishing. Post Formats were introduced a couple of years back to help users and developers to create content in one WYSIWYG Editorbut show it differently on the site. I’ll start by saying that there is quite a bit of press about why there is a general lack of support by theme developers for post formats(see one example below).
– If you have a theme which doesn’t support post formats (most don’t) then you can’t start this way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Get the best for free business and magazine theme for WordPress &amp;#8211; Thanks Woothemes</title>
      <link>https://damien.co/blog/2011-10-04-get-the-best-for-free-business-and-magazine-theme-for-wordpress-thanks-woothemes/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Oct 2011 11:36:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien.co/blog/2011-10-04-get-the-best-for-free-business-and-magazine-theme-for-wordpress-thanks-woothemes/</guid>
      <description>WooThemes have outdone themselves with their most recent free WordPress business theme. Swatchis a powerful business and magazine theme with its own slider / carousel and a custom homepage layout that has 3 widget areas and up to 4 footer widgets.
Seriously – this is the ultimate free theme for any business or serious blogger. It has 2 custom post types, along with the Slides on for the homepage it also has a portfolio for you to show off your work or presentations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HOW TO recover from the most common WordPress website killers</title>
      <link>https://damien.co/wordpress/how-to-recover-from-the-most-common-wordpress-website-killers-2-4432/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2011 16:31:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien.co/wordpress/how-to-recover-from-the-most-common-wordpress-website-killers-2-4432/</guid>
      <description>It’s easy to recover from the 2 most common errors that kill your WordPress website. Fix the issue in 3 simple steps.When something goes wrong WordPress the most common cause is a plugin conflict or a problem with your theme. There’s nothing worse then feeling you’ve been locked out from your own website and can’t get to the wp-admin section to login.
Today, WordPress is one of the world’s best solutions for blogging and website.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HOW TO recover from the most common WordPress website killers</title>
      <link>https://damien.co/blog/2011-07-10-how-to-recover-from-the-most-common-wordpress-website-killers/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2011 15:31:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien.co/blog/2011-07-10-how-to-recover-from-the-most-common-wordpress-website-killers/</guid>
      <description>It’s easy to recover from the 2 most common errors that kill your WordPress website. Fix the issue in 3 simple steps.
When something goes wrong WordPress the most common cause is a plugin conflict or a problem with your theme. There’s nothing worse then feeling you’ve been locked out from your own website and can’t get to the wp-admin section to login.
Today, WordPress is one of the world’s best solutions for blogging and website.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>