<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Statisitics on Damien Saunders</title>
    <link>http://damien.co/tags/statisitics/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Statisitics on Damien Saunders</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2013 20:39:24 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://damien.co/tags/statisitics/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>2012 Website Statistics &amp;#8211; Content Strategy is not buzz words like SEO</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/2012-website-statistics-awesome-8541/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2013 20:39:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/2012-website-statistics-awesome-8541/</guid>
      <description>2012 was the biggest year to date for web site visitors – and with good reason! So Thank You to everyone who came, read and left (and came back, again).
55,266 unique visitors clocked up 5.1 million seconds of visit duration but more importantly pages / visit and average visit duration also grew.
 So what happened in 2012? Search Engine Optimisation (SEO) didn’t work out … but having a content strategy did.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mobile Usage and Trends &amp;#8211; Updated with UK Statistics</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/mobile-marketing/mobile-usage-and-trends-updated-with-uk-statistics-5815/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2011 19:18:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/mobile-marketing/mobile-usage-and-trends-updated-with-uk-statistics-5815/</guid>
      <description>Good mobile insights and statistics are hard to find unless you pay for them … that’s why I’ve just updated my Key Trends and Usage Insights to include data for the UK.
UK Mobile Trends and Insights UK total mobile users 80m (penetration is over 100% of the population)
UK smartphone penetration 46%
UK smartphone app usage 50%
Need Help? Check out my other presentations or contact me for more information.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Android Apps &amp;#8211; 400% growth rate YOY</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/android/android-apps-400-growth-3051/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2011 11:57:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/android/android-apps-400-growth-3051/</guid>
      <description>Android in numbers – thankfully the Google I/O conference helped out by publishing statistics which give some insight to the growth in adoption of smartphones and also help to provide a hint of reality. But these are BIG BIG BIG numbers.
Android Smartphones, Tablets &amp;amp; Devices  Over 100M Android devices activated worldwide with 400K activations added every day More than 310 Android devices from 36 different manufactures Android cellphones are on more than 216 mobile carriers in 112 countries  Android Market  200,000 free and paid applications available in Android Market 4.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>