<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Social CRM on Damien Saunders</title>
    <link>http://damien.co/tags/social-crm/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Social CRM on Damien Saunders</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2011 17:50:46 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://damien.co/tags/social-crm/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Emailvision &amp;#8211; whose the Dummy? or didn&amp;#8217;t someone test your email campaign?</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/social-crm/emailvision-whose-the-dummy-or-didnt-someone-test-your-email-campaign-3907/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2011 17:50:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/social-crm/emailvision-whose-the-dummy-or-didnt-someone-test-your-email-campaign-3907/</guid>
      <description>Social CRM for dummies is something I’ve wanted to read for sometime … it could be a good e-book … if the email marketing campaign worked. This shows the number one problem with integrated social media marketing – broken links.
Emailvision are big news, they put the power into sites like http://alltop.com/ aka Guy Kawasaki … I’d like to learn more about them.
Check your campaign experience works end to end Facebook fails with broken links and images.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Social Media Sunday</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/social-media/social-media-sunday-2-2078/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Nov 2010 16:53:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/social-media/social-media-sunday-2-2078/</guid>
      <description>It’s here again – Social Media Sunday and this week I have chosen 3 of the best Google Apps for social networking and project management.

If you don’t use Google Apps with a custom domain … then you don’t know what you are missing.
Socialwok 
Socialwok creates a professional social network instantly for everyone on the same domain. You can also create projects or shared folders (called Feeds) and invite external people — clients?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ZOHO CRM just integrated with Google Sites</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/social-crm/zoho-crm-just-integrated-with-google-sites-1824/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Nov 2010 09:42:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/social-crm/zoho-crm-just-integrated-with-google-sites-1824/</guid>
      <description>ZOHO CRMis one of the best web based SaaS customer relationship managementweb apps around and now its gone and made it even easier to capture your leads or enquiries from your website – if you use Google Sites.Currently Social CRM is the new name for managing customers – CRM wasn’t good enough and wasn’t work for many. The new tag Social CRM refers to engaging customers online where ever they are and hopefully that’s on your website!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Social Tools for Customer Service – Get Satisfaction</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/social-media/social-tools-for-customer-service-get-satisfaction-1464/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Sep 2010 17:00:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/social-media/social-tools-for-customer-service-get-satisfaction-1464/</guid>
      <description>Get Satisfaction– its what you want when you ring a call centre – like your bank, your tax office or some other service provider. Get Satisfaction, if you don’t know it is the name of a powerful web based customer service tool which helps customers to connect and help themselves.
I’ve just launched a Get Satisfaction forum to demonstrate the features of their free service – and it works well.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>