<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>CoTweet on Damien Saunders</title>
    <link>https://damien.co/tags/cotweet/</link>
    <description>Recent content in CoTweet on Damien Saunders</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2011 14:00:39 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://damien.co/tags/cotweet/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Best Tools for Social Media Marketing if you&#39;re just getting started</title>
      <link>https://damien.co/blog/2011-07-26-best-tools-for-social-media-marketing-if-youre-just-getting-started/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2011 14:00:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien.co/blog/2011-07-26-best-tools-for-social-media-marketing-if-youre-just-getting-started/</guid>
      <description>If you&amp;rsquo;re getting started with Social Media marketing then you need at least 1 web based tool to help you.
For most businesses and individuals, social media marketing starts and ends with Tweetdeck. Which provides an all-in-one solution for pushing content direct from your machine. You need better tools for planning and managing your social media marketing.
However browser based tools for social media marketing are better suited for team or office environs – or if you&amp;rsquo;re like me, someone on the road in different offices who can&amp;rsquo;t have Tweetdeck open all the time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UPDATED: Twitter Tools &amp;#8211; CoTweet best for your business</title>
      <link>https://damien.co/social-media/twitter-tools-cotweet-best-for-your-business-1549/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Sep 2010 11:00:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien.co/social-media/twitter-tools-cotweet-best-for-your-business-1549/</guid>
      <description>CoTweet provides the easiest way for your business to start managing your company or brand on Twitter. If you already are using HootSuite or Tweetdeck you should stop for a minute and check you are doing the right thing for your business. CoTweetis designed for the multi-user / multi-site (!!) environment with assignment, archiving and other management tools – this means you’ll never lose a tweet again (or have to share the computer with your boss).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>