<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Cyanogen on Damien Saunders</title>
    <link>http://damien.co/tags/cyanogen/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Cyanogen on Damien Saunders</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 27 Jun 2011 19:08:44 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://damien.co/tags/cyanogen/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Cyanogenmod 7.1 RC1</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/android/cyanogenmod-7-1-rc1-4070/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jun 2011 19:08:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/android/cyanogenmod-7-1-rc1-4070/</guid>
      <description>Have you updated? - the first release candidate for Cyanogenmod v7.1 has been pushed out today. This update adds (more) support for Android 2.3.4 a number of Android devices from Samsung, LG, Motorola and the HTC Incredible.
Here&amp;rsquo;s a summary of nice features from the changelog:
Common: Support for revoking application permissions
Common: Latest Superuser app
Common: Control brightness by sliding on statusbar
Common: ADWLauncher- Transitions, catalog improvements, bugfixes
Common: Optional GMT correction for SMS/MMS timestamps</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cyanogenmod - How to download big apps on your SD Card</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/2011-05-08-cyanogenmod-how-to-download-big-apps-on-your-sd-card/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 May 2011 12:31:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/2011-05-08-cyanogenmod-how-to-download-big-apps-on-your-sd-card/</guid>
      <description>Are you suffering from Android Market download issues? Have you just rooted your Android with Cyanogenmod and found you can&amp;rsquo;t download Google Maps?
If you can&amp;rsquo;t download Google Maps it&amp;rsquo;s because most Android phones have a download cache limited to 3MB and Google Maps is a whooping 5.4MB.
How to Download large files after rooting your Android The answer to your problems is S2E simple2ext - which moves your download cache off the phone to your SD Card.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cyanogenmod 7.0.3 - have you updated?</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/2011-05-07-cyanogenmod-7-0-3-have-you-updated/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2011 16:38:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/2011-05-07-cyanogenmod-7-0-3-have-you-updated/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cyanogenmod 7.02 have you updated</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/2011-04-28-cyanogenmod-7-02-have-you-updated/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Apr 2011 21:11:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/2011-04-28-cyanogenmod-7-02-have-you-updated/</guid>
      <description>Have you updated? - the latest Cyanogenmod v7.02 has been released. Mostly it fixes bugs and &amp;lsquo;actually&amp;rsquo; fixes GPS.
Being a point release its not focused on new features - but if you haven&amp;rsquo;t updated then you should. As always backup your current Rom before installing this update.
Summary from the changelog:
 Common: Fix issue with missing built-in themes Common: Update bundled ROM Manager to latest version Supersonic: Actually fix GPS Supersonic: Fix proximity and light sensor  You can download it via the Clockwork Rom Manager or manually.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HOWTO: Fix no mobile internet after Cyanogenmod install</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/android/howto-fix-no-mobile-internet-after-cyanogenmod-install-2822/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Apr 2011 21:04:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/android/howto-fix-no-mobile-internet-after-cyanogenmod-install-2822/</guid>
      <description>Here&amp;rsquo;s a simple fix to problems of no Mobile Internet after installing Cyanogenmod rom on your Android. If you&amp;rsquo;re new to rooting your Android or just forgotten how complicated it can be to get online with your mobile phone - you might think this is a really useful tip.
 Check your APN Settings After you root your phone and install CyanogenMod you can find your have no wifi and no wireless internet connection.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cyanogenmod 7RC3</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/android/cyanogenmod-7rc3-2808/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Mar 2011 09:20:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/android/cyanogenmod-7rc3-2808/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve just updated to the latest Cyanogenmod 7 release candidate 3 … it&amp;rsquo;s now looking very polished.
Noticeable extras - application shortcut menus have a link to the Android Market.
 What have you noticed?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I upgraded to Cyanogenmod 7 on HTC Desire</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/2011-02-22-i-upgraded-to-cyanogenmod-7-on-htc-desire/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2011 09:16:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/2011-02-22-i-upgraded-to-cyanogenmod-7-on-htc-desire/</guid>
      <description>I just updated my HTC Desire to the new Cyanogenmod 7 rom and it&amp;rsquo;s been running fine. A part of me does miss the HTC Sense UE overlay .. but … meh. If you have already rooted your phone and been using Clockwork ROM Manager, you just need to go looking for the new Cyanogenmod 7 RC1.
The upgrade process is very simple - but here are a couple of pointers -</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>