<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Startup on Damien Saunders</title>
    <link>https://damien.co/categories/startup/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Startup on Damien Saunders</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 10 Sep 2012 14:06:15 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://damien.co/categories/startup/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Startup Metrics for Pirates (SeedCamp 2008)</title>
      <link>https://damien.co/startup/startup-metrics-for-pirates-seedcamp-2008-7781/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Sep 2012 14:06:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien.co/startup/startup-metrics-for-pirates-seedcamp-2008-7781/</guid>
      <description>If you’re in a Startup you need to agree quite quickly on some of those performance metrics and here, Dave McClure shares his view.
Sure you can go for the glamour figures — like millions of page views, likes or tweets. But wouldn’t you just prefer some hard cash? or qualified leads?
At the end of the day, the stats you pick, you have to stick with and track over time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HOW TO use Twitter for your startup</title>
      <link>https://damien.co/startup/how-to-use-twitter-for-your-startup-2-1069/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2011 09:40:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien.co/startup/how-to-use-twitter-for-your-startup-2-1069/</guid>
      <description>Twitter is a very powerful tool for any startup and I believe it is the first social network any would be entrepreneur needs to setup when launching their new business. The worst mistake any startup marketer will make is just tweeting “Hello World” without a plan.
Make your Twitter Marketing Plan Any startup sales &amp;amp; marketing plan or marcomms plan needs to make the most of the 4 P’s – product place price promotion.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Management lessons we can learn from films &amp;#8211; TRON</title>
      <link>https://damien.co/startup/management-lessons-we-can-learn-from-films-tron-3123/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 May 2011 11:08:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien.co/startup/management-lessons-we-can-learn-from-films-tron-3123/</guid>
      <description>TRONis still a superb film, I was too young when it was first issued, but watching it recently started me thinking about business strategy and business models for startups.
In basic sociology, we learn that society is reflected in films and films are (then) reflected back in society. What this means is that you can analyse a film to learn about (business) culture from that time and look to see if any stereotypes are carried forward into reality.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apple Mac App Store an imperfect tool for small apps developers?</title>
      <link>https://damien.co/startup/apple-mac-app-store-an-imperfect-tool-for-small-apps-developers-2481/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2011 10:26:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien.co/startup/apple-mac-app-store-an-imperfect-tool-for-small-apps-developers-2481/</guid>
      <description>Apple’s new Mac App Store arrives on January 6 and it could be the perfect tool for small app developers and a welcome boost in hybrid web-app startups. That said — Does your business or client want their marketing and product development strategy to be led by Apple’s App Store?
Mac App Store key features for Users Customers of the Mac App Store (eg anyone owning a Mac) will think this is a really useful new system tool.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What&amp;#039;s your business model?</title>
      <link>https://damien.co/startup/whats-your-business-model-1962/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Nov 2010 09:45:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien.co/startup/whats-your-business-model-1962/</guid>
      <description>I was having a catchup with a go0d friend this evening and he reminded me that every startup or or new venture needs to solve a problem.Mobile Communications is a major innovator Of course the mobile phone is a big problem solver and I think its referred to as a game changing innovation – but the game change didn’t happen until mass market usage started to drive demand … and it’s only now, as the price the customer pays for some mobile calls is near to zero (not free, you’re using bundles of minutes now) that you can say ‘talk is cheap’.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Happy Saturday Humour &amp;#8211; What are you like when you pitch?</title>
      <link>https://damien.co/startup/happy-saturday-humour-what-are-you-like-when-you-pitch-1867/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Nov 2010 10:56:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien.co/startup/happy-saturday-humour-what-are-you-like-when-you-pitch-1867/</guid>
      <description>Hope you’re having a good weekend so far! How do you think people perceive your communication skills? and if you’re an entrepreneur — how good are you at pitching? 
source: www.gapingvoid.com</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Task Management with Post-It Notes</title>
      <link>https://damien.co/startup/task-management-with-post-it-notes-1832/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Nov 2010 09:56:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien.co/startup/task-management-with-post-it-notes-1832/</guid>
      <description>As I’m a certified Scrum Master and very good at project and task management I can say I enjoy running planning sessions with teams I do work with. Now I’ve started to discover the freedom of the Post-It Note for planning and brainstorming.

Even better, its essential for any startup to be able to focus on what has to be done and avoid distractions like outsiders wanting extra work or changes to scope.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Announcing Cambridge Startup Weekend December 10 &amp;#8211; 12</title>
      <link>https://damien.co/startup/announcing-cambridge-startup-weekend-december-10-12-1798/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Oct 2010 19:22:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien.co/startup/announcing-cambridge-startup-weekend-december-10-12-1798/</guid>
      <description>Cambridge Startup Weekend (http://cambridge.startupweekend.org) will take place December 10 – 11 – 12 2010 in just over 6 weeks at the Hauser Forum in Cambridge.Startup Weekend is the place to come for anyone with a new idea that they want to see brought to life. Over the weekend teams work together to take the ideas and create real new ventures. Anyone with an idea or interest in being an entrepreneur is welcome.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cambridge Startup Weekend Dec 10 &amp;#8211; 12</title>
      <link>https://damien.co/startup/cambridge-startup-weekend-dec-10-12-1748/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Oct 2010 10:13:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien.co/startup/cambridge-startup-weekend-dec-10-12-1748/</guid>
      <description>Cambridge Startup Weekend is coming … and I mean Cambridge, UK. This will be the first Startup Weekend I’ve worked on outside of London and I’m sure it will be a great success (thanks James).
Cambridge Startup Weekend will take place December 10 – 12 and tickets are on sale now.
see http://cambridge.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Startup Guide to building a website with WordPress</title>
      <link>https://damien.co/startup/startup-guide-to-building-a-website-with-wordpress-1059/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jun 2010 09:00:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien.co/startup/startup-guide-to-building-a-website-with-wordpress-1059/</guid>
      <description>So your new business needs a website – and someone told you to build it using WordPress. Cool .. this collection of resources on WordPress for your new venture will help you:
How to migrate your website to WordPress– from experience and using a real life case study
9 essential plugins for WordPress– here’s my recommendations on WordPress plugins to get you started.
How to make a landing page template in WordPress– landing pages or static pages are great to promote a new product or service and its easy to add a landing page to WordPress</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Essential Startup Resources for Customer Relationship Management</title>
      <link>https://damien.co/startup/essential-startup-resources-for-customer-relationship-management-1053/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jun 2010 13:22:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien.co/startup/essential-startup-resources-for-customer-relationship-management-1053/</guid>
      <description>So here is an essential collection of startup resources to customer relationship management or CRM. When you go into business as a startup or entrepreneur your sales and marketing activities will need to be split 3 ways –
 Customers who are buying from you Nurturing Customers who will buy from you Generating new leads or potential customers  This may seem daunting – so from the day you open your doors or your new web business you’ll want a tool to track all your customers and maybe your suppliers too.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>London Startup Weekend June 2010 Teams</title>
      <link>https://damien.co/blog/2010-06-13-london-startup-weekend-june-2010-teams/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jun 2010 18:18:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien.co/blog/2010-06-13-london-startup-weekend-june-2010-teams/</guid>
      <description>Here is the full list of the teams from London Startup Weekend June 2010. I’ve now added this as a page on the London site. The next weekend for London will be announced soon..
Rags2Riches This is the mobile game to play where every check-in makes you money
http://rags2riches.mobi##BuddyBounce Allows people around the world to meet online through a video speed networking service
http://www.buddybounce.com/
Zolidays Creates your personalised holiday planner based on budget and your interests</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>