<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>research on Damien Saunders</title>
    <link>http://damien.co/tags/research/</link>
    <description>Recent content in research on Damien Saunders</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 May 2011 11:57:15 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://damien.co/tags/research/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Android Apps &amp;#8211; 400% growth rate YOY</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/2011-05-17-android-apps-400-growth/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2011 11:57:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/2011-05-17-android-apps-400-growth/</guid>
      <description>Android in numbers – thankfully the Google I/O conference helped out by publishing statistics which give some insight to the growth in adoption of smartphones and also help to provide a hint of reality. But these are BIG BIG BIG numbers.
Android Smartphones, Tablets &amp;amp; Devices  Over 100M Android devices activated worldwide with 400K activations added every day More than 310 Android devices from 36 different manufactures Android cellphones are on more than 216 mobile carriers in 112 countries  Android Market  200,000 free and paid applications available in Android Market 4.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NEWS: Price Grabber research says we spend more on the mobile</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/news-releases/news-price-grabber-research-says-we-spend-more-on-the-mobile-1347/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jul 2010 09:00:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/news-releases/news-price-grabber-research-says-we-spend-more-on-the-mobile-1347/</guid>
      <description>Finally some proof that Mobile Internet usage is profoundlyshaking up the way consumers shop, according to new research from PriceGrabber.co.uk. Of the 908 online shoppers that were asked about their mobile shopping habits, 66 percent owned a Smartphone or another Web-enabled phone. Of the consumers who shop from their mobile, nearly half (48 percent) claim that the convenience of having the Internet with them wherever they go is their number one reason for smart shopping.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What kids do online: UK Internet Usage</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/2010-02-07-what-kids-do-online-uk-internet-usage/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Feb 2010 12:56:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/2010-02-07-what-kids-do-online-uk-internet-usage/</guid>
      <description>Recent indepth report from New Media Age in the UK focused on the internet usage habits of kids.
Kids research is hard – the age group is from 7 – 13. They are already exposed to a lot of marketing, aware of trends and ‘peer pressure’, but still very much aware of having to please their parents all of the time. It’s also very difficult to ask questions about anything anti-social, illegal due to the young age and formative, questioning minds.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Looking for insights on Mobile and Retail Sector?</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/2010-02-06-looking-for-insights-on-mobile-and-retail-sector/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Feb 2010 17:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/2010-02-06-looking-for-insights-on-mobile-and-retail-sector/</guid>
      <description>&amp;lt;div&amp;gt; The Whitepaper, ‘Mobile in Retail’, seeks to identify the potential for mobile to brands and retailers. It highlights 10 areas, including coupons and loyalty, where mobile is deemed to have a particular impact. The executive summary points to a number of areas of potential gain for businesses adopting mobile as a consumer engagement channel. These are increased sales; increased customer satisfaction and loyalty; and additional value to physical products and experiences through digital services.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gartner Says Consumers Will Download 4,500,000,000 Mobile Apps in 2010</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/gartner-says-consumers-will-download-over-4-billion-mobile-apps-in-2010-420/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Jan 2010 14:33:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/gartner-says-consumers-will-download-over-4-billion-mobile-apps-in-2010-420/</guid>
      <description>This week Gartner reported that consumers will spend a headline figure of £3.8 billion pounds ($6.2 billion USD) in mobile apps during this year. The forecast estimates total downloads to be 4,500,000,000. The numbers are eye wateringly large.
Gartners forecast goes on to mention that 82 per cent of downloads would be free apps … leaving 18 per cent of downloads to come up with cash.
4.5 billion downloads is quite staggering – even if Apple is set to announce its about to hit its 3 billionth download.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Social Media &amp;amp; Marketing Round-up of some good reading</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/mobile-marketing/social-media-marketing-round-up-of-some-good-reading-375/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Dec 2009 16:36:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/mobile-marketing/social-media-marketing-round-up-of-some-good-reading-375/</guid>
      <description>**The problem with doing research on social media and mobile marketing is the overwhelming amount of noise you get from doing searches on Google, Delicious and Twitter.
**
Here are a few links of really useful and easy to consume ‘research’
best ‘inspirational’ video on social media
http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=sIFYPQjYhv8map of social media world
http://www.flickr.com/photos/wasabibratwurst/3128711125/sizes/l/top 100 companies by media spend</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Comparison of Digital Music Retailers in Europe</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/comparison-of-digital-music-retailers-in-europe-246/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Aug 2009 17:28:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/comparison-of-digital-music-retailers-in-europe-246/</guid>
      <description>Comment: There are a number of digital music retailers working around Europe, here is Damien Saunders’ summary of a few of the bigger services (catalogue greater than 1 million tracks).
&amp;lt;td width=&amp;quot;75&amp;quot;&amp;gt; Countries &amp;lt;/td&amp;gt; &amp;lt;td width=&amp;quot;75&amp;quot;&amp;gt; MP3 to buy &amp;lt;/td&amp;gt; &amp;lt;td width=&amp;quot;79&amp;quot;&amp;gt; Subscription &amp;lt;/td&amp;gt; &amp;lt;td width=&amp;quot;75&amp;quot;&amp;gt; Catalogue Size &amp;lt;/td&amp;gt; &amp;lt;td width=&amp;quot;75&amp;quot;&amp;gt; 3rd Party API &amp;lt;/td&amp;gt; &amp;lt;td width=&amp;quot;75&amp;quot;&amp;gt; PC Software &amp;lt;/td&amp;gt;  &amp;lt;td width=&amp;quot;75&amp;quot;&amp;gt; UK &amp;lt;/td&amp;gt; &amp;lt;td width=&amp;quot;75&amp;quot;&amp;gt; Yes &amp;lt;/td&amp;gt; &amp;lt;td width=&amp;quot;79&amp;quot;&amp;gt; No &amp;lt;/td&amp;gt; &amp;lt;td width=&amp;quot;75&amp;quot;&amp;gt; 3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Music file sharing on the up and up</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/music-file-sharing-on-the-up-and-up-81/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2008 15:28:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/music-file-sharing-on-the-up-and-up-81/</guid>
      <description>Damien Saunders says -research shows continued growth in file-sharing and downloading of mp3s is now common place. This survey supports the view that prosecuting the mass population is not the right approach by the labels and rights associations.
British Music Rights research shows that file-sharing is done by a large number of people and even more are downloading music.
Music week reports these findings:
42% of those surveyed say they have uploaded files.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>