<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>marketing mix on Damien Saunders</title>
    <link>https://damien.co/tags/marketing-mix/</link>
    <description>Recent content in marketing mix on Damien Saunders</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 17 Jun 2012 18:47:42 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://damien.co/tags/marketing-mix/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>41 things to do in 41 days to boost your digital marketing</title>
      <link>https://damien.co/marketing-consultant-2/41-things-to-do-in-41-days-to-boost-your-digital-marketing-7161/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Jun 2012 18:47:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien.co/marketing-consultant-2/41-things-to-do-in-41-days-to-boost-your-digital-marketing-7161/</guid>
      <description>[typography font=”Special Elite” size=”25″ size_format=”px”]Want a quick head start to a digital marketing plan for your brand or business? Here are 41 things you can do … over 41 days.[/typography]
Allow an hour a day (and a bit extra at the end of the week to see how you’re progressing).
 Create an account on Twitter for you and your brand – find some friends to follow Create an account on Facebook Create a social media analytics account on MarketMeSuite to monitor your fans and followers Create a Google Alert to track online mentions of your brand Create a Google Alert for mentions of your product Create a Google Alert for mentions of your competitors Create a Google Alert for mentions of you Find out what Web Analytics Tools you use like Google Analytics &amp;amp; Bit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Start a Social Media Marketing Plan – why you need to use social media?</title>
      <link>https://damien.co/social-media/start-a-social-media-marketing-plan-why-you-need-to-use-social-media-1119/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jul 2010 09:00:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien.co/social-media/start-a-social-media-marketing-plan-why-you-need-to-use-social-media-1119/</guid>
      <description>Starting your plan for social media marketing in a small or big business should be driven by a need or a reason.
Why use Social Media – because your customers are using it! First step in your social media marketing plan is to open powerpoint or write on a flipchart the reason why you need to use social media, some good reasons include:
 most of our target audience use social media (no brainer), or because visits to your brand or company website are down as our customers spend more time on social media sites (better) to deliver a sales &amp;amp; marketing programme using online &amp;amp; social media  There are probably plenty of other good reasons you can think of.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to make mobile part of your marketing strategy</title>
      <link>https://damien.co/general/how-to-make-mobile-part-of-your-marketing-strategy-357/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Nov 2009 09:01:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien.co/general/how-to-make-mobile-part-of-your-marketing-strategy-357/</guid>
      <description>Should you be worried that you don’t have an iPhone app? Do you know if you’re website works on a mobile? what about mobile SEO? It is very important for CEO’s and CMO’s to add mobile to their communications and marketing strategy.
The fact that most companies have yet to build a mobile website shows you are not alone and many companies want to know what they should do first.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>