<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Mobile on Damien Saunders</title>
    <link>http://damien.co/tags/mobile/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Mobile on Damien Saunders</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Oct 2012 13:20:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://damien.co/tags/mobile/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>HOW TO: View your WordPress Website on iPhone or Android Mobiles</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/2012-06-17-how-to-view-your-wordpress-website-on-iphone-or-android-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Jun 2012 16:00:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/2012-06-17-how-to-view-your-wordpress-website-on-iphone-or-android-2/</guid>
      <description>WordPress is a very comprehensive all-round tool for websites – and its not just for blogs. If you’re starting out with WordPress and need your site to look smooth on a mobile phone like the iPhone or iPad or any Android mobile then you’ll need a plugin for this.
The best plugin for WordPress that handles any mobile device is easily WPtouch iPhone Theme. Once the plugin is installed and activated its working for you straight away.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>App Design: Google&#43; updates app for iOS  &amp;#8211; result is impressive</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/2012-05-17-app-design-google-updates-app-for-ios-result-is-impressive/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 May 2012 17:30:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/2012-05-17-app-design-google-updates-app-for-ios-result-is-impressive/</guid>
      <description>Google+ has updated it’s app for iPhones –
Even though the app is not universal – you can see Google+ has high-res / retina display assets and so it renders quite ‘crisp’ even at 2x zoom on the iPad.
This is great job using fonts and HTML elements so the overall effect is impressive.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Get Results from an Android Mobile Marketing Strategy</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/mobile-marketing/get-results-from-an-android-mobile-marketing-strategy-5885/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2012 13:12:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/mobile-marketing/get-results-from-an-android-mobile-marketing-strategy-5885/</guid>
      <description>Android Mobiles are taking over the world … and that seems to be supported by the latest statistics or _trends. _If you’re thinking about mobile marketing .. and wondering ‘what is all the fuss about Android’, then this presentation is for you.
Only the latest Android Insights and Statistics  10 billion app downloads (December 2011) 200 million activated devices (November 2011) 400,000 Android Apps (December 2011)  We can only wait for the next Google I/O conference to confirm how these numbers are growing!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mobile Usage and Trends &amp;#8211; Updated with UK Statistics</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/mobile-marketing/mobile-usage-and-trends-updated-with-uk-statistics-5815/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2011 19:18:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/mobile-marketing/mobile-usage-and-trends-updated-with-uk-statistics-5815/</guid>
      <description>Good mobile insights and statistics are hard to find unless you pay for them … that’s why I’ve just updated my Key Trends and Usage Insights to include data for the UK.
UK Mobile Trends and Insights UK total mobile users 80m (penetration is over 100% of the population)
UK smartphone penetration 46%
UK smartphone app usage 50%</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mobile Internet testing tools to check your WP TouchPro changes</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/2011-12-29-mobile-internet-testing-tools-to-check-your-wp-touchpro-changes/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2011 10:44:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/2011-12-29-mobile-internet-testing-tools-to-check-your-wp-touchpro-changes/</guid>
      <description>WordPress makes it easy to publish your site for mobile users. It’s best that you always test your changes on smart phones but did you know that you can check most changes on using your Apple Mac?
 Mobile Internet Solutions WP TouchPro is one of the best solutions to make your site ready for the mobile internet and smart-phone users. The key reason it is so good lies in the fact that it combines both a plugin and has it’s own mobile specific theme.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Remember your Mobile Browser detection for iPad &amp;#038; Smartphones</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/mobile-marketing/remember-your-mobile-browser-detection-for-ipad-smartphones-2589/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2011 09:21:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/mobile-marketing/remember-your-mobile-browser-detection-for-ipad-smartphones-2589/</guid>
      <description>So you’ve built a great website for your clients and they’re happy to see its getting lots of good traffic. Now your client wants to know how to make their website mobile.
Depending on the CMS you used to build the website – WordPressor Drupal for example, be sure to setup a mobile browser plugin that renders your website smartphone and mobile friendly.
For anyone building a website from scratch – mobile browser detection is done in the same was as detecting say IE6.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Members Get it Free &amp;#8211; Definitive Guide to Foursquare for 2011</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/2011-07-25-members-get-it-free-definitive-guide-to-foursquare-for-2011/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jul 2011 22:18:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/2011-07-25-members-get-it-free-definitive-guide-to-foursquare-for-2011/</guid>
      <description>The Definitive Guide to Foursquare has been updated for 2011 … and will be sent out this week. This guide contains all you need to know to get started with marketing using Foursquare. It covers:
 Statistics you need to know Ideas for making your business marketing with Foursquare better What key incentives you should have to reward Mayors Tips for tracking and monitoring much much more …  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Redmine for Issues &amp;#038; Bug track &amp;#8211; things I learned</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/marketing-consultant-2/redmine-for-issues-bug-track-things-i-learned-3058/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 May 2011 17:45:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/marketing-consultant-2/redmine-for-issues-bug-track-things-i-learned-3058/</guid>
      <description>Redmine is described as a flexible project management web application SaaS. I’ve been using it for the past 5 months within a mobile marketing agency – where its used for testing, operations, work orders, issue management and its wiki is used for documentation.
Redmine can not be compared to other bug track, issues or fault management systems like JIRA or CRM platforms with helpdesk tools. It’s flexible, but that comes with a price.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HOW-TO Get started with mobile app testing &amp;#8211; device checklist</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/mobile-marketing/how-to-get-started-with-mobile-app-testing-device-checklist-2829/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Apr 2011 08:37:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/mobile-marketing/how-to-get-started-with-mobile-app-testing-device-checklist-2829/</guid>
      <description>Do you do mobile app testing? Then maybe you need a getting started checklist to help you with your device settings. One thing has not changed in the (nearly) 10 years since mobile internet got started – we still have to check and change device settings.
 Check .. Does the mobile operator name show in the status bar?
 if it says No Carrier it wont work  Check … you have a data connection â can you open any app or browse to a web page.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gartner predicts App Store Revenue Forecast to Surpass $15 Billion in 2011</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/insights-blog/gartner-predicts-app-store-revenue-forecast-to-surpass-15-billion-in-2011-2656/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2011 07:53:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/insights-blog/gartner-predicts-app-store-revenue-forecast-to-surpass-15-billion-in-2011-2656/</guid>
      <description>I’ve been on the lookout for this prediction … in 2010 Gartner predicted Worldwide Mobile App Revenues of xx Billion … for 2011 the prediction is for this to exceed $15 billion
2010 Where are the results! Given that Apple, Android, RIM, Nokia and a whole stack of operators and 3rd parties run mobile app stores – it’s extremely difficult to find out how good Gartner is at forecasts. Or is this just a large number guestimate?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Foursquare most popular location checkin game in London</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/social-media/foursquare-most-popular-location-checkin-tool-in-london-1173/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jul 2010 09:00:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/social-media/foursquare-most-popular-location-checkin-tool-in-london-1173/</guid>
      <description>Foursquare is still the UK’s most popular location based check-in game to play on your mobile. I’ve said it before that Foursquare would come out on tops over Gowalla and Brightkite.
These maps (thanks to Checkin Mania) indicate the difference in the number of locations that users have submitted to each service. The growth from crowd sourced locations and points of interest reflects in the growth of that services usage (ie the most popular service gets the most contributions from users) The point of reference is London Borough Market – one of the more famous places in London to visit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Mobile? Why Now? – short guide to mobile marketing</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/2010-04-18-why-mobile-why-now-short-guide-to-mobile-marketing/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Apr 2010 16:16:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/2010-04-18-why-mobile-why-now-short-guide-to-mobile-marketing/</guid>
      <description>A short guide to mobile marketing is as short as it can get – and provides just enough insights, trends and key facts to help make the most of mobile marketing. What’s included in this is 8 quick suggestions how to include mobile marketing in your marketing strategy.
Why mobile why now</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>b2b Marketing &amp;#8211; how to increase your content sales and improve your content</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/mobile-marketing/b2b-marketing-how-to-increase-your-content-sales-and-improve-your-content-812/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Mar 2010 23:29:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/mobile-marketing/b2b-marketing-how-to-increase-your-content-sales-and-improve-your-content-812/</guid>
      <description>A short guide with b2b marketing tips for improving your content sales and improve your content using mmCHANNEL’s new API.1. Got an upcoming marketing campaign? Need Content? Now any marketing campaign can include digital content like tones, songs, games from a selection of mmCHANNEL manages.
2. Drive traffic to your website or fanpage You can setup a content shop in your existing website using the mmCHANNEL b2bAPI with no need to build any other platforms</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NewsRob best Android application for Google Reader</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/2010-02-28-newsrob-best-android-application-for-google-reader/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Feb 2010 15:11:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/2010-02-28-newsrob-best-android-application-for-google-reader/</guid>
      <description>Newsrob is my favourite application for Android mobiles, it’s been covered in my 10Best Android Apps** list a few times. **Newsrob** integratess with your account for Google Reader (which allows you to manage and read all your RSS feeds). Newsrob recently turned 1 and celebrated by introducing a Pro version and an Adfunded Free Version.**
What’s fantastic about Newsrob Pro Newsrob Prohas a new feature that is great for any social media or mobile specialist.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to make mobile part of your marketing strategy</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/2009-11-09-how-to-make-mobile-part-of-your-marketing-strategy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Nov 2009 09:01:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/2009-11-09-how-to-make-mobile-part-of-your-marketing-strategy/</guid>
      <description>Should you be worried that you don’t have an iPhone app? Do you know if you’re website works on a mobile? what about mobile SEO? It is very important for CEO’s and CMO’s to add mobile to their communications and marketing strategy.
The fact that most companies have yet to build a mobile website shows you are not alone and many companies want to know what they should do first.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sony Ericsson&amp;#039;s first Android phone</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/sony-ericssons-first-android-phone-352/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Nov 2009 10:46:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/sony-ericssons-first-android-phone-352/</guid>
      <description>Sony Ericsson delivered a blow to Microsoft on Tuesday when it unveiled its latest Xperia handset, which unlike its Windows-powered predecessors is based on Google’s Android operating system.
Called X10, the flagship smartphone comes with a new Sony Ericsson-designed user interface that aggregates the user’s contacts and communications from the likes of Facebook and Twitter into a single address book.
The system is akin to HTC’s Sense interface, and Motorola’s Motoblur interface, both of which feature on the respective companies’ new Android phones.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Does building an iPhone App make cents? sense?</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/does-building-an-iphone-make-cents-sense-348/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Nov 2009 19:36:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/does-building-an-iphone-make-cents-sense-348/</guid>
      <description>With the boom in the number of apps in the App Store (over 100,000) and total downloads in excess of 2bn … someone has got to be making money … right?In part, the iPhone does offer a better platform for apps – it’s about to overtake RIM as the leading consumer smartphone, sold more than 34 million units and got some of the highest mobile internet usage rates we’ve seen so far.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>App of the day: Balsamiq &amp;#8211; wireframing and user experience design</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/app-of-the-day-balsamiq-wireframing-and-user-experience-design-328/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Sep 2009 13:48:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/app-of-the-day-balsamiq-wireframing-and-user-experience-design-328/</guid>
      <description>Balsamiq – I love it – the fonts and stuff can seem a bit cheesy … but I’ve take to this like a duck to water. Its much more useful than powerpoint, visio or other tools as its designed for wireframing.
Being built on Adobe Air means anyone can use it.
It’s very quick to create a UE design and while I couldn’t find a template or mockup for cell phone / mobile phone.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3 rewards customers who get customers</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/3-rewards-customers-who-get-customers-312/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2009 13:29:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/3-rewards-customers-who-get-customers-312/</guid>
      <description>From today 3 UK will reward customers with cashback for referrals.
Join 3’s Free Agent team and get paid for promoting our free SIMs online. You get £5 cash when each friend first tops up their SIM by a minimum of £10, and they get an extra £2 credit. There’s no limit to the amount of money you can make.
see also: http://freeagent.three.co.uk/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New UK MVNO before Christmas &amp;#8211; Giffgaff to offer free calls</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/new-uk-mvno-before-christmas-giffgaff-to-offer-free-calls-310/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2009 09:57:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/new-uk-mvno-before-christmas-giffgaff-to-offer-free-calls-310/</guid>
      <description>Giffgaff will reward subscribers with cash rebates when they distribute its SIMs, help other members via its forums and suggest ideas which are then implemented by the company.
source: http://www.nma.co.uk/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Content Providers &amp;amp; Digital New Media Players</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/content-providers-digital-new-media-players-242/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Aug 2009 10:27:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/content-providers-digital-new-media-players-242/</guid>
      <description>Content Providers, Content Partners, Service Providers or Content Delivery – there is a long list of terms that you can be searching for on the internet to get you a list … but is there a consolidated list of whos who in the industry? Here’s just a few:
Arvato– (Europe)
Buongiorno– (Europe)
Fonestarz– (Head office is based in the UK)
Fox Mobile– (Germany) aka Jamba&amp;amp; Jamster
mmCHANNEL (Spain)
Musiwave– (France)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blow out the candles &amp;#8211; Happy 1st Birthday Apple Apps Store</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/blow-out-the-candles-happy-1st-birthday-apple-apps-store-213/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jul 2009 20:55:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/blow-out-the-candles-happy-1st-birthday-apple-apps-store-213/</guid>
      <description>So its Happy Birthday to Apple and its App Store – 1 year old. Its created a new industry and probably will change the way everyone digests content – now that everything has an app or a widget you dont need to browse for it.
Except for Search – Apple and the Apps store has changed how mobile phone manufacturers think about content like Nokia, RIM and Sony Ericsson all launched (or launching) app stores in the past 3 months.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sony Ericsson does chunky retro Walkman W902</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/sony-ericsson-does-chunky-retro-walkman-w902-99/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2008 13:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/sony-ericsson-does-chunky-retro-walkman-w902-99/</guid>
      <description>Ive had a look at the Sony Ericsson new Walkman W902 with retro chunky buttons much like a those on a casette walkman.
The phone’s not retro though – Clear Crystal Audio for your listening pleasure and a 5.0 mega pixel camera is a great feature. I think its also got a really good speaker to annoy Grannies on the bus with.
I hope it comes out with more than a 1Gb of memory!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>