<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>sony ericsson on Damien Saunders</title>
    <link>http://damien.co/tags/sony-ericsson/</link>
    <description>Recent content in sony ericsson on Damien Saunders</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 04 Nov 2009 10:46:19 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://damien.co/tags/sony-ericsson/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Sony Ericsson&amp;#039;s first Android phone</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/sony-ericssons-first-android-phone-352/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Nov 2009 10:46:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/sony-ericssons-first-android-phone-352/</guid>
      <description>Sony Ericsson delivered a blow to Microsoft on Tuesday when it unveiled its latest Xperia handset, which unlike its Windows-powered predecessors is based on Google’s Android operating system.
Called X10, the flagship smartphone comes with a new Sony Ericsson-designed user interface that aggregates the user’s contacts and communications from the likes of Facebook and Twitter into a single address book.
The system is akin to HTC’s Sense interface, and Motorola’s Motoblur interface, both of which feature on the respective companies’ new Android phones.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sony Ericsson does chunky retro Walkman W902</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/sony-ericsson-does-chunky-retro-walkman-w902-99/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2008 13:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/sony-ericsson-does-chunky-retro-walkman-w902-99/</guid>
      <description>Ive had a look at the Sony Ericsson new Walkman W902 with retro chunky buttons much like a those on a casette walkman.
The phone’s not retro though – Clear Crystal Audio for your listening pleasure and a 5.0 mega pixel camera is a great feature. I think its also got a really good speaker to annoy Grannies on the bus with.
I hope it comes out with more than a 1Gb of memory!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>