<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Google on Damien Saunders</title>
    <link>https://damien1.github.io/tags/google/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Google on Damien Saunders</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2013 16:44:08 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://damien1.github.io/tags/google/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Death of Google Reader &amp;#8211; It&amp;#8217;s offline caching that makes RSS so good for me</title>
      <link>https://damien1.github.io/general/death-of-google-reader-its-offline-caching-that-makes-rss-so-good-for-me-8448/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2013 16:44:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien1.github.io/general/death-of-google-reader-its-offline-caching-that-makes-rss-so-good-for-me-8448/</guid>
      <description>It’s what’s on the inside that counts! For me, what makes RSS a success has been mobile apps with offline caching. I don’t sit at home with my browser pointed to reader.google.com … I use mobile apps. Specifically, as I spend a lot of time on London Tube and trains where there is no wifi or mobile coverage, I need an RSS Feed Reader with a Cache!
It’s been great over the years to have Google Reader there for me as a bit of a research index, record keeper and generally more reliable than Delicious or pretty much any social bookmarking service.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google&#43;: still not as interesting as Pinterest   &lt;&lt;- why does everyone want it fail?</title>
      <link>https://damien1.github.io/social-media/google-still-not-as-interesting-as-pinterest-7073/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 May 2012 22:35:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien1.github.io/social-media/google-still-not-as-interesting-as-pinterest-7073/</guid>
      <description>Comment – Seems to me that ‘everyone’ wants to find a fault with Google+ and many maybe ‘wishing’ it to fail. It’s hard to get traction with social networks as we are likely to be regular users of a few social networks. It’s harder still to get people to change their primary social network of choice when your online social network all still use The Facebook.
Source: Google+: still not as interesting as Pinterest, new study finds: ”</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>App Design: Google&#43; updates app for iOS  &amp;#8211; result is impressive</title>
      <link>https://damien1.github.io/apps-2/app-design-google-updates-app-for-ios-result-is-impressive-7044/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 May 2012 17:30:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien1.github.io/apps-2/app-design-google-updates-app-for-ios-result-is-impressive-7044/</guid>
      <description>Google+ has updated it’s app for iPhones – here is a screenshot from my iPad 3

Even though the app is not universal – you can see Google+ has high-res / retina display assets and so it renders quite ‘crisp’ even at 2x zoom on the iPad.
This is great job using fonts and HTML elements so the overall effect is impressive.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google&#43; You can add me to your circles</title>
      <link>https://damien1.github.io/promo/google-are-you-in-yet-4326/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Oct 2011 21:07:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien1.github.io/promo/google-are-you-in-yet-4326/</guid>
      <description>Google+ is the new social network which has everybody talking. If you haven’t joined in yet, it’s nothing new. Except it’s all about you and me and everyone we know.
 So please add me to your circles and let’s get to know a bit more about each other.
 Have you added me to your Google+ http://damiens.ws/ql8xsS</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Interactive] Dangermouse wants you to ro.me &amp;#8211; another great HTML5 music video</title>
      <link>https://damien1.github.io/video/interactive-dangermouse-wants-you-to-ro-me-another-great-html5-music-video-3497/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2011 11:22:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien1.github.io/video/interactive-dangermouse-wants-you-to-ro-me-another-great-html5-music-video-3497/</guid>
      <description>Music artist and producer Dangermouse has done it again – or that’s to say Google has done it with HTML5. The new album called Romeis in the style of a (spaghetti western) film soundtrack and if you’ve not hear it — then you’re missing out.
 HTML5 Music Video wow-ness  Google has again helped to create an interactive music video ‘Chrome Experiment’ – to show off some of the awesome-ness that is HTML5.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Android Market would benefit Developer instead of Apple App Certification?</title>
      <link>https://damien1.github.io/blog/android/android-market-benefits-developer-apples-app-certification-515/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Mar 2010 22:29:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien1.github.io/blog/android/android-market-benefits-developer-apples-app-certification-515/</guid>
      <description>Develop apps for Android or develop mobile apps for Apple, some days its hard to figure out just what to do. On this website I’ve written a lot on Android phones and apps.Around 6000 apps have been removed from the Apple store recently due to their erotic nature. It’s not that Android Market has no quality control – Adult or Erotic does not exist as a content category in Android Market but dating apps or other soft-porn apps so far have not shown huge growth (ahem) on Android.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NewsRob best Android application for Google Reader</title>
      <link>https://damien1.github.io/blog/android/newsrob-best-android-application-for-google-reader-538/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Feb 2010 15:11:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien1.github.io/blog/android/newsrob-best-android-application-for-google-reader-538/</guid>
      <description>Newsrob is my favourite application for Android mobiles, it’s been covered in my 10Best Android Apps** list a few times. **Newsrob** integratess with your account for Google Reader (which allows you to manage and read all your RSS feeds). Newsrob recently turned 1 and celebrated by introducing a Pro version and an Adfunded Free Version.**
What’s fantastic about Newsrob Pro Newsrob Prohas a new feature that is great for any social media or mobile specialist.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mobile SEO &amp;#8211; Google extends click to call to mobile search</title>
      <link>https://damien1.github.io/mobile-marketing/mobile-seo-google-extends-click-to-call-to-mobile-search-446/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Feb 2010 09:11:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien1.github.io/mobile-marketing/mobile-seo-google-extends-click-to-call-to-mobile-search-446/</guid>
      <description>In the next couple of weeks, I’ll be looking closely at Mobile Search and Mobile SEO. This week will be a round up of features on Google Mobile Search
Click to Call
Click to call has been a feature of WAP and mobile portals for sometime, however the mobile phones needed to support this action.
Google has now added Click to Call to Adword Mobile Search Results
Anyone running SEO or Adword campaigns should make sure they have configured the mobile search results as well and to now include the primary phone number for customers or clients to ring in on.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google Wave will it change SMS Texting and Instant Messaging</title>
      <link>https://damien1.github.io/general/google-wave-will-it-change-sms-texting-and-instant-messaging-195/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Aug 2009 14:45:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien1.github.io/general/google-wave-will-it-change-sms-texting-and-instant-messaging-195/</guid>
      <description>Will Google Wave change SMS texting and instant messaging? Most likely … but that’s about the best answer right now. Google will have to find partners to help ‘aggregate’ chat and email and address Internet infrastructure issues in a number of countries.
Thanks to Googles reach, Wave can launch and get a good penetration into its addressable Gmail base. It’s all looking good with a Public Beta? of 100,000 invites due to be sent out in September.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>10 Best Android Apps for your phone</title>
      <link>https://damien1.github.io/blog/android/10-best-android-apps-for-your-phone-250/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Aug 2009 15:14:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien1.github.io/blog/android/10-best-android-apps-for-your-phone-250/</guid>
      <description>Here’s a more up to date list featuring some of the best apps you must get on your Android phone. All of them are free in the Android Market. Some of them also have a freemium paid version. What’s good is that many of these you will use daily, but some of them will just sit on your phone and do what its supposed to do.(update: Nov 21 – Cyrket.com has been offline for some time … but is now around again – but try www.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2 Must have Android Apps from Google</title>
      <link>https://damien1.github.io/general/2-must-have-android-apps-from-google-for-your-htc-magic-or-g1-226/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2009 18:11:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien1.github.io/general/2-must-have-android-apps-from-google-for-your-htc-magic-or-g1-226/</guid>
      <description>Looking for somewhere to go …. Maybe you need to waste some time or want to find something else to try on your Google Android G1 or HTC Magic.
Google obviously has embedded a lot things into the phone – but here are 2 apps that were not installed on the Android phone when you open the box.
Places DirectoryPrice FREE Downloads &amp;gt;250,000
updated — 21 Sept –– Even before augmented reality became a buzzword … Google Places Directory was already bringing Google Maps together with GPS / Location Based Services.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Android Market Best of Apps you must have</title>
      <link>https://damien1.github.io/general/android-market-best-of-apps-you-must-have-166/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Apr 2009 21:23:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien1.github.io/general/android-market-best-of-apps-you-must-have-166/</guid>
      <description>29 Sep 09: This is the better post to read: http://damien.co/2009/08/11/10-best-android-apps-for-your-phone/
Ok I’ve been using an HTC Magic for a few days now and I’m loving it … I’m so hooked I could almost get myself kicked out of the house, or have my ‘beautiful &amp;amp; precious’ phone smashed 🙁Here’s what you too should try there are so many free Apps in the Android Market that you can’t get bored. Given how much I use a phone and my focus on the mobiles and music, heres a choice selection</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>