<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Klout on Damien Saunders</title>
    <link>https://damien.co/tags/klout/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Klout on Damien Saunders</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 19 Jun 2012 14:29:49 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://damien.co/tags/klout/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Best tools to start with Social Media Marketing &amp;#8211; 2011 re-cap (where are they now)</title>
      <link>https://damien.co/social-media-marketing-2/best-tools-to-start-with-social-media-marketing-2011-re-cap-where-are-they-now-7192/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jun 2012 14:29:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien.co/social-media-marketing-2/best-tools-to-start-with-social-media-marketing-2011-re-cap-where-are-they-now-7192/</guid>
      <description>[typography font=”Special Elite” size=”25″ size_format=”px”]If you’re just getting started with Social Media marketing then you need at least 1 web based tool to help you.[/typography]
__In 2011, I wrote a great article on the best tools to start with Social Media Marketing. A year later, things have changed, so I wanted to look back at my 2011 suggestions to see where they are now.
Keep track of your social media status and influence, albeit using Klout’s own scoring.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best Tools for Social Media Marketing if you&#39;re just getting started</title>
      <link>https://damien.co/blog/2011-07-26-best-tools-for-social-media-marketing-if-youre-just-getting-started/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2011 14:00:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien.co/blog/2011-07-26-best-tools-for-social-media-marketing-if-youre-just-getting-started/</guid>
      <description>If you&amp;rsquo;re getting started with Social Media marketing then you need at least 1 web based tool to help you.
For most businesses and individuals, social media marketing starts and ends with Tweetdeck. Which provides an all-in-one solution for pushing content direct from your machine. You need better tools for planning and managing your social media marketing.
However browser based tools for social media marketing are better suited for team or office environs – or if you&amp;rsquo;re like me, someone on the road in different offices who can&amp;rsquo;t have Tweetdeck open all the time.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>