<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Windows on Damien Saunders</title>
    <link>http://damien.co/tags/windows/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Windows on Damien Saunders</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 26 Jun 2010 14:16:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://damien.co/tags/windows/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Tip of the Day: Windows Vista SP2 won&amp;#039;t install on a partitioned drive</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/tip-of-the-day-windows-vista-sp2-wont-install-on-a-partitioned-drive-320/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Sep 2009 15:18:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/tip-of-the-day-windows-vista-sp2-wont-install-on-a-partitioned-drive-320/</guid>
      <description>Tip of the day: Windows Vista clean install doesn&amp;rsquo;t work on a partitioned drive AND if you then partition the drive after installing Vista, the SP2 will not install as well.
Effectively this means you should keep your primary drive as 1 partition … or wait til after you&amp;rsquo;ve installed Vista and all the service packs.
There is a short microsoft kb on this ….
Will this affect installing Windows 7 for the same reason … I think so.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mac OSx Convert - Office tip move between documents</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/mac-osx-convert-office-tip-move-between-documents-308/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Sep 2009 23:47:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/mac-osx-convert-office-tip-move-between-documents-308/</guid>
      <description>Here&amp;rsquo;s a quick one for you … how do you switch between a number of open documents in Word or Excel?
The quick Mac way is CMD + `
The Windows Office way was Pressing F6
If you still want to do this … on the Mac then you have to press FN + Shift + F6</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Virtualbox 3.0.4 Mac OSx How to share folders</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/virtualbox-3-0-4-mac-osx-how-to-share-folders-274/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Aug 2009 20:07:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/virtualbox-3-0-4-mac-osx-how-to-share-folders-274/</guid>
      <description>Virtualbox 3.0.4 is a new update released earlier this month. After updating to this new version file sharing between mac os and the guest windows vista has stopped working.
Something wonderful has happened and there is a new feature that has been added … Under the Devices Menu there is a new entry for “Sharing Folders” - you can now create shared folders in realtime
However to make the shared folders work you still must use the old method of mapping a network drive and remember to type your shared folder name as</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ill move to Linux thanks Amarok</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/2008-08-14-ill-move-to-linux-thanks-amarok/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2008 09:06:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/2008-08-14-ill-move-to-linux-thanks-amarok/</guid>
      <description>Damien says, one of the biggest problems with Linux has always been a lack of strength in its media players. Amarok v2 is now in the pipe and its looking great.
The Amarok 1 client which most Linux users had to use (it was the best option) really lacked in its options for managing artists, albums, compilations as it relied on a database driven columns view. I never found that easy to use.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Whats your media player?</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/whats-your-media-player-88/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Aug 2008 20:18:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/whats-your-media-player-88/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m starting a reader survey on Media Players - as there are a few assumptions I wanted to prove or understand.
  If you have an iPod, iPhone or iTouch you use iTunes
  You use Winamp casue you don&amp;rsquo;t want to use iTunes or WMP
  you use windows media player as its the only thing you know or its the only one on your PC / Laptop</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HOW TO install Virtualbox on Mac osx host &amp;amp; WinXp guest using TinyXP rev</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/2009-04-10-how-to-install-virtualbox-mac-osx-host-winxp-guest-using-tinyxp-rev-09/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/2009-04-10-how-to-install-virtualbox-mac-osx-host-winxp-guest-using-tinyxp-rev-09/</guid>
      <description>Virtualbox is a dream freeware solution for anyone - novice to geek - who wants to run different computers inside their computer - virtual so to speak. Today I&amp;rsquo;ve been tinkering with getting Virtualbox working on a Mac laptop running WinXP.
this is a very old post whats contained below has not been checked since 2012
Virtualbox from Oracle Sunis a freeware, open source virtualisation application .. it comes in a number of flavours - I&amp;rsquo;ve previously used it to run WinXP guests inside WinXP hosts for testing and at work it was the only way to install things without having to go to the IT helpdesk.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>