<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>windows 7 on Damien Saunders</title>
    <link>https://damien1.github.io/tags/windows-7/</link>
    <description>Recent content in windows 7 on Damien Saunders</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 26 Jun 2010 14:16:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://damien1.github.io/tags/windows-7/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>HOW TO Can’t Install Windows 7 upgrade with Virtualbox</title>
      <link>https://damien1.github.io/general/how-to-cant-install-windows-7-upgrade-with-virtualbox-1088/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Jun 2010 14:16:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien1.github.io/general/how-to-cant-install-windows-7-upgrade-with-virtualbox-1088/</guid>
      <description>This is an extremely short guide to a major problem with Windows 7 using Virtualbox. Many users come to this site looking to find the answer – which is – Windows 7 Home Upgrade is sold in Europe and elsewhere as a full install version.
The problem is that installation via Virtualbox will complete but the user will not be able to ‘register’ their copy Windows 7.
The only way to install Windows 7 Upgrade using Virtualbox is to first install Windows XP and then run the Windows 7 Upgrade disc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>15 minute guide to Virtualbox Windows 7 RC1 and your Mac</title>
      <link>https://damien1.github.io/general/15-minute-guide-to-running-windows-7-rc1-on-a-mac-180/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 May 2009 20:05:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien1.github.io/general/15-minute-guide-to-running-windows-7-rc1-on-a-mac-180/</guid>
      <description>So this follows an earlier post of mine about Virtualbox and running Windows XP on a Macbook Pro. Virtualbox is a great piece of software for running virtual operating systems on another machine (like runing Windows 7 on a Mac OSX).Today’s guide shows that you can be up n running with Windows 7 RC in about 15 minutes … thats got to be good ??
So Grab your Windows 7 RC1 ISO file from the Windows website, grab a copy of Virtualbox for Mac and get going.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>