<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Usage on Damien Saunders</title>
    <link>http://damien.co/tags/usage/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Usage on Damien Saunders</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 18 Jul 2012 15:23:16 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://damien.co/tags/usage/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Key trends in mobile usage from the UK</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/2012-07-18-key-trends-in-mobile-usage-from-the-uk/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jul 2012 15:23:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/2012-07-18-key-trends-in-mobile-usage-from-the-uk/</guid>
      <description>Mobile usage in the UK is on the increase. That&amp;rsquo;s all sounding good so far.
The latest communications report from Ofcom has shown a year on year growth of 1.6 million mobiles and the biggest growth in postpaid subscribers due to more customers taking out contracts for smartphones.
Want to download this for free? Read to the end of the presentation and copy the discount coupon code.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Web server performance - usage and load</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/web-server-performance-usage-and-load-5987/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2012 22:00:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/web-server-performance-usage-and-load-5987/</guid>
      <description>Web Application Development can seem easy if you&amp;rsquo;re used to a shared host and WordPress running out of the box. Moving into the world of unmanaged VPS can be daunting at first - or really easy if you&amp;rsquo;re insane.
If you&amp;rsquo;ve got access to a terminal or CLI - command line interface then you have here a number of options for checking your website performance. Here&amp;rsquo;s a few choice one&amp;rsquo;s I&amp;rsquo;ve been using lately.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Social Networks &amp;amp; Social Gaming used most for Mobile Broadband</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/mobile-marketing/social-networks-social-gaming-used-most-for-mobile-broadband-1757/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Oct 2010 09:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/mobile-marketing/social-networks-social-gaming-used-most-for-mobile-broadband-1757/</guid>
      <description>This news from Hutchison 3G UK shows that using social media is more important on their mobile network is interesting …. Keeping up to date with friends or regular gameplay on the move is now more important than checking emails or reading the news. 
In my opinion, Social Networking continues to dominate growth in internet usage - however, you shouldn&amp;rsquo;t assume that its all fun on the go. Social Media sites like Twitter, Facebook and LinkedInare all used for b2b leads and d2c customer service.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>