<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Music on Damien Saunders</title>
    <link>https://damien1.github.io/tags/music/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Music on Damien Saunders</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2011 18:25:48 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://damien1.github.io/tags/music/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Just Updated &amp;#8211; iTunes in the Cloud (beta)</title>
      <link>https://damien1.github.io/general/just-updated-itunes-in-the-cloud-beta-3763/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2011 18:25:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien1.github.io/general/just-updated-itunes-in-the-cloud-beta-3763/</guid>
      <description>There’s a new update to iTunes this morning (evening in the UK) … iTunes 10.3 introduces in the Cloud beta. This was only introduced yesterday at the Apple WWDC.
The update is available for Windows and Apple computers now.
 What’s new in iTunes 10.3 Introducing iTunes in the Cloud beta. The music you purchase in iTunes appears automatically on all your devices. You can also download your past iTunes purchases.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Are you thinking what I&amp;#8217;m thinking? Two predictions for Steve Jobs?</title>
      <link>https://damien1.github.io/general/are-you-thinking-what-im-thinking-two-predictions-for-steve-jobs-3752/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jun 2011 16:04:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien1.github.io/general/are-you-thinking-what-im-thinking-two-predictions-for-steve-jobs-3752/</guid>
      <description>Are you thinking what I’m thinking? It’s only a few hours til the start of the Apple WWDC which is ‘the biggest’ event in the year for Apple Fans.
Something borrowed or something blue? Apple, Lion &amp;amp; iOS5 Does Apple’s new software tickle your fancy? does the idea of conjoined operating systems for mobile and computers excite you?
Yeh I really want a touch-screen on my MacBook Pro – but that will never happen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Interactive] Dangermouse wants you to ro.me &amp;#8211; another great HTML5 music video</title>
      <link>https://damien1.github.io/video/interactive-dangermouse-wants-you-to-ro-me-another-great-html5-music-video-3497/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2011 11:22:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien1.github.io/video/interactive-dangermouse-wants-you-to-ro-me-another-great-html5-music-video-3497/</guid>
      <description>Music artist and producer Dangermouse has done it again – or that’s to say Google has done it with HTML5. The new album called Romeis in the style of a (spaghetti western) film soundtrack and if you’ve not hear it — then you’re missing out.
 HTML5 Music Video wow-ness  Google has again helped to create an interactive music video ‘Chrome Experiment’ – to show off some of the awesome-ness that is HTML5.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Group Review: Manage your CD library collection on a Mac</title>
      <link>https://damien1.github.io/general/cd-library-management-283/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Sep 2009 19:54:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien1.github.io/general/cd-library-management-283/</guid>
      <description>Now that you’ve ripped and digitised all of your CD library – what do you do with your CD’s? One idea is to create a catalogue and then you can box or put away (or recycle) your CD’s and DVD’s giving you much more space to fill with books, CD’s or other stuff.If you’re like me, I’ve been ripping all my CD’s for years and the CD and cases were just collecting dust in my room.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Comparison of Digital Music Retailers in Europe</title>
      <link>https://damien1.github.io/general/comparison-of-digital-music-retailers-in-europe-246/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Aug 2009 17:28:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien1.github.io/general/comparison-of-digital-music-retailers-in-europe-246/</guid>
      <description>Comment: There are a number of digital music retailers working around Europe, here is Damien Saunders’ summary of a few of the bigger services (catalogue greater than 1 million tracks).
&amp;lt;td width=&amp;quot;75&amp;quot;&amp;gt; Countries &amp;lt;/td&amp;gt; &amp;lt;td width=&amp;quot;75&amp;quot;&amp;gt; MP3 to buy &amp;lt;/td&amp;gt; &amp;lt;td width=&amp;quot;79&amp;quot;&amp;gt; Subscription &amp;lt;/td&amp;gt; &amp;lt;td width=&amp;quot;75&amp;quot;&amp;gt; Catalogue Size &amp;lt;/td&amp;gt; &amp;lt;td width=&amp;quot;75&amp;quot;&amp;gt; 3rd Party API &amp;lt;/td&amp;gt; &amp;lt;td width=&amp;quot;75&amp;quot;&amp;gt; PC Software &amp;lt;/td&amp;gt;  &amp;lt;td width=&amp;quot;75&amp;quot;&amp;gt; UK &amp;lt;/td&amp;gt; &amp;lt;td width=&amp;quot;75&amp;quot;&amp;gt; Yes &amp;lt;/td&amp;gt; &amp;lt;td width=&amp;quot;79&amp;quot;&amp;gt; No &amp;lt;/td&amp;gt; &amp;lt;td width=&amp;quot;75&amp;quot;&amp;gt; 3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Aging music lovers what happens when we are 80?</title>
      <link>https://damien1.github.io/general/aging-music-lovers-what-happens-when-we-are-80-191/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 May 2009 15:26:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien1.github.io/general/aging-music-lovers-what-happens-when-we-are-80-191/</guid>
      <description>In a few years time, many of us will want to retire … what’s going to happen to us and our communities we live in if suddenly todays 20 and 30 somethings are 80? What music or digital entertainment will there be? Remembering also that as we start ‘age’ we will have to work later in life beyond today’s retirement age.If, the aging population is bigger than the younger generation – does that mean nightclubs, discos and places like Ibiza will become the place for the 70+ age group?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Datz makes downloading unlimited DRM free music hard</title>
      <link>https://damien1.github.io/general/datz-makes-downloading-unlimited-drm-free-music-hard-110/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2008 10:36:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien1.github.io/general/datz-makes-downloading-unlimited-drm-free-music-hard-110/</guid>
      <description>Comment: Datz music lounge has come out for Xmas in the UK with a £99.99 unlimited music DRM free offer. So whats the hooks … plenty even before you get going.
So Datz announced unlimited DRM Free music downloads (legally) this week … the service has an upfront fee of £99.99 – probably too steep for most people to consider – but maybe Sainsburys thinks it will be a last minute stocking stuffer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sony Ericsson does chunky retro Walkman W902</title>
      <link>https://damien1.github.io/general/sony-ericsson-does-chunky-retro-walkman-w902-99/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2008 13:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien1.github.io/general/sony-ericsson-does-chunky-retro-walkman-w902-99/</guid>
      <description>I’ve had a look at the Sony Ericsson new Walkman W902 with retro chunky buttons much like a those on a casette walkman.
The phone’s not retro though – Clear Crystal Audio for your listening pleasure and a 5.0 mega pixel camera is a great feature. I think its also got a really good speaker to annoy Grannies on the bus with.
I hope it comes out with more than a 1Gb of memory!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I&amp;#039;ll move to Linux thanks Amarok</title>
      <link>https://damien1.github.io/general/ill-move-to-linux-thanks-amarok-96/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2008 09:06:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien1.github.io/general/ill-move-to-linux-thanks-amarok-96/</guid>
      <description>Damien says, one of the biggest problems with Linux has always been a lack of strength in its media players. Amarok v2 is now in the pipe and its looking great.
The Amarok 1 client which most Linux users had to use (it was the best option) really lacked in its options for managing artists, albums, compilations as it relied on a database driven columns view. I never found that easy to use.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Music file sharing on the up and up</title>
      <link>https://damien1.github.io/general/music-file-sharing-on-the-up-and-up-81/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2008 15:28:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien1.github.io/general/music-file-sharing-on-the-up-and-up-81/</guid>
      <description>Damien Saunders says -research shows continued growth in file-sharing and downloading of mp3s is now common place. This survey supports the view that prosecuting the mass population is not the right approach by the labels and rights associations.
British Music Rights research shows that file-sharing is done by a large number of people and even more are downloading music.
Music week reports these findings:
42% of those surveyed say they have uploaded files.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apple to standardise iTunes prices in Europe</title>
      <link>https://damien1.github.io/general/apple-to-standardise-itunes-prices-in-europe-69/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jan 2008 15:08:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien1.github.io/general/apple-to-standardise-itunes-prices-in-europe-69/</guid>
      <description> comment: The reason that Apple charges different retail prices in each market is due to the differences in wholesale prices charged in each market by the major labels. Apple could use this as leverage against the labels to lower their prices in all major EU markets
 </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>