<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Maintenance on Damien Saunders</title>
    <link>http://damien.co/tags/maintenance/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Maintenance on Damien Saunders</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2012 18:58:26 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://damien.co/tags/maintenance/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Planned maintenance and work tonight</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/planned-maintenance-and-work-tonight-5851/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2012 18:58:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/planned-maintenance-and-work-tonight-5851/</guid>
      <description>Just a short note — Tonight there will be some planned maintenance and the wonderful team at Evohost will be migrating me to a newer, faster server.
The downtime will hopefully be kept as short as possible – but maybe come back on Saturday if you find anything funny.
Cheers
Damien</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Custom Maintenance Page for WordPress</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/2011-12-26-custom-maintenance-page-for-wordpress/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Dec 2011 13:00:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/2011-12-26-custom-maintenance-page-for-wordpress/</guid>
      <description>[WordPress] is a great tool. It has its own way of managing updates to your website – and will switch to maintenance mode automatically. Sometimes this is called an HTTP Status 503 Service Unavailable.
For the best user experience you can setup your own custom maintenance page – where you can show your brand, making it clear that this is planned maintenance and give your visitor some where else to go.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to enable WordPress maintenance mode</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/2011-07-09-how-to-enable-wordpress-maintenance-mode-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Jul 2011 17:00:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/2011-07-09-how-to-enable-wordpress-maintenance-mode-2/</guid>
      <description>WordPress is a great tool. It has its own way of managing updates to your website - and will switch to maintenance mode automatically. For the best user experience you should enable maintenance mode yourself.
How to Enable Maintenance Mode without a Plugin - method 1 Activating maintenance mode without a plugin is easy. First, open your FTP program and then navigate to the root folder of you WordPress install.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HOW TO: Enable WordPress maintenance mode</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/wordpress/how-to-enable-wordpress-maintenance-mode-2964/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 May 2011 15:36:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/wordpress/how-to-enable-wordpress-maintenance-mode-2964/</guid>
      <description>WordPress is a great tool. It has its own way of managing updates to your website – and will switch to maintenance mode automatically. For the best user experience you should enable maintenance mode yourself.
How to Enable Maintenance Mode without a Plugin – method 1 Activating maintenance mode without a plugin is easy. First, open your FTP program and then navigate to the root folder of you WordPress install.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>