<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>ZOHO CRM on Damien Saunders</title>
    <link>http://damien.co/tags/zoho-crm/</link>
    <description>Recent content in ZOHO CRM on Damien Saunders</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2011 15:08:21 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://damien.co/tags/zoho-crm/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Updates to popular posts on Zoho CRM [Housekeeping]</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/social-crm/updates-to-popular-posts-on-zoho-crm-housekeeping-4622/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2011 15:08:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/social-crm/updates-to-popular-posts-on-zoho-crm-housekeeping-4622/</guid>
      <description>Zoho CRM is a popular cloud-based service for customer relationship management and I&amp;rsquo;ve been using it for a few years. Recently, I&amp;rsquo;ve started to revisit and update some of earlier posts on Zoho CRM, some of this was prompted by feedback from my customer insights (using Kiss Insights) survey.
So far I&amp;rsquo;ve updated 2 articles - fixed broken images and checked the content of the post:
What is a lead vs contact vs account</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HOW TO get started with ZOHO CRM and load your contacts from Google CSV</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/2011-10-23-how-to-get-started-with-zoho-crm-and-load-your-contacts-from-google-csv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Oct 2011 16:43:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/2011-10-23-how-to-get-started-with-zoho-crm-and-load-your-contacts-from-google-csv/</guid>
      <description>So you have decided to use ZOHO CRM as your Customer Relationship Management (CRM) solution. You&amp;rsquo;re first step is to import your contacts into ZOHO. You will have contacts in a number of places and you want to get them all into ZOHO.
This guide applies to single users of ZOHO CRM and the SOHO small business marketing guy like me. I&amp;rsquo;ll start by focusing on the single user perspective of ZOHO - how to get mycontacts into ZOHO and then I&amp;rsquo;ll finish by mentioning a few tips for people who want to share ZOHO with others in their team.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ZOHO CRM just integrated with Google Sites</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/2010-11-03-zoho-crm-just-integrated-with-google-sites/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Nov 2010 09:42:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/2010-11-03-zoho-crm-just-integrated-with-google-sites/</guid>
      <description>ZOHO CRMis one of the best web based SaaS customer relationship managementweb apps around and now its gone and made it even easier to capture your leads or enquiries from your website - if you use Google Sites.Currently Social CRM is the new name for managing customers - CRM wasn&amp;rsquo;t good enough and wasn&amp;rsquo;t work for many. The new tag Social CRM refers to engaging customers online where ever they are and hopefully that&amp;rsquo;s on your website!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Essential Collection of ZOHO CRM Guides</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/2010-06-28-essential-collection-of-zoho-crm-guides/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jun 2010 09:00:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/2010-06-28-essential-collection-of-zoho-crm-guides/</guid>
      <description>Here is a summer essential collection for ZOHO CRM a customer relationship management or CRM solution. When you get started in business your sales and marketing activities will need to be split 3 ways -
 Customers who are buying from you Nurturing Customers who will buy from you Generating new leads or potential customers  This may seem daunting - so from the day you open your doors or your new web business you&amp;rsquo;ll want a tool to track all your customers and maybe your suppliers too.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Essential Startup Resources for Customer Relationship Management</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/startup/essential-startup-resources-for-customer-relationship-management-1053/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jun 2010 13:22:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/startup/essential-startup-resources-for-customer-relationship-management-1053/</guid>
      <description>So here is an essential collection of startup resources to customer relationship management or CRM. When you go into business as a startup or entrepreneur your sales and marketing activities will need to be split 3 ways -
 Customers who are buying from you Nurturing Customers who will buy from you Generating new leads or potential customers  This may seem daunting - so from the day you open your doors or your new web business you&amp;rsquo;ll want a tool to track all your customers and maybe your suppliers too.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HOW TO: ZOHO CRM empty your Recycle bin to delete accounts &amp;amp; contacts</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/2010-05-08-how-to-zoho-crm-empty-your-recycle-bin-to-delete-accounts-contacts/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 May 2010 22:10:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/2010-05-08-how-to-zoho-crm-empty-your-recycle-bin-to-delete-accounts-contacts/</guid>
      <description>ZOHO CRM is one of the best web based (SaaS) customer relationship management solutions around today and it&amp;rsquo;s got great features even in its free version.
How to delete your contacts, leads, accounts and is pretty easy thing to manage in ZOHO, but until you empty your Recycle Bin, they are still there (and this can affect some reports and views).
The Empty Recycle Bin icon is at the top of the screen on the right hand side … clicking it will show you whats in your recycle bin and you can then choose to empty it or recover records.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>