<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>featured on Damien Saunders</title>
    <link>http://damien.co/tags/featured/</link>
    <description>Recent content in featured on Damien Saunders</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 24 Apr 2011 12:28:13 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://damien.co/tags/featured/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Switching to Scrivener for WordPress blogging</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/wordpress/switching-to-scrivener-for-wordpress-blogging-2901/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Apr 2011 12:28:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/wordpress/switching-to-scrivener-for-wordpress-blogging-2901/</guid>
      <description>I’ve just made the switch – or as we speak, I’m starting to learn about this ‘new’ tool for writers called Scrivener. Described as the app for writers, journalists and anyone that needs to write short or long stories, Scrivener collects together scraps of articles, research material and helps to draft your writing.
To me, the biggest problem with regular blogging is the interface. If you blog on the go then you already know that the WordPress admin suite is not very accessible when you’re in a plane, train or automobile.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SEO best practice for using &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt; and &amp;lt;em&amp;gt;</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/social-media/seo-best-practice-for-using-strong-and-em-2695/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2011 09:42:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/social-media/seo-best-practice-for-using-strong-and-em-2695/</guid>
      <description>As more people become aware of HTML5 it’s time to review how tagging written content will impact search engine optimisation. Tags like and are redundant – instead and have been in use for a few years by many blogging and web developer tools. Now the HTML5 standard recognises that and should only be used for visual style.
You can do more with CSS styles If you remember writing HTML back in the 90’s you might be more comfortable using and .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ideas using Foursquare for Travel Professionals</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/social-media/foursquare/ideas-using-foursquare-for-travel-professionals-2233/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Dec 2010 09:18:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/social-media/foursquare/ideas-using-foursquare-for-travel-professionals-2233/</guid>
      <description>As travel professionals know, your customers want holiday experiences to always remember and preferably off the beaten trail. This week I started a new series focused on Ideas using Foursquarefor social media marketing with guides that will help increase customer satisfaction and improve retention.Today, I will be looking at how you can use social media to offer up some pretty amazing travel experiences using Foursquare. If your clients don’t want to read a Time Out or carry a Lonely Planet – then Foursquare is the perfect guide for locals!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to choose a good social media marketing consultant</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/social-media/how-to-choose-a-good-social-media-marketing-consultant-2030/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Nov 2010 09:41:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/social-media/how-to-choose-a-good-social-media-marketing-consultant-2030/</guid>
      <description>Social media marketingis no longer a buzzword and many brands and businesses are choosing to recruit full-time staff to develop and deliver the quicksilver successesof the best viral campaigns.What’s the difference between a social media consultant, digital planner &amp;amp; a community manager? If you are looking for an independent social media strategist to come in as a consultant or freelance gig then you need to know why a social media marketing consultant is very different to a digital planner or community manager.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Task Management with Post-It Notes</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/startup/task-management-with-post-it-notes-1832/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Nov 2010 09:56:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/startup/task-management-with-post-it-notes-1832/</guid>
      <description>As I’m a certified Scrum Master and very good at project and task management I can say I enjoy running planning sessions with teams I do work with. Now I’ve started to discover the freedom of the Post-It Note for planning and brainstorming.

Even better, its essential for any startup to be able to focus on what has to be done and avoid distractions like outsiders wanting extra work or changes to scope.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>9 Step Guide to Foursquare for Business</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/social-media/foursquare/9-step-guide-to-foursquare-for-business-1703/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Oct 2010 09:00:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/social-media/foursquare/9-step-guide-to-foursquare-for-business-1703/</guid>
      <description>Fresh off the press and updated for everyone that loves Foursquare – 9 step guide to Foursquare for businesses will get you started today.
This guide covers the 9 key points for any retailer – including Why Foursquare! What’s covered in the guide you ask? — then just have a look</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Are Twitter Followers better than Fans?</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/social-media/twitter/are-twitter-followers-better-than-fans-1538/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Sep 2010 11:00:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/social-media/twitter/are-twitter-followers-better-than-fans-1538/</guid>
      <description>Are Twitter Followers better than Facebook Fanswas a topic discussed on emarketer recently. It’s a question I get asked all the time – relatively speaking – Which is the best social network to start social media marketing? The thing is you need to try them both at the same time.And here is the problem every social network has its pro’s and cons – and here is the answer. If you were a criminal, on trial in the Old Bailey, the prosecution’s job is to prove you had the intention of committing a crime, so it was just an accident.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>