<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Layouts on Damien Saunders</title>
    <link>https://damien1.github.io/tags/layouts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Layouts on Damien Saunders</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 15 Oct 2012 11:34:42 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://damien1.github.io/tags/layouts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Freetile &amp;#8211; Visual Post Layouts just about ready</title>
      <link>https://damien1.github.io/blog/2012-10-15-freetile-visual-post-layouts-just-about-ready/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Oct 2012 11:34:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien1.github.io/blog/2012-10-15-freetile-visual-post-layouts-just-about-ready/</guid>
      <description>I wanted to give you a bit of a flavourof what’s coming with my new Visual Post Layouts plugin for WordPress. First things first … it’s ‘pretty good’ (if you’re English) or AWESOME!!!! (if you’re American, Australian, or from anywhere else).
The next thing you can see is the bright colours – there are 7 styles to choose from – Orange, Red, Yellow, Blue, Green, Violet &amp;amp; White.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Visual Post Layouts &amp;#8211; with colour options</title>
      <link>https://damien1.github.io/blog/2012-09-25-visual-post-layouts-with-colour-options/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Sep 2012 22:00:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien1.github.io/blog/2012-09-25-visual-post-layouts-with-colour-options/</guid>
      <description>Visual Post Layouts will be my next WordPress plugin. It’s nearly ready and I’ve been working hard to allow some great control over the plugin.
What’s Coming up? In the first release of the Visual Post Layouts, you’ll have a great set of features as part of the shortcode.
You can create a visual post layout in a post, a page, in fact … almost anywhere 🙂
You also have the option to choose a different colour scheme – if you don’t like Sticky Note Yellow … there will be Violet, Orange and Green.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Freetile Visual Post Layouts a plugin WordPress</title>
      <link>https://damien1.github.io/blog/2012-09-11-freetile-visual-post-layouts-a-plugin-wordpress/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Sep 2012 22:39:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien1.github.io/blog/2012-09-11-freetile-visual-post-layouts-a-plugin-wordpress/</guid>
      <description>Today I’ve been reading up on Freetilea jQuery project by Yannisfor visual layouts similar to what I’ve done with Isotope Visual Post Layouts.
 Freetile is a plugin for jQuery that enables the organization of webpage content in an efficient, dynamic and responsive layout. It can be applied to a container element and it will attempt to arrange it’s children in a layout that makes optimal use of screen space, by “packing” them in a tight arrangement.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Isotope Visual Post Layouts for WordPress version 0.31 is out</title>
      <link>https://damien1.github.io/blog/2012-09-06-isotope-visual-post-layouts-for-wordpress-version-0-3-is-out/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Sep 2012 21:49:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien1.github.io/blog/2012-09-06-isotope-visual-post-layouts-for-wordpress-version-0-3-is-out/</guid>
      <description>Isotope Visual Post Layouts is my plugin for WordPress that makes it easy to add some stunning visual effects to your blog. I’ve just updated the plugin and if you have this installed, then WordPress should tell you automatically to update sometime in the next 24 hours.
Isotope Visual Post Layouts version 0.31 is out I’ve just updated the plugin to v0.31, it’s tested and supported on WordPress 3.4.2 and I also fixed a bug and added a feature.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>