<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>LinkedIn on Damien Saunders</title>
    <link>https://damien1.github.io/tags/linkedin/</link>
    <description>Recent content in LinkedIn on Damien Saunders</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 30 Nov 2010 09:48:33 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://damien1.github.io/tags/linkedin/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Have you tried LinkedIn lately?</title>
      <link>https://damien1.github.io/social-media/have-you-tried-linkedin-lately-2033/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Nov 2010 09:48:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien1.github.io/social-media/have-you-tried-linkedin-lately-2033/</guid>
      <description>LinkedInhas been the business social networkof choice for many and its nearly 10 years old, but younger upstarts have such a mass that its time to look at what LinkedIn can offer to social media marketing, especially for b2b marketing.
There is value in personally knowing your connection When LinkedIn first launched it was not much more than a way to list your work history and connect with business colleagues. It was even important that you had the email address of someone before you could add them – which meant at least you had their business card as people wouldn’t accept requests to connect if they couldn’t remember how they met you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LinkedIn makes it easier to view who viewed your profile</title>
      <link>https://damien1.github.io/social-media/linkedin-makes-it-easier-to-view-who-viewed-your-profile-1777/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Nov 2010 09:07:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien1.github.io/social-media/linkedin-makes-it-easier-to-view-who-viewed-your-profile-1777/</guid>
      <description>LinkedInhas changed its settings so that basic or free users can now find out who actually looked at their profile in the last week. This cool new feature can be found on the LinkedIn website– but you have to first change your own privacy settings from anonymous to share in the benefits of profile stats. I guess its the business persons equivalent of a Facebook poke or like.
Check it out … and while you’re at it – add me as a colleague on LinkedIn</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>