<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>video on Damien Saunders</title>
    <link>https://damien.co/tags/video/</link>
    <description>Recent content in video on Damien Saunders</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2013 11:57:12 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://damien.co/tags/video/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>1 minute video &amp;#8211; Isotope Visual Layouts WordPress plugin</title>
      <link>https://damien.co/blog/2013-03-18-1-minute-video-isotope-visual-layouts-wordpress-plugin/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2013 11:57:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien.co/blog/2013-03-18-1-minute-video-isotope-visual-layouts-wordpress-plugin/</guid>
      <description>Just been on a bit of a testing mission this weekend … I’ve put together this 1 minute screen recording of my WordPress plugin Isotope Visual Layouts.
The video is taken from my Selenium based testing and goes from plugin install, checking plugin options, adding a page, viewing the results and finally deleting the plugin.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[video] Online Shopping with Swedish Twist &amp;#8211; 3 LiveShop</title>
      <link>https://damien.co/strategy/video-online-shopping-with-swedish-twist-3-liveshop-3039/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2011 10:09:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien.co/strategy/video-online-shopping-with-swedish-twist-3-liveshop-3039/</guid>
      <description>Have you seen this … This has to be the future of customer service and online shopping — say goodbye to messy forms or complicated shopping charts. Those crazy people in Tre Sweden www.tre.se just like to push the envelope here. And maybe some of those other mobile operators or utility providers can do this too.
Once you’ve checked out this promo video – go take a look at the 3 LiveShop – it uses Adobe Flash embed video chat for the fun stuff.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video &amp;amp; Integrated Marketing? Latest Internet Usage Video</title>
      <link>https://damien.co/social-media/video-integrated-marketing-latest-internet-usage-video-562/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Mar 2010 10:46:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien.co/social-media/video-integrated-marketing-latest-internet-usage-video-562/</guid>
      <description>Integrated marketing takes a new turn. This latest viral marketing video focuses on the state of the internetand is essentially a load of stats overlaid with a nice cheesy beat playing. All of the statistics are freely available metrics on social media usage, number of internet users, amount of spam mail. Integrated Marketing Viral Video – State of the Internet You have to watch the video first:
Even if you have watched this video infographic already and love it (yes I love it) watch it again.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>