<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Latvia on Damien Saunders</title>
    <link>http://damien.co/tags/latvia/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Latvia on Damien Saunders</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2010 09:30:03 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://damien.co/tags/latvia/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Case Study How to get 100 people in your retail store at the same time</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/2010-11-16-case-study-how-to-get-100-people-in-your-retail-store-at-the-same-time/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2010 09:30:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/2010-11-16-case-study-how-to-get-100-people-in-your-retail-store-at-the-same-time/</guid>
      <description>Regular followers of my work, will have seen an earlier case study on Foursquare marketing for retail and I&amp;rsquo;ve recently been updating this. So this week there are a couple of posts on the Swarm Badge Party that was organised in Latvia.Foursquare casestudy how to get more people in your store
Client Brief Bite Latvija just opened a new technical advice and support centre dedicated to questions about mobile broadband, device configuration and helping people get the most from their mobile.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1st Foursquare Swarm Badge party in Latvia</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/2010-09-22-1st-foursquare-swarm-badge-party-in-latvia/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Sep 2010 09:00:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/2010-09-22-1st-foursquare-swarm-badge-party-in-latvia/</guid>
      <description>Eastern Europe might not be where you would expect to find social media marketing being trialled &amp;lsquo;so soon&amp;rsquo;. In Latvia, this week a Foursquare Swarm Badgeparty is being organised by a local mobile operator Bite Latvija.Latvia is fairly new to smart phones - but Twitter has been embraced by internet users - first for finding and following news stories and now Twitter is more popular than Facebook. So it must be possible to get 50 people in a room with a joint interest in new technology and mobile phones.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>