<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>startups on Damien Saunders</title>
    <link>https://damien.co/tags/startups/</link>
    <description>Recent content in startups on Damien Saunders</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 10 Sep 2012 14:06:15 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://damien.co/tags/startups/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Startup Metrics for Pirates (SeedCamp 2008)</title>
      <link>https://damien.co/startup/startup-metrics-for-pirates-seedcamp-2008-7781/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Sep 2012 14:06:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien.co/startup/startup-metrics-for-pirates-seedcamp-2008-7781/</guid>
      <description>If you’re in a Startup you need to agree quite quickly on some of those performance metrics and here, Dave McClure shares his view.
Sure you can go for the glamour figures — like millions of page views, likes or tweets. But wouldn’t you just prefer some hard cash? or qualified leads?
At the end of the day, the stats you pick, you have to stick with and track over time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Required Summer Reading for startups &amp;#038; product development</title>
      <link>https://damien.co/general/required-summer-reading-for-startups-product-development-4263/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jul 2011 09:14:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien.co/general/required-summer-reading-for-startups-product-development-4263/</guid>
      <description>If you’re about to head off for some sun – do pack these 2 books so you can say you seriously did some ‘work’.
Why Do I need to know these books? You need to know about current tools and the best practices as they are already appearing in many business plans, marketing strategy or new product definitions.
If you evaluate startups and are not getting a business model canvas then you should tell them to go re-write their business pan.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Android Markets – Going International – advice for developers, VCs &amp;amp; startups</title>
      <link>https://damien.co/general/android-markets-going-international-advice-for-developers-vcs-startups-874/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Apr 2010 15:00:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien.co/general/android-markets-going-international-advice-for-developers-vcs-startups-874/</guid>
      <description>Developing for Android? You need to look to the bigger picture … actually this applies to anyone developing apps for mobile phones. If you want your app to be used by people that don’t speak English you need to translate it and provide some support.
There are going to be many opportunities for startups and anyone with a business model to go ‘international’ or expand abroad should check these points are covered in the marketing and product development plans.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>