<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>SocMedSun on Damien Saunders</title>
    <link>https://damien.co/tags/socmedsun/</link>
    <description>Recent content in SocMedSun on Damien Saunders</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 28 Nov 2010 16:53:54 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://damien.co/tags/socmedsun/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Social Media Sunday</title>
      <link>https://damien.co/social-media/social-media-sunday-2-2078/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Nov 2010 16:53:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien.co/social-media/social-media-sunday-2-2078/</guid>
      <description>It’s here again – Social Media Sunday and this week I have chosen 3 of the best Google Apps for social networking and project management.

If you don’t use Google Apps with a custom domain … then you don’t know what you are missing.
Socialwok 
Socialwok creates a professional social network instantly for everyone on the same domain. You can also create projects or shared folders (called Feeds) and invite external people — clients?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Social media Sunday</title>
      <link>https://damien.co/social-media/social-media-sunday-1977/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Nov 2010 11:35:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien.co/social-media/social-media-sunday-1977/</guid>
      <description>Social media Sunday continues this week … With a theme on presentations and communicating. I’m in the country this weekend, so this post was done using blogpress on my iPad which has some great features for managing wordpress more like a magazine.
 Navigation alternatives and insights  Jess3 how social media is changing design  Social media and mobile. From an educationalists perspective
http://www.slideshare.net/mobile/timbuckteeth/combining-mobile-tools-and-social-media#20  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Seen around the internet &amp;#8211; Social Media Sunday</title>
      <link>https://damien.co/social-media/seen-around-the-internet-social-media-sunday-1925/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Nov 2010 18:13:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien.co/social-media/seen-around-the-internet-social-media-sunday-1925/</guid>
      <description>Here’s a new approach for me … It’s Social Media Sunday so here are a few websites to checkout that caught my eye this week.
1. Arcade Fire – We Used to Wait HTML 5 mashed up with Google Maps StreetView meets Arcade Fire. If you haven’t tried this, I give you a hint, you enter the town where you were born and then sit back and absorb the music and the video.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>