<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>maps on Damien Saunders</title>
    <link>https://damien.co/tags/maps/</link>
    <description>Recent content in maps on Damien Saunders</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Sep 2012 08:44:34 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://damien.co/tags/maps/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>WTF! TomTom you make Apple Maps really do suck</title>
      <link>https://damien.co/blog/wtf-tomtom-you-make-apple-maps-really-do-suck-7849/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Sep 2012 08:44:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien.co/blog/wtf-tomtom-you-make-apple-maps-really-do-suck-7849/</guid>
      <description>To me, I used Apple Maps on my iPad to check walking directions. So why is Apple Maps now powered by a Sat nav company like TomTom. Apparently I have to pay tollS to walk 6m to my home … Not just one toll … That&amp;rsquo;s tolls.
And annoyingly all map data is now from some sat nav company so you can&amp;rsquo;t get walking directions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>myGeoBook is building geolocation tools for any website</title>
      <link>https://damien.co/social-media/mygeobook-2276/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Dec 2010 11:00:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien.co/social-media/mygeobook-2276/</guid>
      <description>myGeoBook is about geolocation &amp;amp; social media, with a set of tools for any website developer to use. Maps maybe sexy to some people and yes everyone is talking about mobile location services right now ([ id=”232″ type=”category”]Foursquare[/] anyone).
Here’s a very short guide on how to add a map to WordPress using myGeoBook — but first, here’s an example. This map is based on the Frommers best restaurants in Europe.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Foursquare Best Location Based Social Networking for Android UK Users</title>
      <link>https://damien.co/social-media/foursquare-best-location-based-social-networking-455/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Feb 2010 18:56:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien.co/social-media/foursquare-best-location-based-social-networking-455/</guid>
      <description>Android mobile owners in the UK will be pleased to know that location based social networkingapps have begun to improve and increase in the number of users. In the past few weeks, top location based social networks such as Brightkiteand Foursquarehave really improved the quality and details of UK locations.**
**
It is a problem of user experience that meant many of these services had few UK users and no UK points of interest.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2 Must have Android Apps from Google</title>
      <link>https://damien.co/general/2-must-have-android-apps-from-google-for-your-htc-magic-or-g1-226/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2009 18:11:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien.co/general/2-must-have-android-apps-from-google-for-your-htc-magic-or-g1-226/</guid>
      <description>Looking for somewhere to go …. Maybe you need to waste some time or want to find something else to try on your Google Android G1 or HTC Magic.
Google obviously has embedded a lot things into the phone – but here are 2 apps that were not installed on the Android phone when you open the box.
Places DirectoryPrice FREE Downloads &amp;gt;250,000
updated — 21 Sept –– Even before augmented reality became a buzzword … Google Places Directory was already bringing Google Maps together with GPS / Location Based Services.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>