<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>writing on Damien Saunders</title>
    <link>http://damien.co/tags/writing/</link>
    <description>Recent content in writing on Damien Saunders</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2011 16:42:48 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://damien.co/tags/writing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Best stylus to use with your iPad? (part 1)</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/marketing-consultant-2/best-stylus-to-use-with-your-ipad-part-1-3755/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2011 16:42:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/marketing-consultant-2/best-stylus-to-use-with-your-ipad-part-1-3755/</guid>
      <description>I’ll start by saying I’m a gadget boy — any marketing consultant working on innovation or product delivery has got to know about gadgets. When I got my first iPad last year, I quickly realised that my finger tip was useless for writing. I’ve been collecting styli or styluses and starting to get a good collection.
I have been stopped plenty of times to be asked what’s my preferred tool and over the past 12 months, I’ve used quite a few and thrown out some immediately.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Switching to Scrivener for WordPress blogging</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/wordpress/switching-to-scrivener-for-wordpress-blogging-2901/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Apr 2011 12:28:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/wordpress/switching-to-scrivener-for-wordpress-blogging-2901/</guid>
      <description>I’ve just made the switch – or as we speak, I’m starting to learn about this ‘new’ tool for writers called Scrivener. Described as the app for writers, journalists and anyone that needs to write short or long stories, Scrivener collects together scraps of articles, research material and helps to draft your writing.
To me, the biggest problem with regular blogging is the interface. If you blog on the go then you already know that the WordPress admin suite is not very accessible when you’re in a plane, train or automobile.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Productivity Tip &amp;#8211; Technical Writing &amp;#038; the Writer&amp;#8217;s Block</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/2011-01-31-productivity-tip-technical-writing-the-writers-block/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jan 2011 09:45:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/2011-01-31-productivity-tip-technical-writing-the-writers-block/</guid>
      <description>Each week I set aside time to good writing, but its not the same when each day there are technical documents and scrum artefacts to be prepared. I can’t guarantee to get my writing done. It just doesn’t work like that. Good productive writingtakes time, space and zero distractions – even when its a business process or project brief.
Technical Writing &amp;amp; the Writers block You hear about those creative types in marketing, you may know a few entrepreneurs or inventors who have a spark of genius.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Productivity – Clear some time to get writing</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/2011-01-30-productivity-e28093-clear-some-time-to-get-writing/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jan 2011 17:00:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/2011-01-30-productivity-e28093-clear-some-time-to-get-writing/</guid>
      <description>For over a year now, Sunday has been my day to work. On Sundays, I’ve blocked out a few hours for the productive writing process. I’ve been a trained technical writer for more than 10 years now. I know I can write beautiful prose, except it’s the kind of prose worthy of legal contracts and business processes. Nowadays I’m trying to be more faithful to this skill and be creative in my writing.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>