<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>HTML5 on Damien Saunders</title>
    <link>https://damien.co/tags/html5/</link>
    <description>Recent content in HTML5 on Damien Saunders</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2012 11:30:49 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://damien.co/tags/html5/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>A couple more examples of impressive jQuery and JS</title>
      <link>https://damien.co/blog/couple-more-examples-of-impressive-js-jquery-5974/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2012 11:30:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien.co/blog/couple-more-examples-of-impressive-js-jquery-5974/</guid>
      <description>jQuery and Javascript may not be all that bad for you .. or your website.
Recently I’ve been looking into fluid and responsive layouts for web design and I’ve been using a jQuery framework called Isotope on my blog page.
Isotope looks like it can do magical things. If only I had the time to make it work properly.
So here are two more impressive examples of what you can do with .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Interactive] Dangermouse wants you to ro.me &amp;#8211; another great HTML5 music video</title>
      <link>https://damien.co/video/interactive-dangermouse-wants-you-to-ro-me-another-great-html5-music-video-3497/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2011 11:22:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien.co/video/interactive-dangermouse-wants-you-to-ro-me-another-great-html5-music-video-3497/</guid>
      <description>Music artist and producer Dangermouse has done it again – or that’s to say Google has done it with HTML5. The new album called Romeis in the style of a (spaghetti western) film soundtrack and if you’ve not hear it — then you’re missing out.
 HTML5 Music Video wow-ness  Google has again helped to create an interactive music video ‘Chrome Experiment’ – to show off some of the awesome-ness that is HTML5.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SEO best practice for using &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt; and &amp;lt;em&amp;gt;</title>
      <link>https://damien.co/social-media/seo-best-practice-for-using-strong-and-em-2695/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2011 09:42:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien.co/social-media/seo-best-practice-for-using-strong-and-em-2695/</guid>
      <description>As more people become aware of HTML5 it’s time to review how tagging written content will impact search engine optimisation. Tags like and are redundant – instead and have been in use for a few years by many blogging and web developer tools. Now the HTML5 standard recognises that and should only be used for visual style.
You can do more with CSS styles If you remember writing HTML back in the 90’s you might be more comfortable using and .</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>