<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>cause related marketing on Damien Saunders</title>
    <link>http://damien.co/tags/cause-related-marketing/</link>
    <description>Recent content in cause related marketing on Damien Saunders</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2010 09:52:10 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://damien.co/tags/cause-related-marketing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Cause Related Marketing &amp;amp; Social Media</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/social-media/cause-related-marketing-social-media-1921/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2010 09:52:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/social-media/cause-related-marketing-social-media-1921/</guid>
      <description>Yesterday was Remembrance Sunday in the UK. For a lot of people its more significant than the 2 minute silence on 11 November because they are out doing things related to their cause – remembering the ones who have gone before us, visiting relatives that are veterans or just being the Carer to someone who was injured during service.
This made me think about how social media marketing can play a part in cause related marketing and what I would do to support my cause.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>5 Essential tips for promoting your charity or cause using mobile marketing</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/2010-02-22-essential-tips-promotions-charities-mobile/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Feb 2010 07:44:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/2010-02-22-essential-tips-promotions-charities-mobile/</guid>
      <description>For non-profit organisations, charities and cause related marketing the mobile can provide the best integrated marketing solution for campaigns. There are a number of tools and techniques which can be used to promote your cause or help to raise donations.
1. SMS Premium Text Donations Making donations using your mobile is as simple as sending a text to a special number. For the not so concerned and the lazy its a quick way to send a few dollars, euros or pounds to a worthy cause.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>