<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>template on Damien Saunders</title>
    <link>http://damien.co/tags/template/</link>
    <description>Recent content in template on Damien Saunders</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2013 12:05:33 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://damien.co/tags/template/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Messing with your Head &amp;#8211; when to use WordPress template parts vs JavaScript</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/2013-09-26-messing-with-your-head-when-to-use-wordpress-template-parts-vs-javascript/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2013 12:05:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/2013-09-26-messing-with-your-head-when-to-use-wordpress-template-parts-vs-javascript/</guid>
      <description>Here I am … I&amp;rsquo;m messing with your head. I wanted to see how easy it is to get my Isotope Visual Layouts plugin for WordPress to change your your homepage. Actually it was too easy and the result is destruction and chaos.
No-No – I&amp;rsquo;m Never Going to Mess with your Head First thing to note – Never do anything with a plugin that &amp;lsquo;you&amp;rsquo; the User doesn&amp;rsquo;t expect. That&amp;rsquo;s bad bad karma.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Social Media &amp;amp; Internet Usage Policies for staff and contractors</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/social-media/social-media-internet-usage-policies-for-staff-and-contractors-1691/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Oct 2010 09:00:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/social-media/social-media-internet-usage-policies-for-staff-and-contractors-1691/</guid>
      <description>I recently answered a question on LinkedIn Answers about workplace policies for staff and contractors. Policies should cover acceptable internet &amp;amp; email usage, social media and also mobiles or other tools of trade.3 Policies every workplace should have for staff and new starters You should have policies for-
 social media policy to explain what people can do at work internet and email usage policy so staff know its ok to use email or internet Cellphone or mobile policy be clear about who pays for what  I think in a positive world, such policies should talk about trust and transparency – so the tone should be positive for example:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is a Social Media Policy</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/social-media/what-is-a-social-media-policy-1534/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Sep 2010 09:30:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/social-media/what-is-a-social-media-policy-1534/</guid>
      <description>Are you a fan of social media marketingand driving it for your business? When did you last stop to check that you were protected by your company social media policyor your employee policy allows you to access Facebook, YouTube or Twitter. In many cases, companies do not have a clear policy so the sharing of company information on social networks without the express permission of Marketing or PR could leave you in an iffy situation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why you need a social media policy</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/resources/why-you-need-a-social-media-policy-1654/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Sep 2010 09:00:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/resources/why-you-need-a-social-media-policy-1654/</guid>
      <description>Are you responsible for using Twitter at your office? Or maybe you started answering questions from customers on Facebook … if so you should check what your company policy on social media says.Why You Need a Social Media Policy &amp;amp; What should it cover You need a policy to protect yourself and your company – that policy needs to recognise that we all use social media &amp;amp; social networks every day.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>