<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>books on Damien Saunders</title>
    <link>http://damien.co/tags/books/</link>
    <description>Recent content in books on Damien Saunders</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2011 12:07:48 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://damien.co/tags/books/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The social media bible [book review]</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/social-media-marketing-2/the-social-media-bible-book-review-4666/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2011 12:07:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/social-media-marketing-2/the-social-media-bible-book-review-4666/</guid>
      <description>Social Media Marketing is a growing body of knowledge and everything about &amp;lsquo;it&amp;rsquo; is in a state of flux and changing rapidly, It’s unfair to call anything a bible. I doubt this book will be around in 2000 years – and it’s twice as fat as any bible you might see today.
Admirably, I agree with the authors intention – to collect a lot of (good) writing in one place … but the material in this book has aged already and which means the book is only worth it at a discounted rate or for anyone starting out with their own website or social media novice.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Required Summer Reading for startups &amp;#038; product development</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/required-summer-reading-for-startups-product-development-4263/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jul 2011 09:14:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/required-summer-reading-for-startups-product-development-4263/</guid>
      <description>If you&amp;rsquo;re about to head off for some sun - do pack these 2 books so you can say you seriously did some &amp;lsquo;work&amp;rsquo;.
Why Do I need to know these books? You need to know about current tools and the best practices as they are already appearing in many business plans, marketing strategy or new product definitions.
If you evaluate startups and are not getting a business model canvas then you should tell them to go re-write their business pan.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>