<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>DBC Backup 2 on Damien Saunders</title>
    <link>https://damien.co/tags/dbc-backup-2/</link>
    <description>Recent content in DBC Backup 2 on Damien Saunders</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2014 16:08:07 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://damien.co/tags/dbc-backup-2/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>DBC Backup 2 - minor update</title>
      <link>https://damien.co/blog/2014-01-05-dbc-backup-2-minor-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2014 16:08:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien.co/blog/2014-01-05-dbc-backup-2-minor-update/</guid>
      <description>DBC Backup 2 my WordPress plugin to safely backup your website has had a minor update.
DBC Backup 2 build 2.3.25 has just been published to the WordPress Plugin repository and you can update now.
Features / What&amp;rsquo;s New in DBC Backup 2 build 2.3.25 Fixes - a problem where the settings link didn&amp;rsquo;t work from the WordPress Installed Plugins page
New - help pulldown has been added to the plugin setting page.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DBC Backup 2  new version is ready for you</title>
      <link>https://damien.co/blog/2013-12-14-dbc-backup-2-new-version-ready/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2013 22:46:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien.co/blog/2013-12-14-dbc-backup-2-new-version-ready/</guid>
      <description>DBC Backup 2 is a WordPress plugin that creates backups of your database. DBC Backup 2 has just been update to v2.3.24.
DBC Backup 2 has been completely redesigned and looks great as part of WordPress 3.8.
What&amp;rsquo;s new in DBC Backup 2 The latest version of DBC Backup 2 includes a number of significant changes
 Support for PHP 5.x - resolves issue which required a manual work around / blocked importing backup files Support for MySQL 5.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DBC Backup 2 - v2.3 what&#39;s coming</title>
      <link>https://damien.co/blog/2013-10-17-dbc-backup-2-v2-3-whats-coming/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2013 23:48:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien.co/blog/2013-10-17-dbc-backup-2-v2-3-whats-coming/</guid>
      <description>The next version of DBC Backup 2 is just around the corner - I&amp;rsquo;ve held it back to better test the backup files and tinker with the admin panel.
So What&amp;rsquo;s in DBC Backup 2 v2.3? Key features of this version are
  Support for SQL server 5.5 and up
  Removes annoying debug log errors
  Transitions from mysql to mysqli
  Admin panel now has a default save location and creates a Backup folder inside WP-Content directory.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DBC Backup 2 - new version on the way updated for MySQL 5.6 and latest WordPress</title>
      <link>https://damien.co/blog/2013-10-12-dbc-backup-2-new-version-on-the-way-updated-for-mysql-5-6-and-latest-wordpress/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Oct 2013 23:04:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien.co/blog/2013-10-12-dbc-backup-2-new-version-on-the-way-updated-for-mysql-5-6-and-latest-wordpress/</guid>
      <description>DBC Backup 2 my WordPress plugin to safely back-up your database is getting an massive update. This will add support for the latest MySQL server version 5.6 and is currently in test.
DBC Backup 2 v2.3 is being tested with the latest versions of MySQL server and WordPress. It has been tested to ensure users can import and recover from their backup files.
 About DBC Backup 2
DBC Backup 2 is the WordPress plugin that you want behind the scenes - it safely and easily backs up your WordPress database, posts, settings and comments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DBC Backup 2 updated for WordPress 3.6</title>
      <link>https://damien.co/blog/2013-06-01-dbc-backup-2-updated-for-wordpress-3-6/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2013 13:32:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien.co/blog/2013-06-01-dbc-backup-2-updated-for-wordpress-3-6/</guid>
      <description>A new version of DBC Backup 2 my WordPress plugin to automatically backup your website has been released. This version has been tested to support WordPress 3.6 and is available to download now.
What&amp;rsquo;s new in DBC Backup 2 v2.2 Minor changes to the Settings Page for the plugin, that should make it easier to use.
FIXED - a few bugs
TESTED - on WordPress 3.6</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DBC Backup 2 updated to 2.1.1 it&amp;#8217;s a little bit harder Update Now</title>
      <link>https://damien.co/blog/2012-10-25-dbc-backup-2-updated-to-2-1-1-its-a-little-bit-harder-update-now/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Oct 2012 23:09:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien.co/blog/2012-10-25-dbc-backup-2-updated-to-2-1-1-its-a-little-bit-harder-update-now/</guid>
      <description>A new version of DBC Backup 2 has been released. I’m doing this to make life just a little bit harder. You should update to v2.1.1 as soon as possible please.
What’s in this release? This release looks to address a common security issue with WordPress and browsing folders like /wp-content etc.
I also recommend all users of my plugin and WordPress to check that their .htaccess file includes this 1 line (well 2 lines):</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thank you &amp;#8230; 2000&#43; downloads of DBC Backup 2 for WordPress</title>
      <link>https://damien.co/blog/2012-09-17-thank-you-2000-downloads-of-dbc-backup-2-for-wordpress/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Sep 2012 09:36:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien.co/blog/2012-09-17-thank-you-2000-downloads-of-dbc-backup-2-for-wordpress/</guid>
      <description>I want to say ‘Thank You’ to all of you who have downloaded and installed DBC Backup 2. Over the weekend, plugin downloads rose above 2000.
DBC Backup 2 makes it easy to safely backup your WordPress SQL database to a folder on your web server. It’s a unique solution which also includes regular, scheduled backups so that you can have a daily, weekly or monthly backup.
If you like DBC Backup 2 – please can you rate it 5 Stars on WordPress.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DBC Backup 2 &amp;#8211; gives the confidence that your WordPress database is backed-up and securely stored on your server [press release]</title>
      <link>https://damien.co/blog/2012-07-30-dbc-backup-2-gives-the-confidence-that-your-wordpress-database-is-backed-up-and-securely-stored-on-your-server-press-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jul 2012 14:01:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien.co/blog/2012-07-30-dbc-backup-2-gives-the-confidence-that-your-wordpress-database-is-backed-up-and-securely-stored-on-your-server-press-release/</guid>
      <description>DBC Backup 2 gives the confidence that your WordPress database is backed-up and securely stored on your server.
Database backup and security should be a critical issue for Marketing Agencies, small businesses and any WordPress website user. This plugin makes the whole experience easy with 3 critical features:
3 Critical Features   Storage – the backup file is compressed and saved on your web server and not sent via email or to another 3rdparty.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DBC Backup 2 &amp;#8211; WordPress database backup &amp;#8211; Here comes version 2.1</title>
      <link>https://damien.co/blog/2012-07-27-dbc-backup-2-wordpress-database-backup-here-comes-version-2-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jul 2012 16:30:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien.co/blog/2012-07-27-dbc-backup-2-wordpress-database-backup-here-comes-version-2-1/</guid>
      <description>DBC Backup 2for WordPress database backup has just been updated. The new version improves the user experience for managing the plugin as well as fixing minor bugs.
What is in the new release? 
The new release includes:
 A new admin page layout consistent with other WordPress plugins moves the link for DBC Backup to the Tools menu, again consistent with other plugins Fixes a problem where the user options where not deleted if the plugin was deleted Addresses a problem where users forgot to check the Active for the backup schedule Includes new options for social media sharing and getting help &amp;amp; support.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DBC Backup 2 &amp;#8211; sneak peak of the new version</title>
      <link>https://damien.co/blog/2012-07-21-dbc-backup-2-sneak-peak-of-the-new-version/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Jul 2012 15:36:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien.co/blog/2012-07-21-dbc-backup-2-sneak-peak-of-the-new-version/</guid>
      <description>I wanted to give you a sneak peak at DBC Backup 2 and changes which are coming in the next version. DBC Backup 2 is a simple and easy way to safely backup your WordPress SQL database and store it on your webserver.
DBC Backup 2 – purpose and niche I only recently ‘adopted’ this plugin for my own … and as much as I’d like to add features I don’t really want to change anything about it.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>