<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Rules for Social Media Marketing on Damien Saunders</title>
    <link>http://damien.co/tags/rules-for-social-media-marketing/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Rules for Social Media Marketing on Damien Saunders</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 21 Jun 2012 16:00:54 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://damien.co/tags/rules-for-social-media-marketing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Rule #2 &amp;#8211; Social Media Marketing &amp;#8211; Crucial for Sales &amp;#038; Marketing</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/social-media/rule-2-social-media-marketing-crucial-sales-marketing-7361/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jun 2012 16:00:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/social-media/rule-2-social-media-marketing-crucial-sales-marketing-7361/</guid>
      <description>Social Media marketing – using Twitter, Facebook, LinkedIn, Foursquare, Google+ … needs to form part of any marketing plan across the marketing mix. Do you really need a Digital Marketing Plan? And if your business needs a plan … why does it have to included social media?
Why Digital Marketing &amp;amp; Social Media? Every business – big, small, startup or established brand needs a digital marketing strategy. It’s crucial for your marketing and sales plan (even if you don’t have one) to include digital marketing and social media.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rule #1 &amp;#8211; Social Media Marketing &amp;#8211; don&amp;#8217;t leave it to PR or the intern</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/social-media/rule-1-social-media-marketing-dont-leave-pr-intern-7352/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jun 2012 14:30:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/social-media/rule-1-social-media-marketing-dont-leave-pr-intern-7352/</guid>
      <description>Social Media marketing – using Twitter, Facebook, LinkedIn, Foursquare, Google+ … needs to form part of any marketing plan across the marketing mix. Treating Social Media as a separate activity from the rest of your marketing is a No-No … In fact social media should be integrated into every campaign or promotion.
Digital marketing fits into new customer acquisition, customer retention, CRM, customer engagement and loyalty and anything else that customers do and thats true for D2C brands as well as B2B marketers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Social Media Marketing – Integrate with traditional marketing activities</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/social-media/social-media-marketing-integrate-with-traditional-marketing-activities-1312/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jul 2010 10:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/social-media/social-media-marketing-integrate-with-traditional-marketing-activities-1312/</guid>
      <description>Today’s marketing activities are changing – you can say old skool marketing is being overtaken by new skool ideas and techniques. _Social Media Marketing_ techniques mean you can integrate activities across the marketing mix and do it for ‘free’. Before you cut your budget for traditional marketing like PR, Direct Mail, Radio, Press, TV or Outdoor – STOP – Think about it and find out how to integrate your social media marketing into your traditional marketing channels and _take the conversation online_.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Social Media Marketing &amp;#8211; Integrate across the marketing mix</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/social-media/social-media-marketing-integrate-across-the-marketing-mix-1306/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jul 2010 10:00:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/social-media/social-media-marketing-integrate-across-the-marketing-mix-1306/</guid>
      <description>Social Media Marketing presents the opportunity to try a number of different social networks and promote or market in these as appropriate.Each social network has its own pro’s and con’s such as Twitter is more like a broadcast, one way radioand a Facebook fan page can create conversations that people can easily follow and read.
When you start out with social media marketing, the best sites to start with are:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Social Media Marketing Essential Collection to get started</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/social-media/social-media-marketing-essential-collection-1143/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jul 2010 09:40:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/social-media/social-media-marketing-essential-collection-1143/</guid>
      <description>Optimising for Social Media Marketingwill start to develop as a set of tools or addons to be used as part of a marketing promotion or campaign. If you’re just getting started with social media then you don’t need to optimise, you just need to start out with the right attitude and a good plan.Getting Started with Social Media Marketing In this first collection of articles, I’ve discussed 4 critical areas or rules:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Start a Social Media Marketing Plan – what do you want to achieve?</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/social-media/start-a-social-media-marketing-plan-what-do-you-want-to-achieve-1192/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jul 2010 09:43:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/social-media/start-a-social-media-marketing-plan-what-do-you-want-to-achieve-1192/</guid>
      <description>The start of any social media plan should actually be the end … by that I mean decide on the goals or what you want to achieve. Any good marcomm person or project planner will thank you for this. So what are good outcomes? what do you want to achieve? If you’re starting out in Social Media Marketing you’ll be wanting to get your ‘profile page’ or fan pages just right, get some friends and get some traction.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Start a Social Media Marketing Plan – write your plan</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/social-media/start-a-social-media-marketing-plan-write-your-plan-1124/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jul 2010 09:26:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/social-media/start-a-social-media-marketing-plan-write-your-plan-1124/</guid>
      <description>Start a Social Media Marketing Plan in writing … as we have all probably heard or read, putting even the vaguest plan down on paper will help to make your ideas concrete! The benefit of having a plan on paper means you can consider if your plan and goals are realistic and you can decide as well how involved you want to be in social media marketing.How to Write a Social Media Marketing Plan Your first social media marketing plan need only cover 4 areas:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Start a Social Media Marketing Plan – why you need to use social media?</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/social-media/start-a-social-media-marketing-plan-why-you-need-to-use-social-media-1119/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jul 2010 09:00:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/social-media/start-a-social-media-marketing-plan-why-you-need-to-use-social-media-1119/</guid>
      <description>Starting your plan for social media marketing in a small or big business should be driven by a need or a reason.
Why use Social Media – because your customers are using it! First step in your social media marketing plan is to open powerpoint or write on a flipchart the reason why you need to use social media, some good reasons include:
 most of our target audience use social media (no brainer), or because visits to your brand or company website are down as our customers spend more time on social media sites (better) to deliver a sales &amp;amp; marketing programme using online &amp;amp; social media  There are probably plenty of other good reasons you can think of.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Start a Social Media Marketing Plan – why social media?</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/social-media/start-a-social-media-marketing-plan-why-social-media-1113/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jul 2010 09:00:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/social-media/start-a-social-media-marketing-plan-why-social-media-1113/</guid>
      <description>Do you really need a Social Media Marketing Plan? And if your business needs a plan … why does it have to be social media?
Why Social Media Every business – big, small, startup or established brand needs to be using social media – yesterday. I was reading a flyer today which said ‘its critical for every website to include social media’ — its not the website that needs it … its your marketing and sales plan!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Start a Social Media Marketing Plan – don’t leave it to the PR person</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/social-media/start-a-social-media-marketing-plan-dont-leave-it-to-the-pr-person-1108/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jun 2010 09:00:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/social-media/start-a-social-media-marketing-plan-dont-leave-it-to-the-pr-person-1108/</guid>
      <description>Social Media marketing – using Twitter, Facebook, LinkedIn, Foursquare, Google+ … needs to form part of any marketing plan across the marketing mix. Treating Social Media as a separate activity from the rest of your marketing is a No-No … In fact social media should be integrated into every campaign or promotion.
Social Media marketing fits into new customer acquisition, customer retention, CRM, customer loyalty and anything else that customers do and thats true for D2C brands as well as B2B marketers.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>