<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Social Media Marketing on Damien Saunders</title>
    <link>https://damien.co/categories/social-media-marketing/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Social Media Marketing on Damien Saunders</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 19 Jun 2012 14:29:49 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://damien.co/categories/social-media-marketing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Best tools to start with Social Media Marketing &amp;#8211; 2011 re-cap (where are they now)</title>
      <link>https://damien.co/social-media-marketing-2/best-tools-to-start-with-social-media-marketing-2011-re-cap-where-are-they-now-7192/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jun 2012 14:29:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien.co/social-media-marketing-2/best-tools-to-start-with-social-media-marketing-2011-re-cap-where-are-they-now-7192/</guid>
      <description>[typography font=”Special Elite” size=”25″ size_format=”px”]If you’re just getting started with Social Media marketing then you need at least 1 web based tool to help you.[/typography]
__In 2011, I wrote a great article on the best tools to start with Social Media Marketing. A year later, things have changed, so I wanted to look back at my 2011 suggestions to see where they are now.
Keep track of your social media status and influence, albeit using Klout’s own scoring.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thinkup - Social Media Monitoring (made easier) tools</title>
      <link>https://damien.co/blog/2011-12-19-thinkup-social-media-monitoring-made-easier-tools/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Dec 2011 16:40:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien.co/blog/2011-12-19-thinkup-social-media-monitoring-made-easier-tools/</guid>
      <description>Thinkup - If you want to run your own social media monitoring tool then try this. I&amp;rsquo;ve just installed it, which takes a little bit of time and you need to know some a little bit of how to create your own mySQL databases. If you can&amp;rsquo;t afford to pay for tools - then ThinkUp creates the archive and monitoring you have to have.
Some great features include:
 downloads all your tweets, status updates, etc provides options to retweet, etc creates a visual report on followers, trends, etc deep integration with API&amp;rsquo;s for Twitter, Facebook &amp;amp; Google+ it&amp;rsquo;s free   Are you trying out tools for social media monitoring and analytics?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The social media bible [book review]</title>
      <link>https://damien.co/social-media-marketing-2/the-social-media-bible-book-review-4666/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2011 12:07:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien.co/social-media-marketing-2/the-social-media-bible-book-review-4666/</guid>
      <description>Social Media Marketing is a growing body of knowledge and everything about ‘it’ is in a state of flux and changing rapidly, It’s unfair to call anything a bible. I doubt this book will be around in 2000 years – and it’s twice as fat as any bible you might see today.
Admirably, I agree with the authors intention – to collect a lot of (good) writing in one place … but the material in this book has aged already and which means the book is only worth it at a discounted rate or for anyone starting out with their own website or social media novice.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>