<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>appstore on Damien Saunders</title>
    <link>https://damien.co/tags/appstore/</link>
    <description>Recent content in appstore on Damien Saunders</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 Apr 2011 08:03:21 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://damien.co/tags/appstore/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>A Marketing Consultants Guide to Business Class Apps for iPad</title>
      <link>https://damien.co/marketing-consultant-2/a-marketing-consultants-guide-to-business-class-apps-for-ipad-2853/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Apr 2011 08:03:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien.co/marketing-consultant-2/a-marketing-consultants-guide-to-business-class-apps-for-ipad-2853/</guid>
      <description>If you haven’t got an iPad or still not convinced you’ll need one – then you’re kidding yourself. As a marketing consultant new gadgets like the iPad need to be purchased, used extensively and then replaced with the next new shiny gadget. Why – you might ask? Because how else can you have an opinion or recommend a solution to your clients.
Today – I’m taking a quick look at the list of apps featured in iTunes under the category ‘business class’.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Say hello to 10,000,000,000 little downloads of mobile apps</title>
      <link>https://damien.co/mobile-marketing/say-hello-to-10000000-little-downloads-of-mobile-apps-2577/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jan 2011 22:47:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien.co/mobile-marketing/say-hello-to-10000000-little-downloads-of-mobile-apps-2577/</guid>
      <description>It was only earlier this week that Apple’s homepage changed to advertise the fact that a 10 billion milestone was soon to be reached.
It wouldn’t be insane to think that 10 billion app downloads is a milestone and a half – no other app store or mobile operator portal has reported such impressive download figures.
In other recent news e-marketer reckoned that we all had a collective average of 60 of these apps on our smartphones — that’s a lot of games, news, branded content and generally important little bits of code on our phones.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apple Mac App Store initially I was dubious</title>
      <link>https://damien.co/blog/insights-blog/apple-mac-app-store-initially-i-was-dubious-2529/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2011 09:50:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien.co/blog/insights-blog/apple-mac-app-store-initially-i-was-dubious-2529/</guid>
      <description>Initially I was dubious or even skeptical about the new Apple Mac App Store – and everyone from Mashableto ReadWriteWebto Download Squadhave already done a post about first thoughts or white washed the Apple PR news item.
Things that are surprising in the Mac App Store I was surprised to find this week that Mobile App Developers are using this as the opportunity to port their Apps off of the phone to the desktop.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apple Mac App Store an imperfect tool for small apps developers?</title>
      <link>https://damien.co/startup/apple-mac-app-store-an-imperfect-tool-for-small-apps-developers-2481/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2011 10:26:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien.co/startup/apple-mac-app-store-an-imperfect-tool-for-small-apps-developers-2481/</guid>
      <description>Apple’s new Mac App Store arrives on January 6 and it could be the perfect tool for small app developers and a welcome boost in hybrid web-app startups. That said — Does your business or client want their marketing and product development strategy to be led by Apple’s App Store?
Mac App Store key features for Users Customers of the Mac App Store (eg anyone owning a Mac) will think this is a really useful new system tool.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Does building an iPhone App make cents? sense?</title>
      <link>https://damien.co/general/does-building-an-iphone-make-cents-sense-348/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Nov 2009 19:36:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien.co/general/does-building-an-iphone-make-cents-sense-348/</guid>
      <description>With the boom in the number of apps in the App Store (over 100,000) and total downloads in excess of 2bn … someone has got to be making money … right?In part, the iPhone does offer a better platform for apps – it’s about to overtake RIM as the leading consumer smartphone, sold more than 34 million units and got some of the highest mobile internet usage rates we’ve seen so far.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>