<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>reformatted-my-mac-day on Damien Saunders</title>
    <link>http://damien.co/tags/reformatted-my-mac-day/</link>
    <description>Recent content in reformatted-my-mac-day on Damien Saunders</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 21 Apr 2013 15:29:03 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://damien.co/tags/reformatted-my-mac-day/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Things to do post format with a dual partition Mac OSx #reformatted-my-mac</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/things-to-do-post-format-with-a-dual-partition-mac-osx-reformatted-my-mac-8655/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Apr 2013 15:29:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/things-to-do-post-format-with-a-dual-partition-mac-osx-reformatted-my-mac-8655/</guid>
      <description>So I had to do, what I had to do! and reformatted my Mac and now … I&amp;rsquo;m getting up in running again. I&amp;rsquo;ve been using Mac for a few years now and before that I&amp;rsquo;ve been used to running partitioned hard drives - it saves time when you reformat and usually means (touch wood) you can keep your user data safe from your OS.
 Critical Apps to Install and get up in running in no time  Immediately after logging in for the first time — I did the following …</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Time for a service - #reformated-my-mac-day</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/time-for-a-service-reformated-my-mac-day-8439/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2013 17:33:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/time-for-a-service-reformated-my-mac-day-8439/</guid>
      <description>Reformatting a computer is usually an emotionally distressful activity - involving losing files, trying to find software discs and panic about lost licence codes.
Over the years, I&amp;rsquo;ve reformatted and deleted many computers - kind of like giving your computer a semi annual service. As a result of noticing something not running right .. it just has to be done.
Today&amp;rsquo;s reformat went faster then I expected.
Reformat your Apple Mac and reinstall OSx operating system Once you are happy that you have moved all the files you think you want to keep … All you do is:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I feel like a kid in a candy shop &amp;#8230; #reformatted-my-mac-day</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/i-feel-like-a-kid-in-a-candy-shop-reformatted-my-mac-day-8433/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2013 12:19:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/i-feel-like-a-kid-in-a-candy-shop-reformatted-my-mac-day-8433/</guid>
      <description>I woke up this morning .. it&amp;rsquo;s pouring with rain … my Apple MacBook Pro decides it doesn&amp;rsquo;t want to connect to my wifi.
So I had to do, what I had to do! and reformatted my Mac.
Now … I&amp;rsquo;m getting up in running again.
First things first ..
 Update my user preferences and move my home folder to the second partition (done) Download and Install Chrome (done) Download and Install Dropbox - point to my Dropbox folder on the other partition Download and install 1Password (done)  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>