<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>mobile search on Damien Saunders</title>
    <link>http://damien.co/tags/mobile-search/</link>
    <description>Recent content in mobile search on Damien Saunders</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 May 2010 08:00:57 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://damien.co/tags/mobile-search/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>HOW TO: Google Maps Local claim your business</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/2010-05-12-how-to-google-maps-local-claim-your-business/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 May 2010 08:00:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/2010-05-12-how-to-google-maps-local-claim-your-business/</guid>
      <description>Google Maps is the first site that any business should visit before starting mobile or geospecific marketing. Google Maps Local provides a range of tools to make it easy for anyone to check their details and claim your business.
Why do you need to claim your business on Google Maps? We all know the phenomenon that is searching for something on Google from a Mobile - so as more people have Androidphones or iPhones or other smartphones, more people will use Mobile Internet for Search.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mobile SEO - Google extends click to call to mobile search</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/2010-02-08-mobile-seo-google-extends-click-to-call-to-mobile-search/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Feb 2010 09:11:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/2010-02-08-mobile-seo-google-extends-click-to-call-to-mobile-search/</guid>
      <description>In the next couple of weeks, I&amp;rsquo;ll be looking closely at Mobile Search and Mobile SEO. This week will be a round up of features on Google Mobile Search
Click to Call
Click to call has been a feature of WAP and mobile portals for sometime, however the mobile phones needed to support this action.
Google has now added Click to Call to Adword Mobile Search Results
Anyone running SEO or Adword campaigns should make sure they have configured the mobile search results as well and to now include the primary phone number for customers or clients to ring in on.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>