<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>strategy on Damien Saunders</title>
    <link>http://damien.co/tags/strategy/</link>
    <description>Recent content in strategy on Damien Saunders</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Jun 2012 14:30:58 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://damien.co/tags/strategy/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Rule 1 - Social Media Marketing - don&#39;t leave it to PR or the intern</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/2012-06-20-rule-1-social-media-marketing-dont-leave-pr-intern/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jun 2012 14:30:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/2012-06-20-rule-1-social-media-marketing-dont-leave-pr-intern/</guid>
      <description>Social Media marketing - using Twitter, Facebook, LinkedIn, Foursquare, Google+ … needs to form part of any marketing plan across the marketing mix. Treating Social Media as a separate activity from the rest of your marketing is a No-No … In fact social media should be integrated into every campaign or promotion.
Digital marketing fits into new customer acquisition, customer retention, CRM, customer engagement and loyalty and anything else that customers do and thats true for D2C brands as well as B2B marketers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>41 things to do in 41 days to boost your digital marketing</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/marketing-consultant-2/41-things-to-do-in-41-days-to-boost-your-digital-marketing-7161/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Jun 2012 18:47:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/marketing-consultant-2/41-things-to-do-in-41-days-to-boost-your-digital-marketing-7161/</guid>
      <description>[typography font=”Special Elite” size=”25″ size_format=”px”]Want a quick head start to a digital marketing plan for your brand or business? Here are 41 things you can do … over 41 days.[/typography]
Allow an hour a day (and a bit extra at the end of the week to see how you&amp;rsquo;re progressing).
 Create an account on Twitter for you and your brand - find some friends to follow Create an account on Facebook Create a social media analytics account on MarketMeSuite to monitor your fans and followers Create a Google Alert to track online mentions of your brand Create a Google Alert for mentions of your product Create a Google Alert for mentions of your competitors Create a Google Alert for mentions of you Find out what Web Analytics Tools you use like Google Analytics &amp;amp; Bit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3 articles to read on Brand Marketing &amp;#038; Strategy</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/3-articles-read-brand-marketing-strategy-7318/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Jun 2012 17:19:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/3-articles-read-brand-marketing-strategy-7318/</guid>
      <description>You&amp;rsquo;ll love these 3 articles by Mark Ritson who has a weekly opinion piece in Marketing Week. His column is the inside, back page and the first article I read.
Why Graff Diamonds Failed to list on the Hong Kong Stock Exchange (old school luxury brand)
Link &amp;gt; Marketing Week— is this not the same trap for other FTSE100 and multinationals? becoming old-fashioned and lacking brand appeal
Apple’s leadership bios look about as diverse as an Alabama country club circa 1961</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Axure - workflow for business process &amp;#038; web applications</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/customer-experience-2/axure/axure-workflow-for-business-process-web-applications-7055/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 May 2012 13:05:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/customer-experience-2/axure/axure-workflow-for-business-process-web-applications-7055/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s pretty easy to jump in the deep end with Axure and start building wireframes and hi-fi clickable prototypes. But the joy of Axure is starting low-fi (use Post-It Notes) to map a user journey and then create this process flow in Axure. Following a workflow like this means you get the customer journey mapped and you easily link your Axure wireframes to business processes.
I&amp;rsquo;ve been using Axure for more than a year and it&amp;rsquo;s now my tool of choice for mapping customer journeys and user interaction design.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Required Summer Reading for startups &amp;#038; product development</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/required-summer-reading-for-startups-product-development-4263/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jul 2011 09:14:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/required-summer-reading-for-startups-product-development-4263/</guid>
      <description>If you&amp;rsquo;re about to head off for some sun - do pack these 2 books so you can say you seriously did some &amp;lsquo;work&amp;rsquo;.
Why Do I need to know these books? You need to know about current tools and the best practices as they are already appearing in many business plans, marketing strategy or new product definitions.
If you evaluate startups and are not getting a business model canvas then you should tell them to go re-write their business pan.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Starting in Digital? Don&#39;t ruin your brand reputation with your 1st social media marketing campaign</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/social-media/starting-in-digital-dont-ruin-your-brand-reputation-with-your-1st-social-media-marketing-campaign-3917/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2011 14:40:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/social-media/starting-in-digital-dont-ruin-your-brand-reputation-with-your-1st-social-media-marketing-campaign-3917/</guid>
      <description>Digital marketing has its benefits mainly that it’s easy to launch a social media campaign without any prior relationship with the victim.
I’m more annoyed at the damage young companies do to their brand, reputation and domain-name … at wasted opportunities from legitimate startups who just spam any contacts in one e-mail blast.
Last week, I got an email sent to me with someone elses info - yet it was an invite to join their London business network.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Management lessons we can learn from films - TRON</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/startup/management-lessons-we-can-learn-from-films-tron-3123/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 May 2011 11:08:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/startup/management-lessons-we-can-learn-from-films-tron-3123/</guid>
      <description>TRONis still a superb film, I was too young when it was first issued, but watching it recently started me thinking about business strategy and business models for startups.
In basic sociology, we learn that society is reflected in films and films are (then) reflected back in society. What this means is that you can analyse a film to learn about (business) culture from that time and look to see if any stereotypes are carried forward into reality.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Are you on top of your Social Media Marketing Strategy for 2011?</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/strategy/are-you-on-top-of-your-social-media-marketing-strategy-for-2011-3125/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2011 11:16:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/strategy/are-you-on-top-of-your-social-media-marketing-strategy-for-2011-3125/</guid>
      <description>You&amp;rsquo;re never too late to start your 2011 Social Media Marketing Strategy - This year has gone so fast and I missed starting my Marketing Strategy on 1/1/11. For many marketing people and businesses, developing your strategy is something usually done in the first 3 months of your financial year or calendar year.
If this is the approach your business currently takes, then realise that you&amp;rsquo;re leaving just 75% of the year to deliver 100% of what you set out to achieve.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apple Mac App Store an imperfect tool for small apps developers?</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/startup/apple-mac-app-store-an-imperfect-tool-for-small-apps-developers-2481/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2011 10:26:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/startup/apple-mac-app-store-an-imperfect-tool-for-small-apps-developers-2481/</guid>
      <description>Apple&amp;rsquo;s new Mac App Store arrives on January 6 and it could be the perfect tool for small app developers and a welcome boost in hybrid web-app startups. That said — Does your business or client want their marketing and product development strategy to be led by Apple&amp;rsquo;s App Store?
Mac App Store key features for Users Customers of the Mac App Store (eg anyone owning a Mac) will think this is a really useful new system tool.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>