<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Insights on Damien Saunders</title>
    <link>http://damien.co/categories/insights/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Insights on Damien Saunders</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Jun 2012 14:22:59 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://damien.co/categories/insights/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Social Gaming is on the decline? Blame cannibalisation by mobile and OTT</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/insights-blog/why-social-gaming-decline-blame-cannibalisation-mobile-ott-7316/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jun 2012 14:22:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/insights-blog/why-social-gaming-decline-blame-cannibalisation-mobile-ott-7316/</guid>
      <description>Social Gaming is on the decline – not terminal decline, just platform cannibalisation. Well mostly. Some Social Gamers just go off and play other newer games. The big reason for the decline in social game, I believe is the rise of free games in App Stores like Android Play and iTunes App Store. These App Stores provide a direct to user channel for promotion of games.
5 reasons Social Gaming is on the decline There are 5 reasons this is happening</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Digital Project Management Quality, Quantity Time [humour]</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/2012-05-28-digital-project-management-quality-quantity-time-humour/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 May 2012 10:57:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/2012-05-28-digital-project-management-quality-quantity-time-humour/</guid>
      <description>In all honesty – project management planning should include this as a standard assessment tool …
 Are you trying to run your project too fast without changing scope? Are you expecting your team to deliver too much? Are you cutting corners and the client still expects a great job?  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rackspace &amp;#8211; you wish for simplicity &amp;#8211; what you get is simply choice</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/insights-blog/rackspace-you-wish-for-simplicity-what-you-get-is-simply-choice-5258/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Dec 2011 09:11:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/insights-blog/rackspace-you-wish-for-simplicity-what-you-get-is-simply-choice-5258/</guid>
      <description>Everyone I talk to in digital marketing and everyone who wants to be a technical expert has an opinion on Rackspace. In reality, when it comes to virtualisation, hosting servers, scalability and choice, the price you pay to Rackspace can be significantly less then you pay to other providers.
But at what cost? It seems that freedom is the price you pay and freedom to choose is confusing.
1p per hour for a server is a problem The problem with Rackspace is the pricing model.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Comments are Free</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/insights-blog/comments-are-free-3585/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2011 18:35:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/insights-blog/comments-are-free-3585/</guid>
      <description>With any successful blog, Comments and Spam are juxtaposed at opposite ends of the spectrum. We all want to engage and generate conversations. The change in SEO practices means spam is being replaced by inbound link baiting.
Akismet the only rubber you need In WordPress – part of the battle is won by using the free Akismet plugin which is developed and maintained by Automattic (the ‘commercial arm’ of WordPress.com etc).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Every Important Stat can be drawn in a 2&amp;#215;2 Grid</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/insights-blog/every-important-stat-can-be-drawn-in-a-2x2-grid-2800/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Mar 2011 09:10:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/insights-blog/every-important-stat-can-be-drawn-in-a-2x2-grid-2800/</guid>
      <description>Nolan Chart - XKCD
Just to prove a point – the 2×2 grid is the best way to show-off pretty much interesting statistic or insight</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gartner predicts App Store Revenue Forecast to Surpass $15 Billion in 2011</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/insights-blog/gartner-predicts-app-store-revenue-forecast-to-surpass-15-billion-in-2011-2656/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2011 07:53:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/insights-blog/gartner-predicts-app-store-revenue-forecast-to-surpass-15-billion-in-2011-2656/</guid>
      <description>I’ve been on the lookout for this prediction … in 2010 Gartner predicted Worldwide Mobile App Revenues of xx Billion … for 2011 the prediction is for this to exceed $15 billion
2010 Where are the results! Given that Apple, Android, RIM, Nokia and a whole stack of operators and 3rd parties run mobile app stores – it’s extremely difficult to find out how good Gartner is at forecasts. Or is this just a large number guestimate?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apple Mac App Store initially I was dubious</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/insights-blog/apple-mac-app-store-initially-i-was-dubious-2529/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2011 09:50:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/insights-blog/apple-mac-app-store-initially-i-was-dubious-2529/</guid>
      <description>Initially I was dubious or even skeptical about the new Apple Mac App Store – and everyone from Mashableto ReadWriteWebto Download Squadhave already done a post about first thoughts or white washed the Apple PR news item.
Things that are surprising in the Mac App Store I was surprised to find this week that Mobile App Developers are using this as the opportunity to port their Apps off of the phone to the desktop.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>