<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Social Media on Damien Saunders</title>
    <link>http://damien.co/tags/social-media/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Social Media on Damien Saunders</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2013 16:44:08 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://damien.co/tags/social-media/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Death of Google Reader - It&#39;s offline caching that makes RSS so good for me</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/death-of-google-reader-its-offline-caching-that-makes-rss-so-good-for-me-8448/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2013 16:44:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/death-of-google-reader-its-offline-caching-that-makes-rss-so-good-for-me-8448/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s what&amp;rsquo;s on the inside that counts! For me, what makes RSS a success has been mobile apps with offline caching. I don&amp;rsquo;t sit at home with my browser pointed to reader.google.com … I use mobile apps. Specifically, as I spend a lot of time on London Tube and trains where there is no wifi or mobile coverage, I need an RSS Feed Reader with a Cache!
It&amp;rsquo;s been great over the years to have Google Reader there for me as a bit of a research index, record keeper and generally more reliable than Delicious or pretty much any social bookmarking service.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WP to Buffer (Twitter Sharing) - WordPress Plugins</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/2012-10-24-wp-to-buffer-twitter-sharing-wordpress-plugins/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Oct 2012 13:17:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/2012-10-24-wp-to-buffer-twitter-sharing-wordpress-plugins/</guid>
      <description>“WP to Buffer is a plugin for WordPress that sends updates to your Buffer (bufferapp.com) account for scheduled publishing to social networks when you publish and/or update WordPress Pages, Posts and/or Custom Post Types.”
— Now I like Buffer a lot … I use it mostly via Twitter to &amp;lsquo;Buffer&amp;rsquo; my tweets at different times of the day.
If you don&amp;rsquo;t already have a plugin to send your scheduled posts to Twitter then here&amp;rsquo;s a plugin to try that will send them to your Buffer queue.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting Twitter URLs right with Bit.ly Shortlinks by Yoast</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/2012-10-10-getting-twitter-urls-right-with-bit-ly/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Oct 2012 15:13:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/2012-10-10-getting-twitter-urls-right-with-bit-ly/</guid>
      <description>Integrating Twitter with WordPress is pretty easy to do without a plugin. With a few lines of code you can have a nice tweet this or follow me button on every post or page of your WordPress website.
However, the URL that is part of the Tweet is the permalink URL and for many sites you&amp;rsquo;ll want to Tweet a shortened URL. If like me, using Bit.ly and Yoast&amp;rsquo;s Bitly Shortlink plugin, you maybe wondering how to get your short Bit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rule #2 - Social Media Marketing - Crucial for Sales &amp;#038; Marketing</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/social-media/rule-2-social-media-marketing-crucial-sales-marketing-7361/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jun 2012 16:00:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/social-media/rule-2-social-media-marketing-crucial-sales-marketing-7361/</guid>
      <description>Social Media marketing - using Twitter, Facebook, LinkedIn, Foursquare, Google+ … needs to form part of any marketing plan across the marketing mix. Do you really need a Digital Marketing Plan? And if your business needs a plan … why does it have to included social media?
Why Digital Marketing &amp;amp; Social Media? Every business - big, small, startup or established brand needs a digital marketing strategy. It&amp;rsquo;s crucial for your marketing and sales plan (even if you don&amp;rsquo;t have one) to include digital marketing and social media.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rule 1 - Social Media Marketing - don&#39;t leave it to PR or the intern</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/2012-06-20-rule-1-social-media-marketing-dont-leave-pr-intern/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jun 2012 14:30:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/2012-06-20-rule-1-social-media-marketing-dont-leave-pr-intern/</guid>
      <description>Social Media marketing - using Twitter, Facebook, LinkedIn, Foursquare, Google+ … needs to form part of any marketing plan across the marketing mix. Treating Social Media as a separate activity from the rest of your marketing is a No-No … In fact social media should be integrated into every campaign or promotion.
Digital marketing fits into new customer acquisition, customer retention, CRM, customer engagement and loyalty and anything else that customers do and thats true for D2C brands as well as B2B marketers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Twitter a few suggested alternatives to CoTweet or Hootsuite</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/2012-04-13-twitter-a-few-suggested-alternatives-to-cotweet-or-hootsuite/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Apr 2012 12:53:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/2012-04-13-twitter-a-few-suggested-alternatives-to-cotweet-or-hootsuite/</guid>
      <description>Are you responsible for Twitter and Social Media in your business? Perhaps you&amp;rsquo;ve been feeling a bit lost after CoTweet closed its free version (shame on them) … here are a few alternatives you can look at
HootSuite
 yes I said alternative to CoTweet - personally, I like to use my own bit.ly Pro URL so this was not an option. Hootsuitehas a very reasonably priced premium version and it has clients for pretty much any device  MarketMeSuite</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>5 tips to using Foursquare for retail marketing</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/social-media/foursquare/5-tips-to-using-foursquare-for-retail-marketing-1408/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Nov 2011 09:00:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/social-media/foursquare/5-tips-to-using-foursquare-for-retail-marketing-1408/</guid>
      <description>Are you using Foursquare? Do you want your retail storesor promotions staff to start to use Foursquare too? If you already use social media marketing, then approx 15% of business are already using Foursquare</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to start mobile marketing with Foursquare [presentation]</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/social-media/foursquare/how-to-start-mobile-marketing-with-foursquare-presentation-4942/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Nov 2011 09:45:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/social-media/foursquare/how-to-start-mobile-marketing-with-foursquare-presentation-4942/</guid>
      <description>Mobile marketing and Foursquare are two words that are just right for each other. Foursquare has an impressive base of users and is extremely popular in big cities like London - which means it&amp;rsquo;s ideal for any business or brand to get started with mobile marketing and hyper-local search.
Focus your marketing on mobile - integrate offline with online Now that mobile marketing is becoming the focus of all your online marketing activities (if not, why not?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HOW TO use Twitter for your startup</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/startup/how-to-use-twitter-for-your-startup-2-1069/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2011 09:40:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/startup/how-to-use-twitter-for-your-startup-2-1069/</guid>
      <description>Twitter is a very powerful tool for any startup and I believe it is the first social network any would be entrepreneur needs to setup when launching their new business. The worst mistake any startup marketer will make is just tweeting “Hello World” without a plan.
Make your Twitter Marketing Plan Any startup sales &amp;amp; marketing plan or marcomms plan needs to make the most of the 4 P&amp;rsquo;s - product place price promotion.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Members Get it Free - Definitive Guide to Foursquare for 2011</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/2011-07-25-members-get-it-free-definitive-guide-to-foursquare-for-2011/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jul 2011 22:18:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/2011-07-25-members-get-it-free-definitive-guide-to-foursquare-for-2011/</guid>
      <description>The Definitive Guide to Foursquare has been updated for 2011 … and will be sent out this week. This guide contains all you need to know to get started with marketing using Foursquare. It covers:
 Statistics you need to know Ideas for making your business marketing with Foursquare better What key incentives you should have to reward Mayors Tips for tracking and monitoring much much more …  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WordPress 3.2 Release Candidate is here</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/2011-06-27-wordpress-3-2-release-candidate-is-here-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jun 2011 19:10:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/2011-06-27-wordpress-3-2-release-candidate-is-here-2/</guid>
      <description>The second release candidate for the next version of WordPress 3.2 is here. If you haven&amp;rsquo;t started testing 3.2, now is the time. Previous experience would make this the final RC before the real deal.
 Should I update to this release candidate? As this is a release candidate you shouldn&amp;rsquo;t use this on a really important live site - but it does mean it&amp;rsquo;s pretty stable and useful. You should find that most popular plugins and themes have no issues as developers have been working since RC1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>20 very recent Social Media articles for you</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/social-media/20-very-recent-social-media-articles-for-you-3965/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jun 2011 11:34:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/social-media/20-very-recent-social-media-articles-for-you-3965/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s time to catchup on some missed out reading and get out in the sun. So here is a collection of 10 of the best social media resources for you to read.
So I&amp;rsquo;m not going to second guess these related posts - I&amp;rsquo;m sure there will be stuff about Emailvision, Facebook, brand reputation and cross channel marketing.
[related_posts limit=”20″] SPECIAL PROMO ALERT -  Ever feel that social media &amp;amp; online marketing is too difficult for you?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Emailvision – it&#39;s great to feel engaged</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/social-media/emailvision-%e2%80%93-its-great-to-feel-engaged-3977/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2011 11:10:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/social-media/emailvision-%e2%80%93-its-great-to-feel-engaged-3977/</guid>
      <description>The team at Emailvision have contacted me a lot in the past 3 days … since I wrote a short article on cross channel campaign problems and a lack of testing.
I will say that Emailvision team that I have spoken to have all been great - it&amp;rsquo;s good to know they switched on people who are passionate about their company and what they do.
 The problem with integrated cross-channel marketing is … James from Emailvision resolved / pointed out a few things -</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WordPress 3.2 Release Candidate is here</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/wordpress/wordpress-3-2-release-candidate-is-here-3961/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jun 2011 15:44:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/wordpress/wordpress-3-2-release-candidate-is-here-3961/</guid>
      <description>The first release candidate for the next version of WordPress 3.2 is here.
Should I update to this release candidate? As this is a release candidate you shouldn&amp;rsquo;t use this on a really important live site - but it does mean it&amp;rsquo;s pretty stable and useful. You may find that you have issues with plugins and themes as developers work to support this RC.
 WordPress 3.2 what you can expect WordPress 3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Are you following me ( on Twitter )</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/promo/follow-me-on-facebook-3117/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 May 2011 13:33:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/promo/follow-me-on-facebook-3117/</guid>
      <description>Did you know that social media is more than just blogs and RSS feeds? Well I hope so.
I have a following on Twitter that is &amp;lt;— this BIG —&amp;gt; which is a lot for little ol&amp;rsquo; me. Maybe you prefer Twitter because you can dip in to the Twitterstream - maybe you should try following me.
What does Damien Saunders have to share on Twitter? Damien&amp;rsquo;s Twitter account is kept updated 24/7 with the latest headlines from across my Internet websites.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Are you on top of your Social Media Marketing Strategy for 2011?</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/strategy/are-you-on-top-of-your-social-media-marketing-strategy-for-2011-3125/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2011 11:16:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/strategy/are-you-on-top-of-your-social-media-marketing-strategy-for-2011-3125/</guid>
      <description>You&amp;rsquo;re never too late to start your 2011 Social Media Marketing Strategy - This year has gone so fast and I missed starting my Marketing Strategy on 1/1/11. For many marketing people and businesses, developing your strategy is something usually done in the first 3 months of your financial year or calendar year.
If this is the approach your business currently takes, then realise that you&amp;rsquo;re leaving just 75% of the year to deliver 100% of what you set out to achieve.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You can like me on Facebook too</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/promo/you-can-like-me-on-facebook-too-3121/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 May 2011 13:46:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/promo/you-can-like-me-on-facebook-too-3121/</guid>
      <description>Did you know that social media is more than just blogs and RSS feeds?
If you’ve heard of Facebook - you might like to know that I have a fan page - so if you can like my page that would be great.
By liking me — you’ll have daily updates from the latest news and stuff that is published on my website and you&amp;rsquo;ll be letting me know how much you like Facebook.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What&#39;s it like being a social media consultant [humour]</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/social-media/whats-it-like-being-a-social-media-consultant-humour-2798/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Mar 2011 12:51:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/social-media/whats-it-like-being-a-social-media-consultant-humour-2798/</guid>
      <description>Social Media Marketing Consultant Time Management humour</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best WordPress plugins for social media marketing</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/wordpress/best-wordpress-plugins-for-social-media-marketing-2319/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jan 2011 09:20:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/wordpress/best-wordpress-plugins-for-social-media-marketing-2319/</guid>
      <description>Social Media Marketing plugins for WordPress - you only need a few to have a powerful integrated marketing website.
WordPress plugins there are millions(?) to choose from and they are so easy to install. I tend to be cutting edge and change my plugins often, but here are some of the best plugins to improve WordPress for social media and digital marketing.
The point here is that writing original content can be easy - but your great works need to be found.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ideas using Foursquare for Cafes &amp;amp; Restaurants</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/social-media/foursquare/ideas-using-foursquare-for-cafes-restaurants-2237/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Dec 2010 09:22:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/social-media/foursquare/ideas-using-foursquare-for-cafes-restaurants-2237/</guid>
      <description>To market to market to buy me a Foursquare… for Cafes &amp;amp; Restaurants it’s the time of the year when your customers maybe thinking of Christmas comforts to have at home so get them in your store now. Last week I started a new series focused on Ideas using Foursquarefor social media marketing with guides that will help increase customer satisfaction and improve retention. Today, will be looking at how can use social media marketing to offer some tasty food tidbits that leave your customers wanting to come back for seconds.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ideas using Foursquare for Retailers and Stores</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/social-media/foursquare/ideas-using-foursquare-for-retailers-and-stores-2231/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Dec 2010 09:07:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/social-media/foursquare/ideas-using-foursquare-for-retailers-and-stores-2231/</guid>
      <description>To market to market to buy me a Foursquare … It’s that time of the year and retailers are trying hard to get shoppers in store and away from the weather outside. This week I start a new series focused on Ideas using Foursquarefor social media marketing with guides that will help increase customer satisfaction and improve retention.Today, I will be looking at how Retailers can use social media to offer up some pretty amazing shopping experiences that will leave your shoppers and clients loving you more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Social Media News this morning November 24, 2010</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/news-releases/social-media-news-this-morning-november-24-2010-2068/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Nov 2010 08:01:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/news-releases/social-media-news-this-morning-november-24-2010-2068/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to choose a good social media marketing consultant</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/2010-11-23-how-to-choose-a-good-social-media-marketing-consultant/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Nov 2010 09:41:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/2010-11-23-how-to-choose-a-good-social-media-marketing-consultant/</guid>
      <description>Social media marketingis no longer a buzzword and many brands and businesses are choosing to recruit full-time staff to develop and deliver the quicksilver successesof the best viral campaigns.What&amp;rsquo;s the difference between a social media consultant, digital planner &amp;amp; a community manager? If you are looking for an independent social media strategist to come in as a consultant or freelance gig then you need to know why a social media marketing consultant is very different to a digital planner or community manager.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Social Media News this morning November 22, 2010</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/news-releases/social-media-news-this-morning-november-22-2010-1998/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Nov 2010 08:01:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/news-releases/social-media-news-this-morning-november-22-2010-1998/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Seen around the internet - Social Media Sunday</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/social-media/seen-around-the-internet-social-media-sunday-1925/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Nov 2010 18:13:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/social-media/seen-around-the-internet-social-media-sunday-1925/</guid>
      <description>Here&amp;rsquo;s a new approach for me … It&amp;rsquo;s Social Media Sunday so here are a few websites to checkout that caught my eye this week.
1. Arcade Fire - We Used to Wait HTML 5 mashed up with Google Maps StreetView meets Arcade Fire. If you haven&amp;rsquo;t tried this, I give you a hint, you enter the town where you were born and then sit back and absorb the music and the video.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Social Media &amp;amp; Internet Usage Policies for staff and contractors</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/social-media/social-media-internet-usage-policies-for-staff-and-contractors-1691/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Oct 2010 09:00:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/social-media/social-media-internet-usage-policies-for-staff-and-contractors-1691/</guid>
      <description>I recently answered a question on LinkedIn Answers about workplace policies for staff and contractors. Policies should cover acceptable internet &amp;amp; email usage, social media and also mobiles or other tools of trade.3 Policies every workplace should have for staff and new starters You should have policies for-
 social media policy to explain what people can do at work internet and email usage policy so staff know its ok to use email or internet Cellphone or mobile policy be clear about who pays for what  I think in a positive world, such policies should talk about trust and transparency - so the tone should be positive for example:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is a Social Media Policy</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/social-media/what-is-a-social-media-policy-1534/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Sep 2010 09:30:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/social-media/what-is-a-social-media-policy-1534/</guid>
      <description>Are you a fan of social media marketingand driving it for your business? When did you last stop to check that you were protected by your company social media policyor your employee policy allows you to access Facebook, YouTube or Twitter. In many cases, companies do not have a clear policy so the sharing of company information on social networks without the express permission of Marketing or PR could leave you in an iffy situation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why you need a social media policy</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/resources/why-you-need-a-social-media-policy-1654/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Sep 2010 09:00:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/resources/why-you-need-a-social-media-policy-1654/</guid>
      <description>Are you responsible for using Twitter at your office? Or maybe you started answering questions from customers on Facebook … if so you should check what your company policy on social media says.Why You Need a Social Media Policy &amp;amp; What should it cover You need a policy to protect yourself and your company - that policy needs to recognise that we all use social media &amp;amp; social networks every day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UPDATED: Twitter Tools - CoTweet best for your business</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/social-media/twitter-tools-cotweet-best-for-your-business-1549/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Sep 2010 11:00:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/social-media/twitter-tools-cotweet-best-for-your-business-1549/</guid>
      <description>CoTweet provides the easiest way for your business to start managing your company or brand on Twitter. If you already are using HootSuite or Tweetdeck you should stop for a minute and check you are doing the right thing for your business. CoTweetis designed for the multi-user / multi-site (!!) environment with assignment, archiving and other management tools - this means you&amp;rsquo;ll never lose a tweet again (or have to share the computer with your boss).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Foursquare Rules of Play Change - only 1 checkin a day allowed</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/social-media/foursquare/foursquare-rules-of-play-change-only-1-checkin-a-day-allowed-1426/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2010 17:00:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/social-media/foursquare/foursquare-rules-of-play-change-only-1-checkin-a-day-allowed-1426/</guid>
      <description>Foursquare, one of my favourite location based mobile social networks has changed its rules for the game of &amp;lsquo;who wants to be a Mayor&amp;rsquo;. Foursquare is growing in popularity in a number of cities and rules for game play have been tightened.
Recently it changed the rules to the most checkins in the past 60 days .. and now it has changed to only 1 checkin is valid each day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Which Social Media experience is right for you?</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/2010-08-16-which-social-media-experience-is-right-for-you/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Aug 2010 10:00:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/2010-08-16-which-social-media-experience-is-right-for-you/</guid>
      <description>How to tell what is right in social media? Myth: Build it &amp;amp; they will come Love great content … Love Google Just listen to social media is not a good position </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Social Media Reputation Management using LinkedIn</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/2010-07-29-social-media-reputation-management-using-linkedin/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jul 2010 11:00:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/2010-07-29-social-media-reputation-management-using-linkedin/</guid>
      <description>Managing your online reputation will be more important over time for everyone - as we grow up the content and material that search engines will collect about us is phenomenal. For many, the CV will cease to exist and be replaced by online reputation, search engine results and specialist business networks like LinkedIn.LinkedIn has managed to hold on to the title of business social network over increasing competition from Facebook and other professional networks like Xing or even Plaxo.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Social Media Reputation Management – Google Profile</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/2010-07-28-social-media-reputation-management-google-profile/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jul 2010 11:00:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/2010-07-28-social-media-reputation-management-google-profile/</guid>
      <description>Did you know that Google has a profile page and that it&amp;rsquo;s similar to a profile page on LinkedIn. Managing your reputation and curating your personal SEO plan is something you should do at least once a year. About Google Profile Google Profilecan be associated with a normal Gmail e-mail address along with Google Apps domains and other addresses. In fact, you&amp;rsquo;ll find that if you use Google your profile comes &amp;lsquo;pre-filled&amp;rsquo; with info on what Google might know about you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Foursquare usage peaks on the weekend</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/2010-07-12-foursquare-usage-peaks-on-the-weekend/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2010 13:00:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/2010-07-12-foursquare-usage-peaks-on-the-weekend/</guid>
      <description>Foursquareusage peaks on the Saturday night reports BitsyBot Labswho studied a weeks worth of checkin data from the geo location based mobile social network. Well that&amp;rsquo;s nothing new - anyone working in mobile and content or value added services will be able to match that insight with data usage and revenue trends.Saturday Nights all-right for Checkin Mania I love that BitsyBot completed this research and it will help lots of poor social media marketing people looking to calculate an ROI.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Start a Social Media Marketing Plan – what do you want to achieve?</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/2010-07-07-start-a-social-media-marketing-plan-what-do-you-want-to-achieve/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jul 2010 09:43:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/2010-07-07-start-a-social-media-marketing-plan-what-do-you-want-to-achieve/</guid>
      <description>The start of any social media plan should actually be the end … by that I mean decide on the goals or what you want to achieve. Any good marcomm person or project planner will thank you for this. So what are good outcomes? what do you want to achieve? If you&amp;rsquo;re starting out in Social Media Marketing you&amp;rsquo;ll be wanting to get your &amp;lsquo;profile page&amp;rsquo; or fan pages just right, get some friends and get some traction.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Start a Social Media Marketing Plan – write your plan</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/social-media/start-a-social-media-marketing-plan-write-your-plan-1124/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jul 2010 09:26:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/social-media/start-a-social-media-marketing-plan-write-your-plan-1124/</guid>
      <description>Start a Social Media Marketing Plan in writing … as we have all probably heard or read, putting even the vaguest plan down on paper will help to make your ideas concrete! The benefit of having a plan on paper means you can consider if your plan and goals are realistic and you can decide as well how involved you want to be in social media marketing.How to Write a Social Media Marketing Plan Your first social media marketing plan need only cover 4 areas:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Start a Social Media Marketing Plan – why you need to use social media?</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/social-media/start-a-social-media-marketing-plan-why-you-need-to-use-social-media-1119/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jul 2010 09:00:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/social-media/start-a-social-media-marketing-plan-why-you-need-to-use-social-media-1119/</guid>
      <description>Starting your plan for social media marketing in a small or big business should be driven by a need or a reason
Why use Social Media - because your customers are using it! First step in your social media marketing plan is to open powerpoint or write on a flipchart the reason why you need to use social media, some good reasons include:
 most of our target audience use social media (no brainer), or because visits to your brand or company website are down as our customers spend more time on social media sites (better) to deliver a sales &amp;amp; marketing programme using online &amp;amp; social media  There are probably plenty of other good reasons you can think of.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Start a Social Media Marketing Plan – why social media?</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/social-media/start-a-social-media-marketing-plan-why-social-media-1113/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jul 2010 09:00:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/social-media/start-a-social-media-marketing-plan-why-social-media-1113/</guid>
      <description>Do you really need a Social Media Marketing Plan? And if your business needs a plan … why does it have to be social media?
Why Social Media Every business - big, small, startup or established brand needs to be using social media - yesterday. I was reading a flyer today which said &amp;lsquo;its critical for every website to include social media&amp;rsquo; — its not the website that needs it … its your marketing and sales plan!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Start a Social Media Marketing Plan – don’t leave it to the PR person</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/2010-06-30-start-a-social-media-marketing-plan-dont-leave-it-to-the-pr-person/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jun 2010 09:00:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/2010-06-30-start-a-social-media-marketing-plan-dont-leave-it-to-the-pr-person/</guid>
      <description>Social Media marketing - using Twitter, Facebook, LinkedIn, Foursquare, Google+ … needs to form part of any marketing plan across the marketing mix. Treating Social Media as a separate activity from the rest of your marketing is a No-No … In fact social media should be integrated into every campaign or promotion.
Social Media marketing fits into new customer acquisition, customer retention, CRM, customer loyalty and anything else that customers do and thats true for D2C brands as well as B2B marketers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>50 Completely Useful stats for social media &amp;amp; mobile marketing</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/2010-05-31-50-completely-useful-stats-for-social-media-mobile-marketing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 May 2010 16:27:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/2010-05-31-50-completely-useful-stats-for-social-media-mobile-marketing/</guid>
      <description>To understand more about Social Media and Mobile Marketing its important to get a few facts together on current trends and insights. 50 completely useful stats for social media does just that.
Why do this? well it helps to create some drive … and helps to understand why anyone or any business needs to do more in social media and mobile marketing.
50 completely useful stats for social media &amp;amp; mobile marketing</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gowalla? Foursquare open for Business? Who will setup a business team in Europe First</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/2010-05-11-gowalla-foursquare-open-for-business/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 May 2010 08:00:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/2010-05-11-gowalla-foursquare-open-for-business/</guid>
      <description>Foursquare is now open to business and is moving beyond geo-tagging and location based social networking. But is Foursquare really open to business? After trying to claim my business location and setup an offer for visitors its now been 3 weeks without a reply.
In the UK right now, I believe there is an opportunity for Gowalla, Foursquare, etc to setup a small but viable business team to work with digital agencies or mobile marketing specialists here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Foursquare Best Location Based Social Networking for Android UK Users</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/social-media/foursquare-best-location-based-social-networking-455/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Feb 2010 18:56:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/social-media/foursquare-best-location-based-social-networking-455/</guid>
      <description>Android mobile owners in the UK will be pleased to know that location based social networkingapps have begun to improve and increase in the number of users. In the past few weeks, top location based social networks such as Brightkiteand Foursquarehave really improved the quality and details of UK locations.**
**
It is a problem of user experience that meant many of these services had few UK users and no UK points of interest.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to use Competitions &amp;amp; Social Media to grow your mobile marketing</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/2010-01-13-how-to-use-competitions-social-media-to-grow-your-business/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jan 2010 23:18:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/2010-01-13-how-to-use-competitions-social-media-to-grow-your-business/</guid>
      <description>Running competitions using social media is a good way for brands and businesses to create welcome visitors and friends to their sites. You can now take that competition mobile using mobile apps, games or mobile websites and you don&amp;rsquo;t have to use SMS.
Using Social Media to get your customers discovering you on their mobile Your marketing messages on social media sites like Twitter and Facebook can direct existing customers to discover your mobile website or to download a mobile app.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Social Media &amp;amp; Marketing Round-up of some good reading</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/mobile-marketing/social-media-marketing-round-up-of-some-good-reading-375/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Dec 2009 16:36:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/mobile-marketing/social-media-marketing-round-up-of-some-good-reading-375/</guid>
      <description>**The problem with doing research on social media and mobile marketing is the overwhelming amount of noise you get from doing searches on Google, Delicious and Twitter.
**
Here are a few links of really useful and easy to consume &amp;lsquo;research&amp;rsquo;
best &amp;lsquo;inspirational&amp;rsquo; video on social media
http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=sIFYPQjYhv8map of social media world
http://www.flickr.com/photos/wasabibratwurst/3128711125/sizes/l/top 100 companies by media spend</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>