<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Jenkins on Damien Saunders</title>
    <link>https://damien1.github.io/tags/jenkins/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Jenkins on Damien Saunders</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2013 21:08:35 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://damien1.github.io/tags/jenkins/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Continuous Integration for WordPress plugins &amp;#8211; Jenkins &amp;#8211; Selenium &amp;#8211; Apache Ant</title>
      <link>https://damien1.github.io/blog/2013-04-07-continuous-integration-for-wordpress-plugins-jenkins-selenium-apache-ant/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2013 21:08:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien1.github.io/blog/2013-04-07-continuous-integration-for-wordpress-plugins-jenkins-selenium-apache-ant/</guid>
      <description>I’m no regular WordPress Plugin Developer – I spend most of my day managing projects or other stuff. So when I do develop, I want a trusted, reliable, repeatable workflow setup that is always testing, always building and always telling me whats going on. That’s why I believe in Continuous Integration … and why I’ve turned to Jenkins as my CI Tool and use Apache Ant and Selenium for testing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HOW TO: Install Jenkins-CI on a Mac OS X with Git &amp;#038; Bitbucket</title>
      <link>https://damien1.github.io/development/how-to-install-jenkins-ci-on-a-mac-os-x-with-git-bitbucket-8072/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Dec 2012 13:56:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien1.github.io/development/how-to-install-jenkins-ci-on-a-mac-os-x-with-git-bitbucket-8072/</guid>
      <description>A few notes on getting Jenkins-CI installed on your Mac and setup with Git and Bitbucket for source code management. I’ve been using Git for some time but I had problems / major issues with Jenkins and could never seem to get this working.
Issues with setting up Jenkins and Git on a Mac Here are the issues I was having … the biggest issue was the Error (unable to clone) which showed up when I created a job and added the path to the Bitbucket repo — even after I had added the SSH Key to Bitbucket.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HOW TO: Start, Stop, Restart or Reload Jenkins &amp;#8211; Mac OSx</title>
      <link>https://damien1.github.io/general/how-to-start-stop-restart-or-reload-jenkins-mac-osx-8022/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2012 13:36:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien1.github.io/general/how-to-start-stop-restart-or-reload-jenkins-mac-osx-8022/</guid>
      <description>I’ve just started to use Jenkins as part of a continuous integration setup that I’m building. Mostly I’m doing this to learn and then apply this to something bigger. At home, I’m using Jenkins as a CI server to manage testing of my PHP WordPress plugins. I know it could be overkill, but as a one man band, automating testing is something that saves me time and increases my confidence that the development feature is tested and ready to deploy!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>