<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Gowalla on Damien Saunders</title>
    <link>http://damien.co/tags/gowalla/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Gowalla on Damien Saunders</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 Jul 2010 11:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://damien.co/tags/gowalla/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Gowalla needs business tools for super users</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/social-media/gowalla-needs-business-tools-for-super-users-1326/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jul 2010 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/social-media/gowalla-needs-business-tools-for-super-users-1326/</guid>
      <description>Gowalla may just be a buzzword for the latest social media marketing trend – but with more people getting smart or superphones that ‘can’ multi-task location based _mobile social networks_ are set to be the in thing. Gowalla just needs some tools for business owners or super users to curate or manage business and locations listing (or to give me access to these).Without some of these basic tools for store owners or community managers the opportunitiy to market using Gowalla are very limited.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gowalla New Users heading toward 350000</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/social-media/gowalla-new-users-heading-toward-350000-1267/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jul 2010 11:00:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/social-media/gowalla-new-users-heading-toward-350000-1267/</guid>
      <description>Gowallaand Foursquareare getting more and more attention and a few companies are starting to monitor and track these services. RJ Metrics monitors both services and predicts Gowalla’s user base will shortly make it to 350,000.Somewhere amongst the stats, you’ll see new users for Gowalla are growing around 2,000 per week but Foursquare recently peaked at 20,000 new users. Summer is usually quieter months for data revenue and usage (same for Jan &amp;amp; Feb Downunder), it will be interesting to track the user take up and usage to see if this is different.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Essential Location Based Apps for Android Mobiles</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/social-media/essential-location-based-apps-for-android-mobiles-1221/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2010 09:00:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/social-media/essential-location-based-apps-for-android-mobiles-1221/</guid>
      <description>Everyone is used to taking their mobile with them, so that means location basedapps for mobiles will start to become more popular. A recent issue of Wired noted that it was thanks to Foursquare&amp;amp; Gowalla, that people are now getting more used to sharing their location. On a fun side, many of the new location based mobile apps have games or allow you to collect rewards for visiting new places. Here’s an essential list of location based apps for Androidmobile.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Foursquare user base to hit 2 million this week</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/social-media/foursquare-user-base-to-hit-2-million-this-week-1263/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jul 2010 16:27:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/social-media/foursquare-user-base-to-hit-2-million-this-week-1263/</guid>
      <description>Foursquareand Gowallahave been grabbing the headlines and few companies are starting to monitor and track these services. RJ Metrics claims Foursquare will hit 2 million usersthis week.Somewhere amongst the stats, you’ll see new users for Foursquare are growing around 14,000 per week but recently peaked at 20,000 new users. This is probably due to active promotions such as being featured in Apple or Android TV adverts. August &amp;amp; September are usually quieter months for data revenue and usage thanks to Summer (same for Jan &amp;amp; Feb Downunder), it will be interesting to track the user take up and usage to see if this is different.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Foursquare most popular location checkin game in London</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/social-media/foursquare-most-popular-location-checkin-tool-in-london-1173/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jul 2010 09:00:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/social-media/foursquare-most-popular-location-checkin-tool-in-london-1173/</guid>
      <description>Foursquare is still the UK’s most popular location based check-in game to play on your mobile. I’ve said it before that Foursquare would come out on tops over Gowalla and Brightkite.
These maps (thanks to Checkin Mania) indicate the difference in the number of locations that users have submitted to each service. The growth from crowd sourced locations and points of interest reflects in the growth of that services usage (ie the most popular service gets the most contributions from users) The point of reference is London Borough Market – one of the more famous places in London to visit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gowalla? Foursquare open for Business? Who will setup a business team in Europe First</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/social-media/gowalla-foursquare-open-for-business-926/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 May 2010 08:00:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/social-media/gowalla-foursquare-open-for-business-926/</guid>
      <description>Foursquare is now open to business and is moving beyond geo-tagging and location based social networking. But is Foursquare really open to business? After trying to claim my business location and setup an offer for visitors its now been 3 weeks without a reply.
In the UK right now, I believe there is an opportunity for Gowalla, Foursquare, etc to setup a small but viable business team to work with digital agencies or mobile marketing specialists here.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>