<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Social Media on Damien Saunders</title>
    <link>https://damien1.github.io/categories/social-media/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Social Media on Damien Saunders</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 27 Aug 2012 15:34:23 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://damien1.github.io/categories/social-media/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Popular Posts in Social Media</title>
      <link>https://damien1.github.io/social-media/popular-posts-in-social-media-11-5510/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Aug 2012 15:34:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien1.github.io/social-media/popular-posts-in-social-media-11-5510/</guid>
      <description>It’s time to catchup on some missed out reading and get out in the sun. So here is a collection of 10 of the best Social Media resources that you love to read.
I’m not going to second guess these related posts – I’m sure there will be stuff about Twitter, Facebook, Email Marketing and Foursquare.
[related_posts limit=”10″]</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Popular Posts in Social Media</title>
      <link>https://damien1.github.io/social-media/popular-posts-in-social-media-12-5509/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jul 2012 15:34:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien1.github.io/social-media/popular-posts-in-social-media-12-5509/</guid>
      <description>It’s time to catchup on some missed out reading and get out in the sun. So here is a collection of 10 of the best Social Media resources that you love to read.
I’m not going to second guess these related posts – I’m sure there will be stuff about Twitter, Facebook, Email Marketing and Foursquare.
[related_posts limit=”10″]</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rule #2 &amp;#8211; Social Media Marketing &amp;#8211; Crucial for Sales &amp;#038; Marketing</title>
      <link>https://damien1.github.io/social-media/rule-2-social-media-marketing-crucial-sales-marketing-7361/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jun 2012 16:00:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien1.github.io/social-media/rule-2-social-media-marketing-crucial-sales-marketing-7361/</guid>
      <description>Social Media marketing – using Twitter, Facebook, LinkedIn, Foursquare, Google+ … needs to form part of any marketing plan across the marketing mix. Do you really need a Digital Marketing Plan? And if your business needs a plan … why does it have to included social media?
Why Digital Marketing &amp;amp; Social Media? Every business – big, small, startup or established brand needs a digital marketing strategy. It’s crucial for your marketing and sales plan (even if you don’t have one) to include digital marketing and social media.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rule #1 &amp;#8211; Social Media Marketing &amp;#8211; don&amp;#8217;t leave it to PR or the intern</title>
      <link>https://damien1.github.io/social-media/rule-1-social-media-marketing-dont-leave-pr-intern-7352/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jun 2012 14:30:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien1.github.io/social-media/rule-1-social-media-marketing-dont-leave-pr-intern-7352/</guid>
      <description>Social Media marketing – using Twitter, Facebook, LinkedIn, Foursquare, Google+ … needs to form part of any marketing plan across the marketing mix. Treating Social Media as a separate activity from the rest of your marketing is a No-No … In fact social media should be integrated into every campaign or promotion.
Digital marketing fits into new customer acquisition, customer retention, CRM, customer engagement and loyalty and anything else that customers do and thats true for D2C brands as well as B2B marketers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google&#43;: still not as interesting as Pinterest   &lt;&lt;- why does everyone want it fail?</title>
      <link>https://damien1.github.io/social-media/google-still-not-as-interesting-as-pinterest-7073/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 May 2012 22:35:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien1.github.io/social-media/google-still-not-as-interesting-as-pinterest-7073/</guid>
      <description>Comment – Seems to me that ‘everyone’ wants to find a fault with Google+ and many maybe ‘wishing’ it to fail. It’s hard to get traction with social networks as we are likely to be regular users of a few social networks. It’s harder still to get people to change their primary social network of choice when your online social network all still use The Facebook.
Source: Google+: still not as interesting as Pinterest, new study finds: ”</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Popular Posts in Social Media</title>
      <link>https://damien1.github.io/social-media/popular-posts-in-social-media-4-5506/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Apr 2012 15:34:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien1.github.io/social-media/popular-posts-in-social-media-4-5506/</guid>
      <description>It’s time to catchup on some missed out reading. So here is a collection of 10 of the best Social Media resources that you love to read.
I’m not going to second guess these related posts – I’m sure there will be stuff about Twitter, Facebook, Email Marketing and Foursquare.
[related_posts limit=”10″]</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Popular Posts in Social Media</title>
      <link>https://damien1.github.io/social-media/popular-posts-in-social-media-3-5505/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Mar 2012 15:34:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien1.github.io/social-media/popular-posts-in-social-media-3-5505/</guid>
      <description>It’s time to catchup on some missed out reading. So here is a collection of 10 of the best Social Media resources that you love to read.
I’m not going to second guess these related posts – I’m sure there will be stuff about Twitter, Facebook, Email Marketing and Foursquare.
[related_posts limit=”10″]</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Popular Posts in Social Media</title>
      <link>https://damien1.github.io/social-media/popular-posts-in-social-media-2-5516/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2012 15:34:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien1.github.io/social-media/popular-posts-in-social-media-2-5516/</guid>
      <description>It’s time to catchup on some missed out reading. So here is a collection of 10 of the best Social Media resources that you love to read.
I’m not going to second guess these related posts – I’m sure there will be stuff about Twitter, Facebook, Email Marketing and Foursquare.
[related_posts limit=”10″]</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Popular Posts in Social Media</title>
      <link>https://damien1.github.io/social-media/popular-posts-in-social-media-5515/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2011 16:34:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien1.github.io/social-media/popular-posts-in-social-media-5515/</guid>
      <description>It’s time to catchup on some missed out reading and enjoy the break. So here is a collection of 10 of the best Social Media resources that you love to read.
So I’m not going to second guess these related posts – I’m sure there will be stuff about Twitter, Facebook, Email Marketing and Foursquare.
[related_posts limit=”10″”]</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best Tools for Social Media Marketing if you&#39;re just getting started</title>
      <link>https://damien1.github.io/blog/2011-07-26-best-tools-for-social-media-marketing-if-youre-just-getting-started/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2011 14:00:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien1.github.io/blog/2011-07-26-best-tools-for-social-media-marketing-if-youre-just-getting-started/</guid>
      <description>If you&amp;rsquo;re getting started with Social Media marketing then you need at least 1 web based tool to help you.
For most businesses and individuals, social media marketing starts and ends with Tweetdeck. Which provides an all-in-one solution for pushing content direct from your machine. You need better tools for planning and managing your social media marketing.
However browser based tools for social media marketing are better suited for team or office environs – or if you&amp;rsquo;re like me, someone on the road in different offices who can&amp;rsquo;t have Tweetdeck open all the time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WordPress 3.2 Release Candidate is here</title>
      <link>https://damien1.github.io/social-media/wordpress-3-2-release-candidate-is-here-3-4440/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jun 2011 20:10:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien1.github.io/social-media/wordpress-3-2-release-candidate-is-here-3-4440/</guid>
      <description>The second release candidate for the next version of WordPress 3.2 is here. If you haven’t started testing 3.2, now is the time. Previous experience would make this the final RC before the real deal.
 Should I update to this release candidate? As this is a release candidate you shouldn’t use this on a really important live site – but it does mean it’s pretty stable and useful. You should find that most popular plugins and themes have no issues as developers have been working since RC1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>20 very recent Social Media articles for you</title>
      <link>https://damien1.github.io/social-media/20-very-recent-social-media-articles-for-you-3965/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jun 2011 11:34:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien1.github.io/social-media/20-very-recent-social-media-articles-for-you-3965/</guid>
      <description>It’s time to catchup on some missed out reading and get out in the sun. So here is a collection of 10 of the best social media resources for you to read.
So I’m not going to second guess these related posts – I’m sure there will be stuff about Emailvision, Facebook, brand reputation and cross channel marketing.
[related_posts limit=”20″]– SPECIAL PROMO ALERT –
Ever feel that social media &amp;amp; online marketing is too difficult for you?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Emailvision – it&amp;#8217;s great to feel engaged</title>
      <link>https://damien1.github.io/social-media/emailvision-%e2%80%93-its-great-to-feel-engaged-3977/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2011 11:10:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien1.github.io/social-media/emailvision-%e2%80%93-its-great-to-feel-engaged-3977/</guid>
      <description>The team at Emailvision have contacted me a lot in the past 3 days … since I wrote a short article on cross channel campaign problems and a lack of testing.
I will say that Emailvision team that I have spoken to have all been great – it’s good to know they switched on people who are passionate about their company and what they do.
 The problem with integrated cross-channel marketing is … James from Emailvision resolved / pointed out a few things –</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Could we do better? Short Web Survey from KISS Insights</title>
      <link>https://damien1.github.io/social-media/what-could-we-do-better-add-a-subtle-web-survey-3920/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jun 2011 11:03:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien1.github.io/social-media/what-could-we-do-better-add-a-subtle-web-survey-3920/</guid>
      <description>What could we do to make this site more useful? That’s a good question … and thanks to Kiss Insights its really easy to ask this of your website visitors.
It’s only one answer &amp;amp; takes one second Web surveys should not be a bore and they should not be too long. We’re all so busy now and being asked to spend 15 mins on a survey is pointless.
I guess that’s what makes the KISS approach so powerful – keep it short and simple.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Starting in Digital? Don&amp;#8217;t ruin your brand reputation with your 1st social media marketing campaign</title>
      <link>https://damien1.github.io/social-media/starting-in-digital-dont-ruin-your-brand-reputation-with-your-1st-social-media-marketing-campaign-3917/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2011 14:40:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien1.github.io/social-media/starting-in-digital-dont-ruin-your-brand-reputation-with-your-1st-social-media-marketing-campaign-3917/</guid>
      <description>Digital marketing has its benefits mainly that it’s easy to launch a social media campaign without any prior relationship with the victim.
I’m more annoyed at the damage young companies do to their brand, reputation and domain-name … at wasted opportunities from legitimate startups who just spam any contacts in one e-mail blast.
Last week, I got an email sent to me with someone elses info – yet it was an invite to join their London business network.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Delicious finally updates its Firefox Extension</title>
      <link>https://damien1.github.io/social-media/delicious-finally-updates-its-firefox-extension-3515/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2011 11:38:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien1.github.io/social-media/delicious-finally-updates-its-firefox-extension-3515/</guid>
      <description>Delicious, that’s delicious.com or del.icio.us for those old enough – has finally updated its Firefox extension – though it is still a beta version, the updated extension is available in the Mozilla Add-ons applet-store
If you gave up on Delicious for syncing bookmarks cause browsers added their own tools like Google Bookmarks or Firefox Sync then maybe this isn’t for you.
If you’re still in love with the idea of social bookmarking – tagging and sharing your bookmarks … then this is something for you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Delicious &amp;#8211; I still love you</title>
      <link>https://damien1.github.io/social-media/delicious-i-still-love-you-3517/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2011 11:04:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien1.github.io/social-media/delicious-i-still-love-you-3517/</guid>
      <description>Delicious, that’s delicious.com or del.icio.us for those who can remember it – is one of the original web 2.0 social media services that specialised in social-bookmarking. We should learn to love Delicious again now that they’ve got new owners.
Delicious is the original web 2.0 service we still love A few years back when something called web 2.0 was really a fluffy concept, Del.icio.us was the easy to understand social-bookmarking website.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Facebook Wants your Homepage</title>
      <link>https://damien1.github.io/social-media/facebook-wants-your-homepage-2811/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Mar 2011 07:05:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien1.github.io/social-media/facebook-wants-your-homepage-2811/</guid>
      <description>I’m not one to always login to Facebook … It’s a good week if I don’t log in at all. But for about 500 million people Facebook is pretty important.
As if Facebook really needed to tell you to bookmark their site if you already go there – but this bookmarket / on-site advertising is a fresh change to the usual page prompting you to login from your mobile.
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What&amp;#8217;s it like being a social media consultant [humour]</title>
      <link>https://damien1.github.io/social-media/whats-it-like-being-a-social-media-consultant-humour-2798/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Mar 2011 12:51:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien1.github.io/social-media/whats-it-like-being-a-social-media-consultant-humour-2798/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DotCom Bubble Burst? Latest Internet Startup Valuations</title>
      <link>https://damien1.github.io/social-media/dotcom-bubble-burst-latest-internet-startup-valuations-2789/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2011 09:50:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien1.github.io/social-media/dotcom-bubble-burst-latest-internet-startup-valuations-2789/</guid>
      <description>Startup Valuations got you feeling low? Maybe its time to buy into the dotcom bubble before it bursts. So ride the social media marketing wave …
via Guardian.co.uk
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Using Social Media takes 20% of your Australian day</title>
      <link>https://damien1.github.io/social-media/using-social-media-takes-20-of-your-australian-day-2786/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2011 09:25:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien1.github.io/social-media/using-social-media-takes-20-of-your-australian-day-2786/</guid>
      <description>Australians spend 1 in 5 minutes using social media sites. Social Networking usage was about 22% in December 2010 says comScore.
The statistics reveal that Facebook, Twitter, LinkedIn are some of the most popular destinations. If you add into this instant messaging then the total rises to 35% – which is probably a more realistic definition of social networking.
There is a presentation you can download with really good insights on internet usage across Australia.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SEO best practice for using &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt; and &amp;lt;em&amp;gt;</title>
      <link>https://damien1.github.io/social-media/seo-best-practice-for-using-strong-and-em-2695/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2011 09:42:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien1.github.io/social-media/seo-best-practice-for-using-strong-and-em-2695/</guid>
      <description>As more people become aware of HTML5 it’s time to review how tagging written content will impact search engine optimisation. Tags like and are redundant – instead and have been in use for a few years by many blogging and web developer tools. Now the HTML5 standard recognises that and should only be used for visual style.
You can do more with CSS styles If you remember writing HTML back in the 90’s you might be more comfortable using and .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Saturday Humour &amp;#8211; Size of blogging [infographic]</title>
      <link>https://damien1.github.io/social-media/saturday-humour-size-of-blogging-infographic-2284/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Dec 2010 21:17:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien1.github.io/social-media/saturday-humour-size-of-blogging-infographic-2284/</guid>
      <description>Saturday’s usual weekly comic has been moved aside this week for something more important.

So its a week to Xmas … and all through the house not a creature was stirring – except for creatives and marketing types publishing their great present gifts for the world to enjoy.
What’s your opinion? do you think this Tree of Blogs sums things up quite nicely? and looking ahead – will the roots generate enough food and support for the future?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>myGeoBook is building geolocation tools for any website</title>
      <link>https://damien1.github.io/social-media/mygeobook-2276/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Dec 2010 11:00:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien1.github.io/social-media/mygeobook-2276/</guid>
      <description>myGeoBook is about geolocation &amp;amp; social media, with a set of tools for any website developer to use. Maps maybe sexy to some people and yes everyone is talking about mobile location services right now ([ id=”232″ type=”category”]Foursquare[/] anyone).
Here’s a very short guide on how to add a map to WordPress using myGeoBook — but first, here’s an example. This map is based on the Frommers best restaurants in Europe.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Have you tried LinkedIn lately?</title>
      <link>https://damien1.github.io/social-media/have-you-tried-linkedin-lately-2033/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Nov 2010 09:48:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien1.github.io/social-media/have-you-tried-linkedin-lately-2033/</guid>
      <description>LinkedInhas been the business social networkof choice for many and its nearly 10 years old, but younger upstarts have such a mass that its time to look at what LinkedIn can offer to social media marketing, especially for b2b marketing.
There is value in personally knowing your connection When LinkedIn first launched it was not much more than a way to list your work history and connect with business colleagues. It was even important that you had the email address of someone before you could add them – which meant at least you had their business card as people wouldn’t accept requests to connect if they couldn’t remember how they met you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Social Media Sunday</title>
      <link>https://damien1.github.io/social-media/social-media-sunday-2-2078/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Nov 2010 16:53:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien1.github.io/social-media/social-media-sunday-2-2078/</guid>
      <description>It’s here again – Social Media Sunday and this week I have chosen 3 of the best Google Apps for social networking and project management.

If you don’t use Google Apps with a custom domain … then you don’t know what you are missing.
Socialwok 
Socialwok creates a professional social network instantly for everyone on the same domain. You can also create projects or shared folders (called Feeds) and invite external people — clients?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to choose a good social media marketing consultant</title>
      <link>https://damien1.github.io/social-media/how-to-choose-a-good-social-media-marketing-consultant-2030/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Nov 2010 09:41:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien1.github.io/social-media/how-to-choose-a-good-social-media-marketing-consultant-2030/</guid>
      <description>Social media marketingis no longer a buzzword and many brands and businesses are choosing to recruit full-time staff to develop and deliver the quicksilver successesof the best viral campaigns.What’s the difference between a social media consultant, digital planner &amp;amp; a community manager? If you are looking for an independent social media strategist to come in as a consultant or freelance gig then you need to know why a social media marketing consultant is very different to a digital planner or community manager.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Social media Sunday</title>
      <link>https://damien1.github.io/social-media/social-media-sunday-1977/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Nov 2010 11:35:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien1.github.io/social-media/social-media-sunday-1977/</guid>
      <description>Social media Sunday continues this week … With a theme on presentations and communicating. I’m in the country this weekend, so this post was done using blogpress on my iPad which has some great features for managing wordpress more like a magazine.
 Navigation alternatives and insights  Jess3 how social media is changing design  Social media and mobile. From an educationalists perspective
http://www.slideshare.net/mobile/timbuckteeth/combining-mobile-tools-and-social-media#20  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cause Related Marketing &amp;amp; Social Media</title>
      <link>https://damien1.github.io/social-media/cause-related-marketing-social-media-1921/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2010 09:52:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien1.github.io/social-media/cause-related-marketing-social-media-1921/</guid>
      <description>Yesterday was Remembrance Sunday in the UK. For a lot of people its more significant than the 2 minute silence on 11 November because they are out doing things related to their cause – remembering the ones who have gone before us, visiting relatives that are veterans or just being the Carer to someone who was injured during service.
This made me think about how social media marketing can play a part in cause related marketing and what I would do to support my cause.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Seen around the internet &amp;#8211; Social Media Sunday</title>
      <link>https://damien1.github.io/social-media/seen-around-the-internet-social-media-sunday-1925/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Nov 2010 18:13:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien1.github.io/social-media/seen-around-the-internet-social-media-sunday-1925/</guid>
      <description>Here’s a new approach for me … It’s Social Media Sunday so here are a few websites to checkout that caught my eye this week.
1. Arcade Fire – We Used to Wait HTML 5 mashed up with Google Maps StreetView meets Arcade Fire. If you haven’t tried this, I give you a hint, you enter the town where you were born and then sit back and absorb the music and the video.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LinkedIn makes it easier to view who viewed your profile</title>
      <link>https://damien1.github.io/social-media/linkedin-makes-it-easier-to-view-who-viewed-your-profile-1777/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Nov 2010 09:07:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien1.github.io/social-media/linkedin-makes-it-easier-to-view-who-viewed-your-profile-1777/</guid>
      <description>LinkedInhas changed its settings so that basic or free users can now find out who actually looked at their profile in the last week. This cool new feature can be found on the LinkedIn website– but you have to first change your own privacy settings from anonymous to share in the benefits of profile stats. I guess its the business persons equivalent of a Facebook poke or like.
Check it out … and while you’re at it – add me as a colleague on LinkedIn</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Social Media Marketing Jobs &amp;#8211; Recruiters &amp;amp; HR Professionals</title>
      <link>https://damien1.github.io/social-media/social-media-marketing-jobs-recruiters-hr-professionals-1739/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Oct 2010 09:00:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien1.github.io/social-media/social-media-marketing-jobs-recruiters-hr-professionals-1739/</guid>
      <description>Are you looking for work? Need to know what Recruiters and Agencies in London, UK are looking after Social Media Marketing? Then why not try my new Twitter List 
@damiensaunders/agencies-work-recruitment http://damiens.ws/davWziCurrently the list includes:
Ecom Recruitment – recruitment agency
Propel London – recruitment agency
Stopgap – recruitment agency
theSkein – freelance digital media jobs list
October Recruitment London – recruitment agency
Tanya @ October – Great Recruiter
Want to get yourself added to the list – then just contact me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Social Media &amp;amp; Internet Usage Policies for staff and contractors</title>
      <link>https://damien1.github.io/social-media/social-media-internet-usage-policies-for-staff-and-contractors-1691/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Oct 2010 09:00:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien1.github.io/social-media/social-media-internet-usage-policies-for-staff-and-contractors-1691/</guid>
      <description>I recently answered a question on LinkedIn Answers about workplace policies for staff and contractors. Policies should cover acceptable internet &amp;amp; email usage, social media and also mobiles or other tools of trade.3 Policies every workplace should have for staff and new starters You should have policies for-
 social media policy to explain what people can do at work internet and email usage policy so staff know its ok to use email or internet Cellphone or mobile policy be clear about who pays for what  I think in a positive world, such policies should talk about trust and transparency – so the tone should be positive for example:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is a Social Media Policy</title>
      <link>https://damien1.github.io/social-media/what-is-a-social-media-policy-1534/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Sep 2010 09:30:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien1.github.io/social-media/what-is-a-social-media-policy-1534/</guid>
      <description>Are you a fan of social media marketingand driving it for your business? When did you last stop to check that you were protected by your company social media policyor your employee policy allows you to access Facebook, YouTube or Twitter. In many cases, companies do not have a clear policy so the sharing of company information on social networks without the express permission of Marketing or PR could leave you in an iffy situation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UPDATED: Twitter Tools &amp;#8211; CoTweet best for your business</title>
      <link>https://damien1.github.io/social-media/twitter-tools-cotweet-best-for-your-business-1549/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Sep 2010 11:00:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien1.github.io/social-media/twitter-tools-cotweet-best-for-your-business-1549/</guid>
      <description>CoTweet provides the easiest way for your business to start managing your company or brand on Twitter. If you already are using HootSuite or Tweetdeck you should stop for a minute and check you are doing the right thing for your business. CoTweetis designed for the multi-user / multi-site (!!) environment with assignment, archiving and other management tools – this means you’ll never lose a tweet again (or have to share the computer with your boss).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Social Tools for Customer Service – Get Satisfaction</title>
      <link>https://damien1.github.io/social-media/social-tools-for-customer-service-get-satisfaction-1464/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Sep 2010 17:00:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien1.github.io/social-media/social-tools-for-customer-service-get-satisfaction-1464/</guid>
      <description>Get Satisfaction– its what you want when you ring a call centre – like your bank, your tax office or some other service provider. Get Satisfaction, if you don’t know it is the name of a powerful web based customer service tool which helps customers to connect and help themselves.
I’ve just launched a Get Satisfaction forum to demonstrate the features of their free service – and it works well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bit.ly Making offline marketing work for social media with URL shortener</title>
      <link>https://damien1.github.io/social-media/bit-ly-making-offline-marketing-work-for-social-media-with-url-shortener-1444/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Sep 2010 10:00:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien1.github.io/social-media/bit-ly-making-offline-marketing-work-for-social-media-with-url-shortener-1444/</guid>
      <description>Engagement metrics and CPE are going to become more popular this year and next year, and so how do you take the offline world online? Or how can you start track the value of that billboard you just spent 10,000,000 dollars on?
Well that looks obvious! So how are you tracking offline to online engagement?
At the moment Bit.ly Pro offers free service – you provide a customer domain or sub domain and it does the rest.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How do you measure ROI in social media?</title>
      <link>https://damien1.github.io/social-media/how-do-you-measure-roi-in-social-media-1439/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Sep 2010 11:00:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien1.github.io/social-media/how-do-you-measure-roi-in-social-media-1439/</guid>
      <description>All to often people or companies start using social media but don’t know how to measure the return on investment or calculate a payoff from using social media. Here’s a few easy ideas to start calculating ROIs for you to consider.Calculating ROI for your CFO Typically a ROI calculation is your total revenue or benefit divided by the costs. But if it cost you zilch to setup the twitter account .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Which Social Media experience is right for you?</title>
      <link>https://damien1.github.io/social-media/which-social-media-experience-is-right-for-you-1406/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Aug 2010 10:00:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien1.github.io/social-media/which-social-media-experience-is-right-for-you-1406/</guid>
      <description>How to tell what is right in social media? Myth: Build it &amp;amp; they will come Love great content … Love Google Just listen to social media is not a good position </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vilnius Lithuania loves Foursquare</title>
      <link>https://damien1.github.io/social-media/vilnius-lithuania-loves-foursquare-1393/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Aug 2010 10:00:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien1.github.io/social-media/vilnius-lithuania-loves-foursquare-1393/</guid>
      <description>Foursquaretoday is the most popular mobile checkin app in Vilnius, Lithuania. While not everyone here can afford the iPhone – many people are using Foursquare on their Blackberry.
Point of note – Blackberry App World is not available in Lithuania and so people are using hacks to install this.
Here’s a couple of screenshots from Checkin Mania confirming the number of venues is great in Foursquare vs Gowalla in the central old town area.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Social Media Reputation Management using LinkedIn</title>
      <link>https://damien1.github.io/social-media/social-media-reputation-management-using-linkedin-1367/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jul 2010 11:00:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien1.github.io/social-media/social-media-reputation-management-using-linkedin-1367/</guid>
      <description>Managing your online reputation will be more important over time for everyone – as we grow up the content and material that search engines will collect about us is phenomenal. For many, the CV will cease to exist and be replaced by online reputation, search engine results and specialist business networks like LinkedIn.LinkedIn has managed to hold on to the title of business social network over increasing competition from Facebook and other professional networks like Xing or even Plaxo.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Social Media Reputation Management – Google Profile</title>
      <link>https://damien1.github.io/social-media/social-media-reputation-management-google-profile-1360/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jul 2010 11:00:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien1.github.io/social-media/social-media-reputation-management-google-profile-1360/</guid>
      <description>Did you know that Google has a profile page and that it’s similar to a profile page on LinkedIn. Managing your reputation and curating your personal SEO plan is something you should do at least once a year. About Google Profile Google Profilecan be associated with a normal Gmail e-mail address along with Google Apps domains and other addresses. In fact, you’ll find that if you use Google your profile comes ‘pre-filled’ with info on what Google might know about you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Essential Collection to Get Started with Foursquare</title>
      <link>https://damien1.github.io/resources/essential-collection-to-get-started-with-foursquare-1301/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jul 2010 15:00:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien1.github.io/resources/essential-collection-to-get-started-with-foursquare-1301/</guid>
      <description>If you’re new to _Foursquare_ or your business is wondering how to leverage geolocation social networks in areas like sales and marketing, customer service or retention then this _essential collection_ will help you to get started.Of course, when you first started using Facebook, Foursquare, Gowalla, MySpace, etc, etc your initial experience is about ‘what does this do for me’, not ‘what can my business do with this’. If your business is new to this then take a look at my social media marketing kit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gowalla needs business tools for super users</title>
      <link>https://damien1.github.io/social-media/gowalla-needs-business-tools-for-super-users-1326/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jul 2010 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien1.github.io/social-media/gowalla-needs-business-tools-for-super-users-1326/</guid>
      <description>Gowalla may just be a buzzword for the latest social media marketing trend – but with more people getting smart or superphones that ‘can’ multi-task location based _mobile social networks_ are set to be the in thing. Gowalla just needs some tools for business owners or super users to curate or manage business and locations listing (or to give me access to these).Without some of these basic tools for store owners or community managers the opportunitiy to market using Gowalla are very limited.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Social Media Marketing – Integrate with traditional marketing activities</title>
      <link>https://damien1.github.io/social-media/social-media-marketing-integrate-with-traditional-marketing-activities-1312/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jul 2010 10:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien1.github.io/social-media/social-media-marketing-integrate-with-traditional-marketing-activities-1312/</guid>
      <description>Today’s marketing activities are changing – you can say old skool marketing is being overtaken by new skool ideas and techniques. _Social Media Marketing_ techniques mean you can integrate activities across the marketing mix and do it for ‘free’. Before you cut your budget for traditional marketing like PR, Direct Mail, Radio, Press, TV or Outdoor – STOP – Think about it and find out how to integrate your social media marketing into your traditional marketing channels and _take the conversation online_.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Easy Guide to Social Media Marketing &amp;amp; Location</title>
      <link>https://damien1.github.io/resources/easy-guide-to-social-media-marketing-location-1316/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jul 2010 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien1.github.io/resources/easy-guide-to-social-media-marketing-location-1316/</guid>
      <description>This easy guide to social media &amp;amp; location marketingwas something I published only to SlideShare – a new channel which has great potential for B2B digital marketing. This guide sums up key activities to get you started and is a bit of motivation that you can share with office colleagues. Key points include:
 Claim your Business on Foursquare Claim your Entry on Google Maps Create an Email Newsletter Create a Facebook Website Cross Promote using Twitter, Facebook and your website  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Social Media Marketing &amp;#8211; Integrate across the marketing mix</title>
      <link>https://damien1.github.io/social-media/social-media-marketing-integrate-across-the-marketing-mix-1306/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jul 2010 10:00:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien1.github.io/social-media/social-media-marketing-integrate-across-the-marketing-mix-1306/</guid>
      <description>Social Media Marketing presents the opportunity to try a number of different social networks and promote or market in these as appropriate.Each social network has its own pro’s and con’s such as Twitter is more like a broadcast, one way radioand a Facebook fan page can create conversations that people can easily follow and read.
When you start out with social media marketing, the best sites to start with are:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gowalla New Users heading toward 350000</title>
      <link>https://damien1.github.io/social-media/gowalla-new-users-heading-toward-350000-1267/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jul 2010 11:00:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien1.github.io/social-media/gowalla-new-users-heading-toward-350000-1267/</guid>
      <description>Gowallaand Foursquareare getting more and more attention and a few companies are starting to monitor and track these services. RJ Metrics monitors both services and predicts Gowalla’s user base will shortly make it to 350,000.Somewhere amongst the stats, you’ll see new users for Gowalla are growing around 2,000 per week but Foursquare recently peaked at 20,000 new users. Summer is usually quieter months for data revenue and usage (same for Jan &amp;amp; Feb Downunder), it will be interesting to track the user take up and usage to see if this is different.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Social Media Marketing Essential Collection to get started</title>
      <link>https://damien1.github.io/social-media/social-media-marketing-essential-collection-1143/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jul 2010 09:40:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien1.github.io/social-media/social-media-marketing-essential-collection-1143/</guid>
      <description>Optimising for Social Media Marketingwill start to develop as a set of tools or addons to be used as part of a marketing promotion or campaign. If you’re just getting started with social media then you don’t need to optimise, you just need to start out with the right attitude and a good plan.Getting Started with Social Media Marketing In this first collection of articles, I’ve discussed 4 critical areas or rules:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Get started with Foursquare for Social Media &amp;amp; Mobile Marketing</title>
      <link>https://damien1.github.io/social-media/get-started-with-foursquare-for-social-media-mobile-marketing-1231/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jul 2010 09:00:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien1.github.io/social-media/get-started-with-foursquare-for-social-media-mobile-marketing-1231/</guid>
      <description>Foursquareis a location based service(LBS) for your mobile and at the same time its a social network. In the past 12 months Foursquare has grown in popularity to possibly be the biggest Geo Location Based Social Networkin the UK – well at least in London.
Foursquare (the name is from a school yard game played in the USA) started about 2 years back and has apps for iPhone, Android &amp;amp; BlackBerry … this is a free business directory where every listing was added by a customer or a visitor to that shop.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>8 Step Guide to Foursquare</title>
      <link>https://damien1.github.io/resources/8-step-guide-to-foursquare-1287/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jul 2010 11:00:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien1.github.io/resources/8-step-guide-to-foursquare-1287/</guid>
      <description>
With all the excitement of _Foursquare_ heading to 2,000,000 users this week it was time to post this 8 step guide to Foursquare to help you get started using this geo-location social network.8 Step Guide is a easy to follow and includes tips like:
 Claim your business Run Competitions for Customers Reward the Mayor Track your Checkins Cross promote Foursquare on Twitter, Facebook &amp;amp; your website  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HOW TO Claim your business listing in Foursquare</title>
      <link>https://damien1.github.io/social-media/how-to-claim-your-business-listing-in-foursquare-1235/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jul 2010 09:32:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien1.github.io/social-media/how-to-claim-your-business-listing-in-foursquare-1235/</guid>
      <description>Foursquareis a popular geo location based social network and available on mobile for iPhone, Androd &amp;amp; Blackberry phones. The business directory listings are free to add and initially added by customers or visitors to stores or shops who check-in.You need to claim your business entry so you can update the details and add special offers for Mayors, visitors etc. Your business or store is probably already in the directory if you are in London or a major city.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Foursquare usage peaks on the weekend</title>
      <link>https://damien1.github.io/social-media/foursquare-usage-peaks-on-the-weekend-1258/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2010 13:00:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien1.github.io/social-media/foursquare-usage-peaks-on-the-weekend-1258/</guid>
      <description>Foursquareusage peaks on the Saturday night reports BitsyBot Labswho studied a weeks worth of checkin data from the geo location based mobile social network. Well that’s nothing new – anyone working in mobile and content or value added services will be able to match that insight with data usage and revenue trends.
Saturday Nights all-right for Checkin Mania I love that BitsyBot completed this research and it will help lots of poor social media marketing people looking to calculate an ROI.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Essential Location Based Apps for Android Mobiles</title>
      <link>https://damien1.github.io/social-media/essential-location-based-apps-for-android-mobiles-1221/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2010 09:00:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien1.github.io/social-media/essential-location-based-apps-for-android-mobiles-1221/</guid>
      <description>Everyone is used to taking their mobile with them, so that means location basedapps for mobiles will start to become more popular. A recent issue of Wired noted that it was thanks to Foursquare&amp;amp; Gowalla, that people are now getting more used to sharing their location. On a fun side, many of the new location based mobile apps have games or allow you to collect rewards for visiting new places. Here’s an essential list of location based apps for Androidmobile.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Foursquare user base to hit 2 million this week</title>
      <link>https://damien1.github.io/social-media/foursquare-user-base-to-hit-2-million-this-week-1263/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jul 2010 16:27:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien1.github.io/social-media/foursquare-user-base-to-hit-2-million-this-week-1263/</guid>
      <description>Foursquareand Gowallahave been grabbing the headlines and few companies are starting to monitor and track these services. RJ Metrics claims Foursquare will hit 2 million usersthis week.Somewhere amongst the stats, you’ll see new users for Foursquare are growing around 14,000 per week but recently peaked at 20,000 new users. This is probably due to active promotions such as being featured in Apple or Android TV adverts. August &amp;amp; September are usually quieter months for data revenue and usage thanks to Summer (same for Jan &amp;amp; Feb Downunder), it will be interesting to track the user take up and usage to see if this is different.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What will be your next Foursquare Badge – new Hubspot Grader tool</title>
      <link>https://damien1.github.io/social-media/what-will-be-your-next-foursquare-badge-new-hubspot-grader-tool-1208/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jul 2010 09:12:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien1.github.io/social-media/what-will-be-your-next-foursquare-badge-new-hubspot-grader-tool-1208/</guid>
      <description>If you’re using Foursquare for social media and personal fun, you’ll be interested to know about the new-ish tool from Hubspot. Square Graderis their new tool which rates your Foursquare profile and what’s interesting is it predicts your next Foursquare Badge.
Square Grader may not be their finest tool – unlike their other tools which grade your websiteor blog, Square Grader doesn’t offer much in the way of suggestions to improve your rating.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Start a Social Media Marketing Plan – what do you want to achieve?</title>
      <link>https://damien1.github.io/social-media/start-a-social-media-marketing-plan-what-do-you-want-to-achieve-1192/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jul 2010 09:43:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien1.github.io/social-media/start-a-social-media-marketing-plan-what-do-you-want-to-achieve-1192/</guid>
      <description>The start of any social media plan should actually be the end … by that I mean decide on the goals or what you want to achieve. Any good marcomm person or project planner will thank you for this. So what are good outcomes? what do you want to achieve? If you’re starting out in Social Media Marketing you’ll be wanting to get your ‘profile page’ or fan pages just right, get some friends and get some traction.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Foursquare most popular location checkin game in London</title>
      <link>https://damien1.github.io/social-media/foursquare-most-popular-location-checkin-tool-in-london-1173/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jul 2010 09:00:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien1.github.io/social-media/foursquare-most-popular-location-checkin-tool-in-london-1173/</guid>
      <description>Foursquare is still the UK’s most popular location based check-in game to play on your mobile. I’ve said it before that Foursquare would come out on tops over Gowalla and Brightkite.
These maps (thanks to Checkin Mania) indicate the difference in the number of locations that users have submitted to each service. The growth from crowd sourced locations and points of interest reflects in the growth of that services usage (ie the most popular service gets the most contributions from users) The point of reference is London Borough Market – one of the more famous places in London to visit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Damien Saunders Foursquare Super Mayor</title>
      <link>https://damien1.github.io/social-media/damien-saunders-foursquare-super-mayor-1162/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jul 2010 11:00:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien1.github.io/social-media/damien-saunders-foursquare-super-mayor-1162/</guid>
      <description>Looking for some help with your Foursquare and Social Media Marketing? Then look no further than the badges of the people who you work with. Damien Saunders has been working hard to collect badges, pins, mayorships to be able to provide the best insights and metrics for the location based checkin mobile games.
The game inside Foursquare has two parts:
 Any user can become a Mayor when they check-in the most to a particular venue, Users get badges for activities like going to a 5 different coffee shops.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Start a Social Media Marketing Plan – write your plan</title>
      <link>https://damien1.github.io/social-media/start-a-social-media-marketing-plan-write-your-plan-1124/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jul 2010 09:26:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien1.github.io/social-media/start-a-social-media-marketing-plan-write-your-plan-1124/</guid>
      <description>Start a Social Media Marketing Plan in writing … as we have all probably heard or read, putting even the vaguest plan down on paper will help to make your ideas concrete! The benefit of having a plan on paper means you can consider if your plan and goals are realistic and you can decide as well how involved you want to be in social media marketing.How to Write a Social Media Marketing Plan Your first social media marketing plan need only cover 4 areas:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Foursquare Swarm – find 50 of your best friends in the one place</title>
      <link>https://damien1.github.io/social-media/foursquare-swarm-find-50-of-your-best-friends-in-the-one-place-1169/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jul 2010 21:19:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien1.github.io/social-media/foursquare-swarm-find-50-of-your-best-friends-in-the-one-place-1169/</guid>
      <description>Foursquare can be loads of fun for the casual user and collecting badges can be just as fun as trying to be the local town mayor. Foursquare has still to come up with a good tool for events, but it does have the Swarm badge.
Get 50 of your best friends to checkin at the same location at the same time … and you’ll get the Swarm badge too.
Are you using Foursquare or Gowalla?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Start a Social Media Marketing Plan – why you need to use social media?</title>
      <link>https://damien1.github.io/social-media/start-a-social-media-marketing-plan-why-you-need-to-use-social-media-1119/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jul 2010 09:00:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien1.github.io/social-media/start-a-social-media-marketing-plan-why-you-need-to-use-social-media-1119/</guid>
      <description>Starting your plan for social media marketing in a small or big business should be driven by a need or a reason.
Why use Social Media – because your customers are using it! First step in your social media marketing plan is to open powerpoint or write on a flipchart the reason why you need to use social media, some good reasons include:
 most of our target audience use social media (no brainer), or because visits to your brand or company website are down as our customers spend more time on social media sites (better) to deliver a sales &amp;amp; marketing programme using online &amp;amp; social media  There are probably plenty of other good reasons you can think of.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Start a Social Media Marketing Plan – why social media?</title>
      <link>https://damien1.github.io/social-media/start-a-social-media-marketing-plan-why-social-media-1113/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jul 2010 09:00:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien1.github.io/social-media/start-a-social-media-marketing-plan-why-social-media-1113/</guid>
      <description>Do you really need a Social Media Marketing Plan? And if your business needs a plan … why does it have to be social media?
Why Social Media Every business – big, small, startup or established brand needs to be using social media – yesterday. I was reading a flyer today which said ‘its critical for every website to include social media’ — its not the website that needs it … its your marketing and sales plan!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Start a Social Media Marketing Plan – don’t leave it to the PR person</title>
      <link>https://damien1.github.io/social-media/start-a-social-media-marketing-plan-dont-leave-it-to-the-pr-person-1108/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jun 2010 09:00:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien1.github.io/social-media/start-a-social-media-marketing-plan-dont-leave-it-to-the-pr-person-1108/</guid>
      <description>Social Media marketing – using Twitter, Facebook, LinkedIn, Foursquare, Google+ … needs to form part of any marketing plan across the marketing mix. Treating Social Media as a separate activity from the rest of your marketing is a No-No … In fact social media should be integrated into every campaign or promotion.
Social Media marketing fits into new customer acquisition, customer retention, CRM, customer loyalty and anything else that customers do and thats true for D2C brands as well as B2B marketers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best Collection of Tools for Twitter you Need</title>
      <link>https://damien1.github.io/social-media/best-collection-tool-for-twitter-you-need-1076/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jun 2010 23:16:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien1.github.io/social-media/best-collection-tool-for-twitter-you-need-1076/</guid>
      <description>Here’s a collection of the best tools for Twitter for any Social Media Specialist or Community Manager.
Twitter is a powerful tool for getting your message out there. Just like starting a new business, you need to have a guide that shows you how to make the most out of Twitter.**
**
Managing your Tweets Tweetdeck – http://www.tweetdeck.com/
set up lots of columns and lists to watch all your Tweeting</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>50 Completely Useful stats for social media &amp;amp; mobile marketing</title>
      <link>https://damien1.github.io/mobile-marketing/50-completely-useful-stats-for-social-media-mobile-marketing-1002/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 May 2010 16:27:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien1.github.io/mobile-marketing/50-completely-useful-stats-for-social-media-mobile-marketing-1002/</guid>
      <description>To understand more about Social Media and Mobile Marketing its important to get a few facts together on current trends and insights. 50 completely useful stats for social media does just that.
Why do this? well it helps to create some drive … and helps to understand why anyone or any business needs to do more in social media and mobile marketing.
**
**</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gowalla? Foursquare open for Business? Who will setup a business team in Europe First</title>
      <link>https://damien1.github.io/social-media/gowalla-foursquare-open-for-business-926/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 May 2010 08:00:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien1.github.io/social-media/gowalla-foursquare-open-for-business-926/</guid>
      <description>Foursquare is now open to business and is moving beyond geo-tagging and location based social networking. But is Foursquare really open to business? After trying to claim my business location and setup an offer for visitors its now been 3 weeks without a reply.
In the UK right now, I believe there is an opportunity for Gowalla, Foursquare, etc to setup a small but viable business team to work with digital agencies or mobile marketing specialists here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video &amp;amp; Integrated Marketing? Latest Internet Usage Video</title>
      <link>https://damien1.github.io/social-media/video-integrated-marketing-latest-internet-usage-video-562/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Mar 2010 10:46:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien1.github.io/social-media/video-integrated-marketing-latest-internet-usage-video-562/</guid>
      <description>Integrated marketing takes a new turn. This latest viral marketing video focuses on the state of the internetand is essentially a load of stats overlaid with a nice cheesy beat playing. All of the statistics are freely available metrics on social media usage, number of internet users, amount of spam mail. Integrated Marketing Viral Video – State of the Internet You have to watch the video first:
Even if you have watched this video infographic already and love it (yes I love it) watch it again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Foursquare Best Location Based Social Networking for Android UK Users</title>
      <link>https://damien1.github.io/social-media/foursquare-best-location-based-social-networking-455/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Feb 2010 18:56:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien1.github.io/social-media/foursquare-best-location-based-social-networking-455/</guid>
      <description>Android mobile owners in the UK will be pleased to know that location based social networkingapps have begun to improve and increase in the number of users. In the past few weeks, top location based social networks such as Brightkiteand Foursquarehave really improved the quality and details of UK locations.**
**
It is a problem of user experience that meant many of these services had few UK users and no UK points of interest.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What kids do online: UK Internet Usage</title>
      <link>https://damien1.github.io/mobile-marketing/what-kids-do-online-uk-internet-usage-444/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Feb 2010 12:56:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien1.github.io/mobile-marketing/what-kids-do-online-uk-internet-usage-444/</guid>
      <description>Recent indepth report from New Media Age in the UK focused on the internet usage habits of kids.
Kids research is hard – the age group is from 7 – 13. They are already exposed to a lot of marketing, aware of trends and ‘peer pressure’, but still very much aware of having to please their parents all of the time. It’s also very difficult to ask questions about anything anti-social, illegal due to the young age and formative, questioning minds.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to use Competitions &amp;amp; Social Media to grow your mobile marketing</title>
      <link>https://damien1.github.io/mobile-marketing/how-to-use-competitions-social-media-to-grow-your-business-399/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jan 2010 23:18:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien1.github.io/mobile-marketing/how-to-use-competitions-social-media-to-grow-your-business-399/</guid>
      <description>Running competitions using social media is a good way for brands and businesses to create welcome visitors and friends to their sites. You can now take that competition mobile using mobile apps, games or mobile websites and you don’t have to use SMS.
Using Social Media to get your customers discovering you on their mobile Your marketing messages on social media sites like Twitter and Facebook can direct existing customers to discover your mobile website or to download a mobile app.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vote in my Mobile Marketing and Mobile Apps Poll</title>
      <link>https://damien1.github.io/mobile-marketing/vote-in-my-mobile-marketing-and-mobile-apps-poll-379/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Dec 2009 13:59:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien1.github.io/mobile-marketing/vote-in-my-mobile-marketing-and-mobile-apps-poll-379/</guid>
      <description>Take a vote … what do you do for mobile marketing and have you tried any mobile apps?
http://polls.linkedin.com/p/69091/tbhgt</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Social Media &amp;amp; Marketing Round-up of some good reading</title>
      <link>https://damien1.github.io/mobile-marketing/social-media-marketing-round-up-of-some-good-reading-375/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Dec 2009 16:36:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien1.github.io/mobile-marketing/social-media-marketing-round-up-of-some-good-reading-375/</guid>
      <description>**The problem with doing research on social media and mobile marketing is the overwhelming amount of noise you get from doing searches on Google, Delicious and Twitter.
**
Here are a few links of really useful and easy to consume ‘research’
best ‘inspirational’ video on social media
http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=sIFYPQjYhv8map of social media world
http://www.flickr.com/photos/wasabibratwurst/3128711125/sizes/l/top 100 companies by media spend</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>