<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>General on Damien Saunders</title>
    <link>http://damien.co/categories/general/</link>
    <description>Recent content in General on Damien Saunders</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 May 2020 23:02:24 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://damien.co/categories/general/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello Hugo</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/2020-05-0-10-hello-hugo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 May 2020 23:02:24 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/2020-05-0-10-hello-hugo/</guid>
      <description>Welcome &amp;hellip; and say Hello to Hugo.
I&amp;rsquo;m sorry to say my love affair with WordPress is at an end. I moved on, and over the last few years, found maintaining my old site painful. It was time to move.
It&amp;rsquo;s not all WordPress fault - I&amp;rsquo;ve had continue problems of short outages after my web host was bought out by another company. After migrating to a new server, I lost all my sub-domains so WordPress Multisite was of no use.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019 Where am I?</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/2019-04-28-2019-where-am-i/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2019 16:56:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/2019-04-28-2019-where-am-i/</guid>
      <description>Hi there. Yes, it&amp;rsquo;s been awhile, but I&amp;rsquo;m back and just trying to figure out what I will do with this site.
In the meantime, social media and digital marketing has moved on; so most of my content is on Instagram. Don&amp;rsquo;t get me started about Twitter. Do people still use it? or just bots?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello 2016</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/hello-2016-9155/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Feb 2016 10:16:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/hello-2016-9155/</guid>
      <description>Hello - It&amp;rsquo;s been a long time and now I&amp;rsquo;m back.
Things are going to change around here and I&amp;rsquo;ll be writing more about my experiences with SharePoint 2013 and less on WordPress.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I&#39;m out of memory, but you shouldn&#39;t see it</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/2014-04-06-im-memory-shouldnt-see/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Apr 2014 15:02:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/2014-04-06-im-memory-shouldnt-see/</guid>
      <description>Well it&amp;rsquo;s happened - I seem to be hitting memory issues as a result of running too many WordPress sites on a shared hosting plan.
As a start to addressing this - I&amp;rsquo;m consolidating my sites and _may_ turn off WordPress multisite. I don&amp;rsquo;t really need it though it makes things easier to update one site rather than doing them one at a time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Isotope Visual Layouts lite new version out now</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/2014-02-04-isotope-visual-layouts-lite/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2014 22:47:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/2014-02-04-isotope-visual-layouts-lite/</guid>
      <description>Isotope Visual Layouts lite, my free WordPress plugin which adds animated grid layouts to your website has been updated.

What’s New in Version 3.0  Introduces Metro UI CSS to replace my own custom code Updates Isotope jQuery to latest version   Where can I get it? Isotope Visual Layouts lite is a free plugin – you just need to register and download.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Using a Netgear N600 DGND3700v1 to extend a home network</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/using-netgear-n600-dgnd3700v1-extend-home-network-8747/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jan 2014 23:36:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/using-netgear-n600-dgnd3700v1-extend-home-network-8747/</guid>
      <description>I’ve brought a brand new Asus RT-AC66U modem/router and decided that to use my old Netgear N600 ADSL modem/router DGND3700v1 to extend my home network and expand my wireless network.
I’ve put the Netgear in a room where there was poor wifi signal strength and used a powerline (ethernet over power) adapter to connect back to the new main connection.
To get the Netgear to behave like a wireless Access Point and extend my existing network should have been easy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Isotope Visual Layouts Pro &amp;#038; Infinite Scroll</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/2013-06-26-isotope-visual-layouts-pro-infinite-scroll/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2013 21:55:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/2013-06-26-isotope-visual-layouts-pro-infinite-scroll/</guid>
      <description>Check out this little clip of my Isotope Visual Layouts plugin for WordPress with Infinite Scroll … All this functionality exists in the Pro version of the plugin today.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Things to do post format with a dual partition Mac OSx #reformatted-my-mac</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/things-to-do-post-format-with-a-dual-partition-mac-osx-reformatted-my-mac-8655/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Apr 2013 15:29:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/things-to-do-post-format-with-a-dual-partition-mac-osx-reformatted-my-mac-8655/</guid>
      <description>So I had to do, what I had to do! and reformatted my Mac and now … I’m getting up in running again. I’ve been using Mac for a few years now and before that I’ve been used to running partitioned hard drives – it saves time when you reformat and usually means (touch wood) you can keep your user data safe from your OS.
 Critical Apps to Install and get up in running in no time  Immediately after logging in for the first time — I did the following …</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2012 Website Statistics &amp;#8211; Content Strategy is not buzz words like SEO</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/2012-website-statistics-awesome-8541/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2013 20:39:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/2012-website-statistics-awesome-8541/</guid>
      <description>2012 was the biggest year to date for web site visitors – and with good reason! So Thank You to everyone who came, read and left (and came back, again).
55,266 unique visitors clocked up 5.1 million seconds of visit duration but more importantly pages / visit and average visit duration also grew.
 So what happened in 2012? Search Engine Optimisation (SEO) didn’t work out … but having a content strategy did.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Isotope Visual Layouts &amp;#8211; How to change the default number of posts</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/2013-04-14-isotope-visual-layouts-how-to-change-the-default-number-of-posts/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Apr 2013 20:08:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/2013-04-14-isotope-visual-layouts-how-to-change-the-default-number-of-posts/</guid>
      <description>In my Isotope Visual Layouts WordPress plugin, you’ll find that Inline code documentation has been added to pretty much all the functions so just start by opening the main plugin file dbf_isotope.php and do a search for
function dbc_isotope_shortcode_handler($atts)Under that you just need to change posts=20 to posts=-1
Note .. this also applies to Visual Layouts Pro</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WordPress &amp;#038; MarsEdit &amp;#8211; schedule the future date of publishing bug</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/2013-04-14-wordpress-marsedit-schedule-the-future-date-of-publishing-bug/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Apr 2013 15:00:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/2013-04-14-wordpress-marsedit-schedule-the-future-date-of-publishing-bug/</guid>
      <description>I’ve been using MarsEdit for years and really like its features … recently I reformatted my Mac and now find that all my WordPress posts are being published immediately. Even after I set the date for ‘tomorrow’ for example.
By the way .. I’d love it if MarsEdit would add a text editor toolbar to make it easier to apply formatting styles like lists, headers or font styles.
 Small Bug – Set post date gets overwritten when you change post status I was getting annoyed and found that if I set the blog post date to ‘tomorrow’, then set the post status to published .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WordPress 3.6 beta 1 is here</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/2013-04-07-wordpress-3-6-beta-1-is-here/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2013 21:23:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/2013-04-07-wordpress-3-6-beta-1-is-here/</guid>
      <description>The first beta release of WordPress 3.6 is here and it’s time to get testing and checking things. I’m already getting excited about WordPress 3.6 as it brings a lot of focus on tools for developers and for WordPress admin section.
What’s changing in WordPress 3.6? The first beta candidate has been released. So we can now expect another beta and the then 2 or 3 RC ‘release candidates’. This means we’re not going to see any new surprises.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Death of Google Reader &amp;#8211; It&amp;#8217;s offline caching that makes RSS so good for me</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/death-of-google-reader-its-offline-caching-that-makes-rss-so-good-for-me-8448/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2013 16:44:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/death-of-google-reader-its-offline-caching-that-makes-rss-so-good-for-me-8448/</guid>
      <description>It’s what’s on the inside that counts! For me, what makes RSS a success has been mobile apps with offline caching. I don’t sit at home with my browser pointed to reader.google.com … I use mobile apps. Specifically, as I spend a lot of time on London Tube and trains where there is no wifi or mobile coverage, I need an RSS Feed Reader with a Cache!
It’s been great over the years to have Google Reader there for me as a bit of a research index, record keeper and generally more reliable than Delicious or pretty much any social bookmarking service.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Time for a service &amp;#8211; #reformated-my-mac-day</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/time-for-a-service-reformated-my-mac-day-8439/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2013 17:33:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/time-for-a-service-reformated-my-mac-day-8439/</guid>
      <description>Reformatting a computer is usually an emotionally distressful activity – involving losing files, trying to find software discs and panic about lost licence codes.
Over the years, I’ve reformatted and deleted many computers – kind of like giving your computer a semi annual service. As a result of noticing something not running right .. it just has to be done.
Today’s reformat went faster then I expected.
Reformat your Apple Mac and reinstall OSx operating system Once you are happy that you have moved all the files you think you want to keep … All you do is:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I feel like a kid in a candy shop &amp;#8230; #reformatted-my-mac-day</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/i-feel-like-a-kid-in-a-candy-shop-reformatted-my-mac-day-8433/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2013 12:19:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/i-feel-like-a-kid-in-a-candy-shop-reformatted-my-mac-day-8433/</guid>
      <description>
I woke up this morning .. it’s pouring with rain … my Apple MacBook Pro decides it doesn’t want to connect to my wifi.
So I had to do, what I had to do! and reformatted my Mac.
Now … I’m getting up in running again.
First things first ..
 Update my user preferences and move my home folder to the second partition (done) Download and Install Chrome (done) Download and Install Dropbox – point to my Dropbox folder on the other partition Download and install 1Password (done)  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why I use WordPress?</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/2013-03-06-why-i-use-wordpress/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2013 11:22:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/2013-03-06-why-i-use-wordpress/</guid>
      <description>Why use WordPress and Compare WordPress features sound like pretty SEO friendly keywords. Right? And if you’re new to WordPress, you’ll probably see many articles focus on three words – Free, Simple &amp;amp; Easy. These words tell you nothing about WordPress and so this is to help you decide to choose WordPress.
I started using WordPress in 2003 and I still have my hosted account London.WordPress.com. I switched to standalone or self-hosted in 2009 and from 2010, I’ve been running WordPress network or WordPress multisite.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HOW TO: Start, Stop, Restart or Reload Jenkins &amp;#8211; Mac OSx</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/how-to-start-stop-restart-or-reload-jenkins-mac-osx-8022/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2012 13:36:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/how-to-start-stop-restart-or-reload-jenkins-mac-osx-8022/</guid>
      <description>I’ve just started to use Jenkins as part of a continuous integration setup that I’m building. Mostly I’m doing this to learn and then apply this to something bigger. At home, I’m using Jenkins as a CI server to manage testing of my PHP WordPress plugins. I know it could be overkill, but as a one man band, automating testing is something that saves me time and increases my confidence that the development feature is tested and ready to deploy!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I&amp;#8217;m on WordPress Stack Exchange &amp;#8230; are you?</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/2012-10-07-im-on-wordpress-stack-exchange-are-you/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Oct 2012 14:56:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/2012-10-07-im-on-wordpress-stack-exchange-are-you/</guid>
      <description>You can join in the conversation with me and many others on WordPress Stack Exchange</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thank you &amp;#8230; 2000&#43; downloads of DBC Backup 2 for WordPress</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/2012-09-17-thank-you-2000-downloads-of-dbc-backup-2-for-wordpress/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Sep 2012 09:36:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/2012-09-17-thank-you-2000-downloads-of-dbc-backup-2-for-wordpress/</guid>
      <description>I want to say ‘Thank You’ to all of you who have downloaded and installed DBC Backup 2. Over the weekend, plugin downloads rose above 2000.
DBC Backup 2 makes it easy to safely backup your WordPress SQL database to a folder on your web server. It’s a unique solution which also includes regular, scheduled backups so that you can have a daily, weekly or monthly backup.
If you like DBC Backup 2 – please can you rate it 5 Stars on WordPress.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NEWS: Isotope Visual Post Layouts v0.32 just a bug fix</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/2012-09-16-news-isotope-visual-post-layouts-v0-32-just-a-bug-fix/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Sep 2012 20:50:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/2012-09-16-news-isotope-visual-post-layouts-v0-32-just-a-bug-fix/</guid>
      <description>Isotope Visual Post Layouts v0.32 was published to the plugins repository at WordPress.org on Sunday.
What’s in this release? v0.32 is a minor bug fix and apologies from me. It’s been one single bug that has plagued me since the first version of the plugin. It’s now fixed.
Filtrify – Add-on coming soon I’ve started work on my first add-in for Isotope Visual Post Layouts. This will be a feature you can purchase to include Filtrify drop-down menu (as featured on damien.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Axure &amp;#8211; responsive layouts &amp;#038; truly responsive nav bar</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/axure-responsive-layouts-truly-responsive-nav-bar-6563/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Apr 2012 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/axure-responsive-layouts-truly-responsive-nav-bar-6563/</guid>
      <description>Axure can be made to play responsively … here are 3 responsive browser widths and a truly responsive nav bar.
This is just a follow-up to an earlier post today on responsive layouts in Axure. It’s easy to make the nav bar responsive and even tested this with rotation. Pinch to zoom also gave some unexpected delight.
Updated for 4 responsive design layouts 10 April 2012 – The demo has now been updated to support 4 design layouts</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Top Posts March</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/top-posts-march-5265/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Apr 2012 08:39:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/top-posts-march-5265/</guid>
      <description>Well that was the end of March! So in case you were living underground here are the most popular posts that you missed from last month:
[wpp order_by=”views” pages=”0″ range=”monthly”]
and just a reminder … there are lots of updated presentations for you to view (and download) – including How to Get Started with Foursquare</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Top Posts February</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/top-posts-february-5263/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Mar 2012 09:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/top-posts-february-5263/</guid>
      <description>Well that was the end of February! So in case you were living underground here are the most popular posts that you missed from last month:
[wpp order_by=”views” pages=”0″ range=”monthly”]
and just a reminder … there are lots of updated presentations for you to view (and download) – including How to Get Started with Foursquare</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Top Posts January</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/top-posts-january-5261/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2012 09:37:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/top-posts-january-5261/</guid>
      <description>Well that was the end of January! So in case you were living underground here are the most popular posts that you missed from last month:
[wpp order_by=”views” stats_comments=0 stats_views=1 excerpt_length=55 excerpt_format=1 pages=”0″ range=”monthly”]
 and just a reminder … there are lots of updated presentations you view (and download) – including How to Get Started with Foursquare</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2012 is the year HTML5 will be on your CV</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/2012-is-the-year-html5-will-be-on-your-cv-6120/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2012 15:57:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/2012-is-the-year-html5-will-be-on-your-cv-6120/</guid>
      <description>This year, is the year that HTML5 will be on your CV. That is … if only you can prove what you did was in HTML5. Right now, I think that HTML5 is a bit of a catch-phrase (or catchy acronym?) when what we’re all doing uses a lot of .js and other familiar code frameworks.
HTML5 is not a new language – but it is visual Every project I’ve got so far this year will need HTML5.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Update on Maintenance Work</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/update-on-maintenance-work-5862/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2012 12:26:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/update-on-maintenance-work-5862/</guid>
      <description>Thanks for your patience while I had some work done to migrate my site to a new server.
The average page load time is now around 5 seconds as reported by Google Analytics – it had been floating between 12 – 20 seconds on various days last week.
So hopefully, we’ll have no more issues.
Cheers
Damien</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thank You &amp;#8211; 47% growth YOY &amp;#8211; 31,000 visitors and 14,000 presentation views</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/thank-you-47-growth-yoy-31000-visitors-and-14000-presentation-views-5859/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Jan 2012 22:16:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/thank-you-47-growth-yoy-31000-visitors-and-14000-presentation-views-5859/</guid>
      <description>What a year 2011 was … over 31,000 people visited my site which is a growth of about 47% year on year.
So thank you to all of you who came, read and left … and to the few of you who do come back again and again.
Google Analytics Web Trends I’ve been using Google Analytics since I moved to stand-alone WordPress in 2009. I support agencies and brands to develop complex reporting and engagement insights using Google Analytics.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Planned maintenance and work tonight</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/planned-maintenance-and-work-tonight-5851/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2012 18:58:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/planned-maintenance-and-work-tonight-5851/</guid>
      <description>Just a short note — Tonight there will be some planned maintenance and the wonderful team at Evohost will be migrating me to a newer, faster server.
The downtime will hopefully be kept as short as possible – but maybe come back on Saturday if you find anything funny.
Cheers
Damien</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Top Posts December 2011</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/top-posts-december-2011-2555/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2012 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/top-posts-december-2011-2555/</guid>
      <description>So that was 2011 … so in case you were living underground here are the most popular posts that you missed from last month:
[wpp order_by=”views” stats_comments=0 stats_views=1 excerpt_length=55 excerpt_format=1 pages=”0″ range=”monthly”]</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcome to 2012 &amp;#8211; You made it!</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/welcome-to-2012-you-made-it-5275/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2012 11:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/welcome-to-2012-you-made-it-5275/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to 2012 … and yes, you made it! There is no point in a retrospective, stuff happened and we learn from it. There is no point on pre-guessing what will happen, stuff happens and we react to it.
However you may want to look at it – we made it this far. It’s a new year, so enjoy it … while it lasts.
Thanks
Damien</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Merry Christmas to everyone .. make the most of it</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/merry-christmas-to-everyone-make-most-of-it-5401/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Dec 2011 13:23:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/merry-christmas-to-everyone-make-most-of-it-5401/</guid>
      <description>Merry Christmas … I found this quote recently and I think it’s quite funny and timely
~Richard Lamm
I hope you’re having a great day! wherever you are in the world – make the most of it.
Thanks for your support this year and hope to see you again soon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sorry about the bugs right now</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/sorry-the-bugs-right-now-5368/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2011 16:38:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/sorry-the-bugs-right-now-5368/</guid>
      <description>Dear Reader … Hello!
Sorry about the bugs that have been around for the past 2 days. At the start of this week I changed my caching solution and then I started to use a content delivery network.
The combination of both changes – and also having other things to do had led to a rather large ‘outage’ on Monday. Migrating content to the CDN is also still a bit problematic.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Most Popular Posts for 2011</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/most-popular-posts-for-2011-2557/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Dec 2011 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/most-popular-posts-for-2011-2557/</guid>
      <description>In case you’ve been wondering what’s popular here or maybe just looking for something else to click on … then here’s a few posts that seemed to be interesting with you out there…
So thanks! and enjoy the last of 2011.
Damien
  [wpp order_by=”views” pages=”0″ range=”all”]</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Top Posts November 2011</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/top-posts-november-2011-2554/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2011 11:26:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/top-posts-november-2011-2554/</guid>
      <description>Well that was the end of November! So in case you were living underground here are the most popular posts that you missed from last month:
[wpp order_by=”views” stats_comments=0 stats_views=1 excerpt_length=55 excerpt_format=1 pages=”0″ range=”monthly”]
 and just a reminder … there are lots of updated presentations you view (and download) – including How to Get Started with Foursquare</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Top Posts October 2011</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/top-posts-october-2011-2553/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2011 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/top-posts-october-2011-2553/</guid>
      <description>In case you were living underground here are a few of the most popular posts that you missed from last month:
[wpp order_by=”views” pages=”0″ range=”monthly”]</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It wasn&amp;#8217;t about design &amp;#8211; it was the first computer I used. Thanks Steve</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/it-wasnt-about-design-it-was-the-first-computer-i-used-thanks-steve-4444/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Oct 2011 09:32:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/it-wasnt-about-design-it-was-the-first-computer-i-used-thanks-steve-4444/</guid>
      <description>What was your first computer? The first computer I had regular use of was kept locked up in my school’s library. It was an Apple IIe with a green monochrome monitor. At 9 years of age, I was hooked.

Growing up far, far away where the most important news of the day was NZ losing its number 1 market for dairy and lamb as the UK joined the ‘EU’ – a piece of technology like the Apple IIe probably cost the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Required Summer Reading for startups &amp;#038; product development</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/required-summer-reading-for-startups-product-development-4263/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jul 2011 09:14:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/required-summer-reading-for-startups-product-development-4263/</guid>
      <description>If you’re about to head off for some sun – do pack these 2 books so you can say you seriously did some ‘work’.
Why Do I need to know these books? You need to know about current tools and the best practices as they are already appearing in many business plans, marketing strategy or new product definitions.
If you evaluate startups and are not getting a business model canvas then you should tell them to go re-write their business pan.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Social Media Marketing with WordPress needs a good theme</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/2011-07-04-social-media-marketing-with-wordpress-needs-a-good-theme/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jul 2011 15:02:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/2011-07-04-social-media-marketing-with-wordpress-needs-a-good-theme/</guid>
      <description>Get a good theme – it’s all about the instant appeal that any visitor has when they first land on your site. WordPress has many themes suited for social media marketing with a magazine layout, a featured panel and ready to go marketing plugins.
Why WordPress? WordPress is one of the world’s most popular solutions for blogging
If you’re reading and researching Why WordPress – you’ll probably see many articles focus on three words – Free, Simple &amp;amp; Easy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Top Posts June 2011</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/top-posts-june-2011-2549/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jul 2011 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/top-posts-june-2011-2549/</guid>
      <description>Ahh June … how we loved you … first it was drier then a dusty desert here in the UK, then wetter then wet and finally … So, In case you were living underground here are the most popular posts that you missed from last month:
[wpp order_by=”views” range=”monthly” pages=”0″ stats_comments=0 stats_views=1]</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MarsEdit updates &amp;#8211; best desktop blogging app for WordPress &amp;amp; Mac</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/2011-07-03-marsedit-updates-best-desktop-blogging-app-for-wordpress-mac/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jul 2011 14:58:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/2011-07-03-marsedit-updates-best-desktop-blogging-app-for-wordpress-mac/</guid>
      <description>MarsEditthe preferred desktop and offline blogging application for WordPress and Apple Macusers has updated.This is mostly a bug-fix release and the update will automatically install for most users.
What’s in this release? The release notehighlights a few good things for WordPress users such as:
 Media Manager now remembers and restores last-selected folder across launches Fix a bug that prevented custom text and background color preferences from working in rich text mode Add protections to avoid crashing on some malformed server responses Fix a bug where only the first paragraph was styled with e.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Comment is Free (again) thanks to Facebook</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/comment-is-free-again-thanks-to-facebook-3758/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jun 2011 10:52:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/comment-is-free-again-thanks-to-facebook-3758/</guid>
      <description>Recently I moaned about the state of comments and spam – and I hinted that comments would be enabled across my website again.
My interests in social media do extend to ‘the Facebook’ – but my expertise is definitely not with that network. Given a limited number of hours in each day, I have enough social media stuff to do.
Facebook Comments Only a few months back, Facebook launched their own comments system allowing external websites an easy way to integrate with Facebooks own commenting system.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Just Updated &amp;#8211; iTunes in the Cloud (beta)</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/just-updated-itunes-in-the-cloud-beta-3763/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2011 18:25:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/just-updated-itunes-in-the-cloud-beta-3763/</guid>
      <description>There’s a new update to iTunes this morning (evening in the UK) … iTunes 10.3 introduces in the Cloud beta. This was only introduced yesterday at the Apple WWDC.
The update is available for Windows and Apple computers now.
 What’s new in iTunes 10.3 Introducing iTunes in the Cloud beta. The music you purchase in iTunes appears automatically on all your devices. You can also download your past iTunes purchases.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Are you thinking what I&amp;#8217;m thinking? Two predictions for Steve Jobs?</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/are-you-thinking-what-im-thinking-two-predictions-for-steve-jobs-3752/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jun 2011 16:04:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/are-you-thinking-what-im-thinking-two-predictions-for-steve-jobs-3752/</guid>
      <description>Are you thinking what I’m thinking? It’s only a few hours til the start of the Apple WWDC which is ‘the biggest’ event in the year for Apple Fans.
Something borrowed or something blue? Apple, Lion &amp;amp; iOS5 Does Apple’s new software tickle your fancy? does the idea of conjoined operating systems for mobile and computers excite you?
Yeh I really want a touch-screen on my MacBook Pro – but that will never happen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Top Posts May 2011</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/top-posts-may-2011-2548/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2011 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/top-posts-may-2011-2548/</guid>
      <description>In case you were living under a rock – here are the most popular posts that you missed from last month.
There’s a lot here for Android which continues to grow in popularity.
[wpp order_by=”views” range=”monthly” pages=”0″ stats_comments=0 stats_views=1]
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Top Posts April 2011</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/top-posts-april-2011-2547/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 May 2011 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/top-posts-april-2011-2547/</guid>
      <description>Wow what a month! It might have been one of the hotest April’s in the UK – it certainly ended with one hot Wedding.
In case you were living underground here are the most popular posts that you missed from last month:
[wpp order_by=”views” range=”monthly” pages=”0″ stats_comments=0 stats_views=1]</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Twitter Weekly Social Media News for 2011-04-24 [LINKAGE}</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/twitter-weekly-social-media-news-for-2011-04-24-linkage-2899/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Apr 2011 10:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/twitter-weekly-social-media-news-for-2011-04-24-linkage-2899/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Twitter Weekly Social Media News for 2011-04-17 [LINKAGE}</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/twitter-weekly-social-media-news-for-2011-04-17-linkage-2876/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Apr 2011 10:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/twitter-weekly-social-media-news-for-2011-04-17-linkage-2876/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Twitter Weekly Social Media News for 2011-04-10 [LINKAGE}</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/twitter-weekly-social-media-news-for-2011-04-10-linkage-2864/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Apr 2011 10:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/twitter-weekly-social-media-news-for-2011-04-10-linkage-2864/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Twitter Weekly Social Media News for 2011-04-03 [LINKAGE}</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/twitter-weekly-social-media-news-for-2011-04-03-linkage-2816/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Apr 2011 10:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/twitter-weekly-social-media-news-for-2011-04-03-linkage-2816/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Twitter Weekly Social Media News for 2011-03-27 [LINKAGE}</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/twitter-weekly-social-media-news-for-2011-03-27-linkage-2805/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Mar 2011 10:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/twitter-weekly-social-media-news-for-2011-03-27-linkage-2805/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apple Aperture updates to 3.1.2</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/apple-aperture-updates-to-3-1-2-2803/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Mar 2011 16:57:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/apple-aperture-updates-to-3-1-2-2803/</guid>
      <description>Apple has updated its Aperture software to 3.1.2 – it seems to focus on the new users who quite likely brought the Appstore copy.
The release note is not very useful – but maybe the adjustments will be interesting to see what happens.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Twitter Weekly Social Media News for 2011-03-20 [LINKAGE}</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/twitter-weekly-social-media-news-for-2011-03-20-linkage-2797/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Mar 2011 10:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/twitter-weekly-social-media-news-for-2011-03-20-linkage-2797/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Twitter Weekly Social Media News for 2011-03-13 [LINKAGE}</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/twitter-weekly-social-media-news-for-2011-03-13-linkage-2796/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Mar 2011 10:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/twitter-weekly-social-media-news-for-2011-03-13-linkage-2796/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Twitter Weekly Social Media News for 2011-03-06 [LINKAGE}</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/twitter-weekly-social-media-news-for-2011-03-06-linkage-2795/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Mar 2011 10:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/twitter-weekly-social-media-news-for-2011-03-06-linkage-2795/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Top Posts February 2011</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/top-posts-february-2011-2545/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2011 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/top-posts-february-2011-2545/</guid>
      <description>February has not been a fun month – my website suffered a spate of catchable errors – a bit like a flu except more like an online virus.
In case you were living underground, here are the most popular posts that you may have missed from last month:
[wpp order_by=”views” pages=”0″]</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Twitter Weekly Social Media News for 2011-02-27 [LINKAGE}</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/twitter-weekly-social-media-news-for-2011-02-27-linkage-2-2793/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Feb 2011 10:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/twitter-weekly-social-media-news-for-2011-02-27-linkage-2-2793/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Twitter Weekly Social Media News for 2011-02-27 [LINKAGE}</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/twitter-weekly-social-media-news-for-2011-02-27-linkage-2792/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Feb 2011 10:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/twitter-weekly-social-media-news-for-2011-02-27-linkage-2792/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Remember to add my Google&#43; Page</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/remember-to-add-my-google-page-5395/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2011 20:39:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/remember-to-add-my-google-page-5395/</guid>
      <description>Now Google+ has launched pages for business … so if you’re using Google+ then please add Damien’s Google+ page.

I’ll be sharing the latest presentations and other news and marketing stuff only on my Google+ page.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Twitter Weekly Social Media News for 2011-02-20 [LINKAGE}</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/twitter-weekly-social-media-news-for-2011-02-20-linkage-2770/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Feb 2011 10:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/twitter-weekly-social-media-news-for-2011-02-20-linkage-2770/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Saturday Humour &amp;#8211; Procrastination</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/saturday-humour-procrastination-2737/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Feb 2011 10:55:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/saturday-humour-procrastination-2737/</guid>
      <description>procrastination-flowchart.png (1490×1188): “”
(Via lalawag.com)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Top Posts January 2011</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/top-posts-january-2011-2544/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Feb 2011 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/top-posts-january-2011-2544/</guid>
      <description>Here are the posts that you loved from January 2011 in case you were living underground for the past month:
[wpp order_by=”views” pages=”0″ range=”monthly”]</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Twitter Weekly Social Media News for 2011-01-23 [LINKAGE}</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/twitter-weekly-social-media-news-for-2011-01-23-linkage-2583/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jan 2011 10:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/twitter-weekly-social-media-news-for-2011-01-23-linkage-2583/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Twitter Weekly Social Media News for 2011-01-16 [LINKAGE}</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/twitter-weekly-social-media-news-for-2011-01-16-linkage-2569/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jan 2011 10:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/twitter-weekly-social-media-news-for-2011-01-16-linkage-2569/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Twitter Weekly Social Media News for 2011-01-09 [LINKAGE}</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/twitter-weekly-social-media-news-for-2011-01-09-linkage-2562/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jan 2011 10:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/twitter-weekly-social-media-news-for-2011-01-09-linkage-2562/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Your ideas are wanted for my next Slideshare Presentation</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/your-ideas-are-wanted-for-my-next-slideshare-presentation-2508/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2011 09:29:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/your-ideas-are-wanted-for-my-next-slideshare-presentation-2508/</guid>
      <description>Well hello Dear Reader
As you probably know – I really enjoy putting together a good presentation and publishing it on Slideshare— over the past year, I’ve averaged one presentation a month and managed to be featured on Slideshare 3 times.
So I’m looking for ideas on social media or marketing strategy or something else for my next presentation — and I’d like to have your ideas.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Most Popular December 2010</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/top-posts/most-popular-december-2010-2378/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2011 10:00:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/top-posts/most-popular-december-2010-2378/</guid>
      <description>December 2010 has been and gone … so it’s Happy New Year and welcome 2011. Just in case you were stuck under a rock for the past month, here’s a few of my most read posts.
[wpp pages=”0” order_by=”views” range=”monthly” stats_comments=0 cats_to_exclude=”1″]</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Most Popular Posts for 2010 a year in review</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/top-posts/most-popular-posts-for-2010-2386/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Dec 2010 10:00:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/top-posts/most-popular-posts-for-2010-2386/</guid>
      <description>**2010 has been and gone … so it’s time to welcome 2011. It’s been a busy year even though it had no deviation of its 365 expected length in days. I guess 2010 just had more tough days then easy days! What do you think?**
A Year in Review– 2010 the stats more than 24,000unique visitors from 153countries
according to Alexa.com my website ranks in the Top 5%of websites and currently sites around 836,000</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Today I&amp;#039;m a flag-waving, card-carrying Pom!</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/today-im-a-flag-waving-card-carrying-pom-2287/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Dec 2010 21:36:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/today-im-a-flag-waving-card-carrying-pom-2287/</guid>
      <description>Just in time for Christmas – after 6 years of being harangued at Passport Control, questioned a million times and having to cough up around a £1000 a year for the past 3 years, I can now say I’m a whinging Pom. 
And on my first day of being a Citizen of the United Kingdom — I was stumped by this piece of poor user experience design when applying for my British Passport.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Saturday Humour</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/saturday-humour-2155/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Dec 2010 09:42:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/saturday-humour-2155/</guid>
      <description>Here’s a funny one for all you budding entrepreneurs and lawyers.

Thanks to XKCD who do the best stuff on an almost daily basis!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apple&amp;#039;s iPad updates to multi-tasking &amp;amp; free find my iPad</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/apples-ipad-updates-to-multi-tasking-free-find-my-ipad-2064/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Nov 2010 09:00:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/apples-ipad-updates-to-multi-tasking-free-find-my-ipad-2064/</guid>
      <description>In case you have been under a rock since (Tues evening in the UK or Wed morning in Aus) or maybe in some foreign land so far far away from the Internet – let me be the first to tell you … the long awaited iPad IOS 4.2 is now available and it introduces at least 100 features. so now go away, find your iPad, plug it in to your computer and launch iTunes … if you don’t have an iPad but want one … then now you can go buy one  if you don’t have an iPad and are not interested in all things mac … ‘pfft’ i say to you</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Social Media News this morning November 24, 2010</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/news-releases/social-media-news-this-morning-november-24-2010-2068/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Nov 2010 08:01:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/news-releases/social-media-news-this-morning-november-24-2010-2068/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>20,000 visitors so far this year</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/20000-visitors-so-far-this-year-1995/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Nov 2010 09:29:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/20000-visitors-so-far-this-year-1995/</guid>
      <description>So its mid-November and I’m just looking at the Google Analytics report to see how I’m getting on. Data visualisation is a big thing but raw numbers are also pretty good.20,000 visitors so far this year generated 50,000 page views.
That’s pretty good for a one man marketing guy and his machine.
Alexa’s Web Information also seems interesting – and if you don’t know what Alexa says about your site .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Social Media News this morning November 22, 2010</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/news-releases/social-media-news-this-morning-november-22-2010-1998/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Nov 2010 08:01:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/news-releases/social-media-news-this-morning-november-22-2010-1998/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Saturday Funny &amp;#8211; a guide to the internet</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/saturday-funny-a-guide-to-the-internet-1875/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Nov 2010 10:37:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/saturday-funny-a-guide-to-the-internet-1875/</guid>
      <description>So how would you explain the internet to a 19th century Dickensian street urchin. Can you make it through the flowchart without being killed?

Source: FastCompany</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Her Majesty is on #Facebook</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/her-majesty-is-on-facebook-1966/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Nov 2010 09:08:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/her-majesty-is-on-facebook-1966/</guid>
      <description>Everyone loves a wedding – but does everyone need a friend??</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>POLL: How often do you Check-in?</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/poll-how-often-do-you-check-in-1941/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2010 23:04:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/poll-how-often-do-you-check-in-1941/</guid>
      <description>If you use Foursquare, Gowalla, Facebook Places, Rummble or Geomium — Then please vote. It’s only 1 click.
Let’s see if we are all obsessive about our checkins history or too cool for this crazy location fad!
// </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best iPad App for design and graphics gets better</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/best-ipad-app-for-design-and-graphics-gets-better-1857/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Nov 2010 10:59:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/best-ipad-app-for-design-and-graphics-gets-better-1857/</guid>
      <description>Sketchbook Pro, in my opinion is the best iPad app for photo editing, graphic and web design. And its new update just makes it better. The new release makes it a great all round tool for note taking, wireframe and web design.
A Power tool for notes, sketches and mockups I like to think I’m a pro digital photographer so I like my photo software to do amazing things – even if I cant.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Social Media campaign #ukuncuts shows people are not happy @Vodafone</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/social-media-campaign-ukuncuts-shows-people-are-not-happy-vodafone-1817/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Nov 2010 09:01:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/social-media-campaign-ukuncuts-shows-people-are-not-happy-vodafone-1817/</guid>
      <description>I’m going to copy here an opinion piecefrom the Guardian’s Comment is free section. It’s about a social media campaign related to the Twitter hashtag #ukuncuts which is impacting VodafoneUK — Vodafone has been facing protests &amp;amp; flashmobs in the past few weeks, something about 6 billion pounds and a few people think the UK Gov’t could do with the money.
Vodafone UK store in London Oxford Street forced to close</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WordPress Theme &amp;#8211; Continuum via Woothemes</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/wordpress/wordpress-theme-continuum-via-woothemes-1762/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Oct 2010 08:30:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/wordpress/wordpress-theme-continuum-via-woothemes-1762/</guid>
      <description>Some days I think a spring cleanis just as good for you as taking a holiday. Out with the old and give yourself some more space to create a mess.
Take for example this website – its built using WordPress and being very critical about the quality of my work or ‘portfolio’, I always want to be tweaking and changing my website and lookg at ways to make things better. So thankfully, today Woothemes(who I use with all my projects) came out with a new magazine layout that I’ve installed already.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Just installed Office for Mac 2011- first thoughts</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/just-installed-office-for-mac-2011-first-thoughts-1755/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Oct 2010 13:47:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/just-installed-office-for-mac-2011-first-thoughts-1755/</guid>
      <description>So .. Thanks to Amazon and Royal Mail at 730am I received my copy of Office for Mac 2011. Most obvious change is that the floating palette or toolbox is gone, replaced by the Ribbon which has been in Windows Version for a few years.
It now seems way way faster … Once one office app is open, the others open bleedingly fast. So they must now share more of a common backend.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>iWork &amp;#8211; Pages I don&amp;#039;t like</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/iwork-pages-i-dont-like-1687/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Oct 2010 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/iwork-pages-i-dont-like-1687/</guid>
      <description>I started the week with the ambition to just use iWork for a week. Today’s Tuesday and now I see the #failure of such a challenge.iWork Pages can’t convert Word documents so easily I’ve been sent a word document to review for a friend – that should be easy as iWork opens Microsoft Office Word .docx formats. The document opens ok … but the content has been placed into separate textblocks on the page just like any traditional desktop publishing app would do – but of course this was supposed to be a document that needed to be cleaned up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Challenge of the week &amp;#8211; Can I get by with iWork alone</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/challenge-of-the-week-can-i-get-by-with-iwork-alone-1680/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Oct 2010 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/challenge-of-the-week-can-i-get-by-with-iwork-alone-1680/</guid>
      <description>Having cleaned up my Macbook Pro and reformatted the hard drive … I’m going to spend the week using iWorkfor all my document needs. I’m a smart guy … I know I love Office for Mac(powerpoint makes any presentation look hot) – but maybe I can be doing sexy presentations in Keynote instead.So I’ve not got Office on my Mac and will let you know – I anticipate that I’ll be frustrated by Pages and its desktop publishing layouts but I should get used to that quickly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Insert Disc &amp;amp; Press Enter to Format</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/insert-disc-press-enter-to-format-1674/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Oct 2010 15:00:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/insert-disc-press-enter-to-format-1674/</guid>
      <description>Some old habits die hardand so last night I reformatted my 18 month old macbook pro. I had felt that it was starting to run a bit slow than ‘normal’ and I recently had a problem with a kernel panic (caused when testing a up to 21mb USB modem). So I have a ‘clean’ new computer and that has also given me a chance to think about what to reinstall.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Damien Saunders has some spare time</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/damien-saunders-has-some-spare-time-1670/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Sep 2010 15:00:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/damien-saunders-has-some-spare-time-1670/</guid>
      <description>Just keeping you up dated on work and availability – I’ll be back in London from 1 October and am available to come consult on your marketing strategy or work on those end of year projects that are kicking off now.So if you have a project coming up or maybe you are looking for some review or marketing strategy advice please get in contact.
Take a look at my profile on LinkedIn if you want to get an idea about my skills and competencies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WP Supercache &amp;#8211; were you seeing Garbage</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/wordpress/wp-supercache-were-you-seeing-garbage-1482/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Sep 2010 11:00:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/wordpress/wp-supercache-were-you-seeing-garbage-1482/</guid>
      <description>Sorry … I didn’t realise … my site has been having problems for a couple of weeks now. It turns out the WP Supercache a [ id=”693″ type=”post”]favourite WordPress[/] plugin was corrupting my site due to a conflict with my server compression.My Google Analytics bounce rate reports were quite high for the past couple of weeks and I didnt see anything was wrong until someone told me they were seeing garbadge on my website.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lithuania Youth love Basketball</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/lithuania-youth-love-basketball-1411/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Aug 2010 10:30:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/lithuania-youth-love-basketball-1411/</guid>
      <description>Lithuania is a basketball crazy nation – which may seem odd if you know little about this newer European Union state. Lithuania has had a long history with basketball even in the days of the Soviet Union (USSR).
Lithuania will also be hosting the Mens European Championships in summer 2011. Something to look forward too. I guess as the days grow darker and colder, indoor team sports like Basketball are good for the fans and the players.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lithuanian Youth love to use the Internet</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/lithuanian-youth-love-to-use-the-internet-1383/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Aug 2010 10:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/lithuanian-youth-love-to-use-the-internet-1383/</guid>
      <description>In Lithuania the usage of the internet is reaching saturation point. A 2009 official report shows 95% of young people aged 16-24 with internet access**.**
Lithuania has one of the highest per capita access to broadband ratios due to small land mass and population of just under 4 million. It’s also atypical of ‘westernised’ European markets and the Lithuanian youth are no different – wanting mobile phones, good clothes, good education and a future with a good job (most likely in London).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Damien Saunders examines Social Media in Vilnius Lithuania for a few months</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/damien-saunders-examines-social-media-in-vilnius-lithuania-for-a-few-months-1378/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Aug 2010 13:00:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/damien-saunders-examines-social-media-in-vilnius-lithuania-for-a-few-months-1378/</guid>
      <description>From: Our intrepid report
Location: Vilnius, Lithuania
Date: 8 August 2010
This could sound like the start of yet another long worded PR update with little to say and lots of flowery prose. Who I am to say if I write long winded rambling sentences with little or no meaning?
But anyway – I digress, Ill be working for a couple of months in Lithuania (yes in the East of Eastern Europe near the Baltic Sea).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HOW TO: View your WordPress Website on iPhone or Android</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/wordpress/how-to-view-your-wordpress-website-on-iphone-or-android-1343/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jul 2010 16:00:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/wordpress/how-to-view-your-wordpress-website-on-iphone-or-android-1343/</guid>
      <description>WordPressis a very comprehensive all-round tool for websites – and its not just for blogs. If you’re starting out with WordPress and need your site to look smooth on a mobile phone like the iPhone or any big screen Androidmobile then you’ll need a plugin for this.The best plugin for WordPress that handles any mobile device is easily WPtouch iPhone Theme. Once the plugin is installed and activated its working for you straight away.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HOW TO export posts from WordPress to Word Doc via PDF in Mac OSx</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/wordpress/how-to-export-posts-from-wordpress-to-word-doc-via-pdf-in-mac-osx-1335/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jul 2010 18:00:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/wordpress/how-to-export-posts-from-wordpress-to-word-doc-via-pdf-in-mac-osx-1335/</guid>
      <description>WordPress is one of the best end to end solutions for building a website and it has a large selection of themes, plugins and tools to make it more than just another blog. I recommend WordPress at the start of any project – just because it typically requires less management involvement or decisions from the IT or Tech teams to get started with.Having spent a lot more time writing about Social Media lately, I wanted to collect these posts into an editable collection (maybe I should have started by writing all my posts in word you might say).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Most popular posts for June</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/most-popular-posts-for-june-1178/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jul 2010 09:00:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/most-popular-posts-for-june-1178/</guid>
      <description>Summer is a peak time for social media marketing activity and there has been a lot going on. What have you noticed in the way of marketing around town?
Each month I try to look back and reflect a little on what was written and posted here. Here are the Top 3 posts by popularity from June.
 How to Use Twitter for your startup Essential Collection of ZOHO CRM resources Best Collection of tools for Twitter  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HOW TO Can’t Install Windows 7 upgrade with Virtualbox</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/how-to-cant-install-windows-7-upgrade-with-virtualbox-1088/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Jun 2010 14:16:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/how-to-cant-install-windows-7-upgrade-with-virtualbox-1088/</guid>
      <description>This is an extremely short guide to a major problem with Windows 7 using Virtualbox. Many users come to this site looking to find the answer – which is – Windows 7 Home Upgrade is sold in Europe and elsewhere as a full install version.
The problem is that installation via Virtualbox will complete but the user will not be able to ‘register’ their copy Windows 7.
The only way to install Windows 7 Upgrade using Virtualbox is to first install Windows XP and then run the Windows 7 Upgrade disc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>London Startup Weekend Day 2 Summary</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/london-startup-weekend-day-2-summary-1025/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jun 2010 10:21:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/london-startup-weekend-day-2-summary-1025/</guid>
      <description>Day 2: London Startup Weekend … Friday night’s ideas and pitch session, finished with 12 formative teams. When they arrived on Saturday this had started to change and a couple of teams merged.
Saturday morning we go down to work quickly with our mentor Raam CEO from Touchnote spending team with every team. In the afternoon Andrew Lockley came around to mentor and we were joined by Alex vanSomeren from the Cambridge entrepreneur scene.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I&amp;#039;m looking for a new project or work</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/im-looking-for-a-new-project-or-work-1020/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jun 2010 11:46:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/im-looking-for-a-new-project-or-work-1020/</guid>
      <description>So after things quiet down this weekend, I mean after London Startup Weekend has finished and the dust has settled … as of Monday, I’m a free agent looking for new work and a new project to get stuck into.
Given my all rounder background in social media and digital marketing … if you’re in need of someone who can move between planner, strategist, manager or something else then get in touch.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>London Startup Weekend starts in 2 days (insert panic now)</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/london-startup-weekend-starts-in-2-days-insert-panic-now-1016/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Jun 2010 15:30:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/london-startup-weekend-starts-in-2-days-insert-panic-now-1016/</guid>
      <description>London Startup Weekend, the 54 weekend event for anyone into startups or running their own business starts this Friday. Yes I’m going mental and about to have a breakdown. The weekend is going to awesome.
I’m running around organising food for everyone, organising drinks for everyone and every 2 mins it seems someone wants a new press release or post on the website london.startupweekend.org
My hats off to anyone who steps forward and says ‘Ill organise a 2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Review: Virtualbox 3.1 Beginners Guide</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/book-review-virtualbox-3-1-beginners-guide-962/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 May 2010 09:00:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/book-review-virtualbox-3-1-beginners-guide-962/</guid>
      <description>As far as book reviews go, from personal experience they are much harder to write then a review of a music album or live gig. So when reading VirtualBox 3.1 Beginners Guideby Alfonso V. Romero (Packt Publishing) I was surprised at how easy the book was to read and how an experienced VirtualBox user can dip in and find something new.
VirtualBox is one of my favourite system virtualisation apps that I use on my Mac and my Windows machines.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Virtualbox has a new how to book</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/virtualbox-has-a-new-how-to-book-918/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 May 2010 16:00:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/virtualbox-has-a-new-how-to-book-918/</guid>
      <description>Virtualbox – is my favourite tool for creating and running all things windows or linux on my mac. Installing Virtualbox on a mac with windowsis a breeze and its easy to run then having to reboot into bootcamp.
Now Packt Publishing have released VirtualBox 3.1: Beginner’s Guide this sample chapter is for Linux host machines. The book’s ambition is to ‘give you a thorough introduction to this award-winning virtualization product’. It will help you implement the right virtual environment for you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Skimlinks is working &amp;#8211; is it afiliate marketing or what?</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/wordpress/skimlinks-is-working-is-it-afiliate-marketing-or-what-911/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 May 2010 09:13:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/wordpress/skimlinks-is-working-is-it-afiliate-marketing-or-what-911/</guid>
      <description>I just added the Skimlinkswordpress plugin to my site. Skimlinks is my first step into affiliate marketing (is that what it is?). The wordpress plugin was very easy to install – but I think I should have read up more on affiliate marketing so it was over to the NMA magazine who recently ran an special on affiliate marketing to help me out.
In essence, affiliate marketing involves any 3rd party creating content that is linked to a product page and the affiliate gets a commission for the sale.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>London Startup Weekend June 4 &amp;#8211; 6 tickets on sale</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/london-startup-weekend-june-4-6-tickets-on-sale-905/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 May 2010 15:38:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/london-startup-weekend-june-4-6-tickets-on-sale-905/</guid>
      <description>**Damien Saunders is organising the next London Startup Weekend (http://london.startupweekend.org) @startuplondon which will take place June 4 – 5 – 6 2010 in just under a month at the IBM offices on London’s Southbank. Getting around to organising a weekend like this is taking up a little bit of my time .. but I believe in the concept and the cause – and its going to be a great weekend!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Android Markets – Going International – advice for developers, VCs &amp;amp; startups</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/android-markets-going-international-advice-for-developers-vcs-startups-874/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Apr 2010 15:00:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/android-markets-going-international-advice-for-developers-vcs-startups-874/</guid>
      <description>Developing for Android? You need to look to the bigger picture … actually this applies to anyone developing apps for mobile phones. If you want your app to be used by people that don’t speak English you need to translate it and provide some support.
There are going to be many opportunities for startups and anyone with a business model to go ‘international’ or expand abroad should check these points are covered in the marketing and product development plans.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zoho CRM best free web based CRM included in Google Apps Marketplace</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/social-crm/zoho-crm-best-free-web-based-crm-included-in-google-apps-marketplace-748/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Mar 2010 23:04:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/social-crm/zoho-crm-best-free-web-based-crm-included-in-google-apps-marketplace-748/</guid>
      <description>ZOHO CRM, which I reckon is the best free CRM for the web or SaaSis now available to add from the new Google Apps Marketplace.
(note if you’re already using ZOHO CRM with Google Apps you are better to leave things as they are for now)
What is CRM? Customer Relationship Management or CRM is really about 3 things:
 Building up knowledge on the people you do with business with or relate to – your clients, customers and the companies they work for Communicating with your customers and managing those ‘relationships’ Selling your stuff, or supporting your clients and staff to sell  In the past business process managers would have focused on Managing Customers as a key process for the Customer Lifecycle.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zoho CRM How to choose a Web Based CRM solution</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/social-crm/zoho-crm-how-to-choose-a-web-based-crm-solution-365/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Mar 2010 00:02:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/social-crm/zoho-crm-how-to-choose-a-web-based-crm-solution-365/</guid>
      <description>Inbound Marketers, Sales managers, customer care, account managers, business development managers – all need a good system for managing diaries, customer details and leads. Managing your sCRM using something like Zoho CRM means you have access to all your customer relationship data anywhere you are. And you don’t have to install anything on your Mac, PC or Linux operating system, just open your favourite web browser.
What is CRM? Customer Relationship Management (CRM) is an art and a science.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HOW TO fix the Fatal Error: Allowed Memory Size in WordPress</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/wordpress/how-to-fix-the-fatal-error-allowed-memory-size-in-wordpress-740/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2010 21:12:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/wordpress/how-to-fix-the-fatal-error-allowed-memory-size-in-wordpress-740/</guid>
      <description>WordPress offers lots of plugins to choose from and if you add to many you will soon come across this Fatal Error message. You can easily fix the problem (and then go back to adding more plugins).
This out of memory error doesn’t mean you have to go buy more RAM — just have to amend a line of text in a wordpress settings file.
Fix the Fatal Error: Allowed Memory Size  When you installed WordPress you either uploaded it using FTP yourself or went to an admin cpanel and installed it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HOW-TO install Ubuntu using Virtualbox on a Mac</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/how-to-install-ubuntu-using-virtualbox-on-a-mac-2-712/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Mar 2010 23:27:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/how-to-install-ubuntu-using-virtualbox-on-a-mac-2-712/</guid>
      <description>How easy is it to install Ubuntu on your Mac– this quick visual guide will have Ubuntu running within your Mac os X in under 20mins.If you’re really keen – maybe you want to use my guide on Virtualbox &amp;amp; install Windows XP on your MacGetting Started  Follow my instructions to download and install Virtualbox on your Macor Grab a copy of Virtualbox from virtualbox.org  Virtualbox Main Screen  Launch Virtualbox and click on New  Virtualbox Create New Virtual Machine for Ubuntu  Give your new virtual machine a name like Ubuntu Select Linux and Ubuntu from the drop downs  Virtualbox Set Memory  Set base memory to at least 1Gb.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WordPress: 9 Plugins for any new install</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/wordpress/wordpress-top-9-plugins-for-any-new-install-693/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Mar 2010 21:07:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/wordpress/wordpress-top-9-plugins-for-any-new-install-693/</guid>
      <description>WordPress provides a great tool to build and run your own website – it has 1000’s of plugins that add functionality to your website. Here then is a short list of essential plugins to get you started.Akismet Akismet is included in every installation of WordPress and so it make it one of the most popular plugins. There are better spam protectors, this doesn’t stop spam comments. You need a wordpress.com user name so that the plugin can sync over the internet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>February 2010 – Top Post</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/top-posts/february-2010-top-post-569/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Mar 2010 21:53:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/top-posts/february-2010-top-post-569/</guid>
      <description>Hi everyone
Here’s a short wrap up of what went down last month … more importantly what was popular reading.
 Why is Foursquare the best location based social network in the UK? 5 essential tips for mobile marketing when working with charities or NGO’s 10 best apps for your android mobile  I didn’t mention anything about Mobile World Congress as people like Ewan at Mobile Industry Reviewdid a far better job!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to install Virtualbox on a Mac</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/how-to-install-virtualbox-on-a-mac-533/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Feb 2010 14:48:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/how-to-install-virtualbox-on-a-mac-533/</guid>
      <description>This is 2 minute guide covering how to get Virtualbox and install it on your Mac. You would choose to use Virtualbox for 2 reasons
 Virtualbox is freeware in comparison to Fusion for Mac Virtualbox runs inside your Mac so you don’t have to reboot like Bootcamp  It’s been some time since I visited my favorite topic, which is using my Mac OSx Snow Leopard to run virtual operating systems like Tiny XP, Windows 7RC or Ubunutu.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Most Read Posts &amp;#8211; January 2010</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/most-read-posts-january-2010-426/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Feb 2010 12:18:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/most-read-posts-january-2010-426/</guid>
      <description>Top 3 posts for January 2010 that you loved to read the most were:
– How to install Virtualbox on your Mac with WindowsXP &amp;amp; TinyXP
– 10 Best Android Apps for your phone
– 10 Things to do with your Android and a Barcode Scanner</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gartner Says Consumers Will Download 4,500,000,000 Mobile Apps in 2010</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/gartner-says-consumers-will-download-over-4-billion-mobile-apps-in-2010-420/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Jan 2010 14:33:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/gartner-says-consumers-will-download-over-4-billion-mobile-apps-in-2010-420/</guid>
      <description>This week Gartner reported that consumers will spend a headline figure of £3.8 billion pounds ($6.2 billion USD) in mobile apps during this year. The forecast estimates total downloads to be 4,500,000,000. The numbers are eye wateringly large.
Gartners forecast goes on to mention that 82 per cent of downloads would be free apps … leaving 18 per cent of downloads to come up with cash.
4.5 billion downloads is quite staggering – even if Apple is set to announce its about to hit its 3 billionth download.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Android Market 3 of the Best Games</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/android/android-market-best-games-412/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Jan 2010 00:43:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/android/android-market-best-games-412/</guid>
      <description>Mobile Games for Android phones are now improving. The Android Market has a number of very good games that will help waste hours of your time. The 3 best and most popular Android mobile games are:
Robo Defense (free and premium) best tower defense game on the Android. Why? because your enemies don’t have a set route to follow. Its kinda like a long rugby or gridiron playing field and you have to stop them from getting to the other end.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to not impact your SEO and website traffic when changing WordPress Permalinks</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/wordpress/how-to-not-impact-your-seo-and-website-traffic-when-changing-wordpress-permalinks-406/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jan 2010 17:54:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/wordpress/how-to-not-impact-your-seo-and-website-traffic-when-changing-wordpress-permalinks-406/</guid>
      <description>Having made some changes to your wordpress permalinks, you can easily protect your web site traffic, SEO and search results from Google. This means you and your visitors get no 404 not found error.
This wordpress plug-in looks at the incoming link URL structure and then redirects on the fly to the correct post with the new permalink structure.
This didn’t make my list of Top 9 WordPress pluginsfor a new install – but if you are migrating a website this is critical.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>South Africa &amp;#8230; 5 million online and growing</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/south-africa-5-million-online-and-growing-403/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Jan 2010 18:22:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/south-africa-5-million-online-and-growing-403/</guid>
      <description>South Africa is one of the fastest growing markets for mobile and internet usage is also growing rapidly. A history of poor international bandwidth / connectivity has meant speeds have remained slow.
South Africa’s internet users grew from 4.6 million to 5.3 million last year, a rise of 15%, according to research by World Wide Worx, a technology and research and strategy organisation, sponsored by Cisco.
The climb follows years of stagnation between 2002 to 2007, when internet penetration in South Africa never rose above 7%.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello 2010 and www.damien.co</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/2010-01-07-hello-2010/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jan 2010 16:24:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/2010-01-07-hello-2010/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to my new look website &amp;hellip; I moved my site and I&amp;rsquo;m sure it looks a lot slicker and more aware of trends in social media
Best address for the new site is www.damien.co
any problems - please tweet me @damiensaunders</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best Apps for your Mac &amp;#8211; after a clean install</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/best-apps-for-your-mac-after-a-clean-install-372/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Nov 2009 15:41:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/best-apps-for-your-mac-after-a-clean-install-372/</guid>
      <description>So I have had to rebuild my Mac running OS X 10.6 Snow Leopard 3 times in the past 2 days after having problems with a t-mobile usb modem which corrupts the hard drive.Here’s the short list of my favourite, can’t live without em, just got to install them apps:
Best Apps for your Mac  ClamXav – still the best and most recommended free virus protection for your mac Adium – pronounced like stadium, this is the multi chat application for the mac Skype – for free calls to the office and home Dropbox – for sharing files between the office and clients Mac Office 2008 – word, powerpoint and to some extent excel, because all my templates are Office based and the guys in the office use PC’s.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Could it be Tesco Mobile selling iPhone? or just Tesco Supermarkets</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/could-it-be-tesco-mobile-selling-iphone-or-just-tesco-supermarkets-368/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Nov 2009 11:00:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/could-it-be-tesco-mobile-selling-iphone-or-just-tesco-supermarkets-368/</guid>
      <description>Sounds like good news in the UK market ‘opening’ up to more distribution channels for the iPhone. Tesco’s annouced it plans to start selling the iPhone by the end of the year and promised to add value to the market, where prices are stagnating between O2 and Orange.
What this means is that Tesco will be just another distributor like the Carphone Warehouse — and so at first, it didn’t seem clear if customers will have a choice of O2 or Orange.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>10 things to do with your Android and a Barcode Scanner</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/android/10-things-to-do-with-your-android-and-a-barcode-scanner-304/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Nov 2009 10:30:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/android/10-things-to-do-with-your-android-and-a-barcode-scanner-304/</guid>
      <description>There’s no better sound than the reassuring ‘Beep at the Checkout Register’. So now you have your own Android mobile phone …here’s a few barcode scanning things you can do at home or in the shops.
First you need the best Android Barcode Scanner – which now has integration with Google search on the mobile.
 Add a book to your Amazon Wishlist – just snap the barcode and save to list Catalogue your books at home using Anobiit from Anobii Catalogue your CD’s with Kooaba Look up reviews of that Wine you’ve just been drinking – Wine by the Bar is the perfect app for you Compare prices for that Electrical Gadget – Scan the Barcode and search online for it Create your own Barcode – After installing Barcode Scanner, open your Android Contacts .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to make mobile part of your marketing strategy</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/how-to-make-mobile-part-of-your-marketing-strategy-357/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Nov 2009 09:01:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/how-to-make-mobile-part-of-your-marketing-strategy-357/</guid>
      <description>Should you be worried that you don’t have an iPhone app? Do you know if you’re website works on a mobile? what about mobile SEO? It is very important for CEO’s and CMO’s to add mobile to their communications and marketing strategy.
The fact that most companies have yet to build a mobile website shows you are not alone and many companies want to know what they should do first.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sony Ericsson&amp;#039;s first Android phone</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/sony-ericssons-first-android-phone-352/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Nov 2009 10:46:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/sony-ericssons-first-android-phone-352/</guid>
      <description>Sony Ericsson delivered a blow to Microsoft on Tuesday when it unveiled its latest Xperia handset, which unlike its Windows-powered predecessors is based on Google’s Android operating system.
Called X10, the flagship smartphone comes with a new Sony Ericsson-designed user interface that aggregates the user’s contacts and communications from the likes of Facebook and Twitter into a single address book.
The system is akin to HTC’s Sense interface, and Motorola’s Motoblur interface, both of which feature on the respective companies’ new Android phones.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Does building an iPhone App make cents? sense?</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/does-building-an-iphone-make-cents-sense-348/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Nov 2009 19:36:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/does-building-an-iphone-make-cents-sense-348/</guid>
      <description>With the boom in the number of apps in the App Store (over 100,000) and total downloads in excess of 2bn … someone has got to be making money … right?In part, the iPhone does offer a better platform for apps – it’s about to overtake RIM as the leading consumer smartphone, sold more than 34 million units and got some of the highest mobile internet usage rates we’ve seen so far.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Giving Great Service &amp;#8211; learning from Turkey&amp;#039;s positive over employment</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/giving-great-service-learning-from-turkeys-positive-over-employment-342/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Oct 2009 15:04:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/giving-great-service-learning-from-turkeys-positive-over-employment-342/</guid>
      <description>Excellence in customer service is one thing that Turkey can be proud of. As a direct result of years of high unemployment businesses and individuals are finding ways to ‘add value’ and earn a few Lira. There are many positiv arguments for employing people in ‘low paid’ jobs that improve everyones living.
It’s been 2 years since I was living in Istanbul. I’ve returned for a week and was looking out for signs of the impact of the ‘credit crunch’.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is Android Lagging Behind in Sales? Not Likely</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/android/is-android-lagging-behind-in-sales-not-likely-338/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Oct 2009 15:10:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/android/is-android-lagging-behind-in-sales-not-likely-338/</guid>
      <description>Recently the blogosphere has gone a bit crazy, excuse my lack of hyperbole about the Android platform. Was this ‘Android’ supposed to do battle with the iPhone?
Just because no operators or manufacturers have openly commented about their smart phone sales figures doesn’t mean its bad news. Looking at the number of Android powered phones out now or due in the next 2 months shows a lot of promise
 HTC Hero – some bloggers say it’s the best Android yet G1 – the funny one with the flip out keyboard, still only with T-Mobile Magic – Vodafone took this and the Android platform global Tattoo – coming out again to Vodafone before xmas Motorola DEXT – a lifesaver for Motorola – probably the phone that saves them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MacOSx Converts: XNJB get your Creative audio player to charge on a Mac</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/macosx-converts-xnjb-get-your-creative-audio-player-to-charge-on-a-mac-331/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Oct 2009 15:05:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/macosx-converts-xnjb-get-your-creative-audio-player-to-charge-on-a-mac-331/</guid>
      <description>XNJB: is the app of the day for people who have used MP3 players from Creative technology. Moving to a Mac I was at a lose as to how to copy music to my Creative Zen and how to charge my Creative on my Mac.
This is where XNJB comes to the rescue and lets you copy music or charge your Creative while running Mac OSX 10.6 Snow Leopard.
XNJB should be bundled with Creative Media Players … after all these years and all the marketing hype around the Mac not having official support for Mac is sometimes a death knell or ‘dirge’ for any brand.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>App of the day: Balsamiq &amp;#8211; wireframing and user experience design</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/app-of-the-day-balsamiq-wireframing-and-user-experience-design-328/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Sep 2009 13:48:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/app-of-the-day-balsamiq-wireframing-and-user-experience-design-328/</guid>
      <description>Balsamiq – I love it – the fonts and stuff can seem a bit cheesy … but I’ve take to this like a duck to water. Its much more useful than powerpoint, visio or other tools as its designed for wireframing.
Being built on Adobe Air means anyone can use it.
It’s very quick to create a UE design and while I couldn’t find a template or mockup for cell phone / mobile phone.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>An Apple a Day &amp;#8230; more operators to sell iPhone</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/an-apple-a-day-more-operators-to-sell-iphone-325/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Sep 2009 16:00:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/an-apple-a-day-more-operators-to-sell-iphone-325/</guid>
      <description>Following on yesterday’s news that Orange Uk will start selling iPhone … ending O2 / Telefonica’s virtual monopoly in the UK. Today, Vodafone in UK and Ireland announced their plans to sell Apple iPhones.
Good news for the operators? well ending the monopoly of iPhone was a good move. An operator with a data usage strategy will want to be selling iPhones along side other data hungry phones like RIM, Android, Symbian devices.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tip of the Day: Windows Vista SP2 won&amp;#039;t install on a partitioned drive</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/tip-of-the-day-windows-vista-sp2-wont-install-on-a-partitioned-drive-320/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Sep 2009 15:18:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/tip-of-the-day-windows-vista-sp2-wont-install-on-a-partitioned-drive-320/</guid>
      <description>Tip of the day: Windows Vista clean install doesn’t work on a partitioned drive AND if you then partition the drive after installing Vista, the SP2 will not install as well.
Effectively this means you should keep your primary drive as 1 partition … or wait til after you’ve installed Vista and all the service packs.
There is a short microsoft kb on this ….
Will this affect installing Windows 7 for the same reason … I think so.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Orange UK to get Apple</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/orange-uk-to-get-apple-314/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2009 13:34:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/orange-uk-to-get-apple-314/</guid>
      <description>Apple’s iPhone will be available to Orange customers in the UK later this year, ending rival O2’s exclusive deal over the must-have handset, the mobile operator said.
The announcement by Orange ends months of speculation that it was trying to muscle in on O2’s deal with Apple, which gave it exclusive UK rights to the iPhone in 2007. The 3G and 3GS versions will be available to Orange UK customers “later this year”, but no further details of dates, handset costs or tariffs are available yet, the firm said.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3 rewards customers who get customers</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/3-rewards-customers-who-get-customers-312/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2009 13:29:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/3-rewards-customers-who-get-customers-312/</guid>
      <description>From today 3 UK will reward customers with cashback for referrals.
Join 3’s Free Agent team and get paid for promoting our free SIMs online. You get £5 cash when each friend first tops up their SIM by a minimum of £10, and they get an extra £2 credit. There’s no limit to the amount of money you can make.
see also: http://freeagent.three.co.uk/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New UK MVNO before Christmas &amp;#8211; Giffgaff to offer free calls</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/new-uk-mvno-before-christmas-giffgaff-to-offer-free-calls-310/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2009 09:57:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/new-uk-mvno-before-christmas-giffgaff-to-offer-free-calls-310/</guid>
      <description>Giffgaff will reward subscribers with cash rebates when they distribute its SIMs, help other members via its forums and suggest ideas which are then implemented by the company.
source: http://www.nma.co.uk/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mac OSx Convert &amp;#8211; Office tip move between documents</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/mac-osx-convert-office-tip-move-between-documents-308/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Sep 2009 23:47:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/mac-osx-convert-office-tip-move-between-documents-308/</guid>
      <description>Here’s a quick one for you … how do you switch between a number of open documents in Word or Excel?
The quick Mac way is CMD + `
The Windows Office way was Pressing F6
If you still want to do this … on the Mac then you have to press FN + Shift + F6</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mac OSx Convert Tip of the Day &amp;#8211; Screenshots</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/mac-osx-convert-tip-of-the-day-screenshots-302/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Sep 2009 18:51:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/mac-osx-convert-tip-of-the-day-screenshots-302/</guid>
      <description>The snipping tool has to be one of the best features introduced into Windows Vista (except for the nasty red line around the pictures). PRT-SCRN is now a thing of the past. But what do you do when your Mac doesnt even have a PRT SCRN key? Press any key ? ? ? ?
CMD+SHIFT+4 is the combination to remember .. and then press the space bar if you want a screen shot of the current window</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Group Review: Manage your CD library collection on a Mac</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/cd-library-management-283/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Sep 2009 19:54:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/cd-library-management-283/</guid>
      <description>Now that you’ve ripped and digitised all of your CD library – what do you do with your CD’s? One idea is to create a catalogue and then you can box or put away (or recycle) your CD’s and DVD’s giving you much more space to fill with books, CD’s or other stuff.If you’re like me, I’ve been ripping all my CD’s for years and the CD and cases were just collecting dust in my room.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mac OSx Convert Tip of the Day &amp;#8211; keyboard shortcuts</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/mac-osx-convert-tip-of-the-day-keyboard-shortcuts-287/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Sep 2009 19:26:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/mac-osx-convert-tip-of-the-day-keyboard-shortcuts-287/</guid>
      <description>The Mac OSx Convert has been reading up various selections of 101 of the best (or worst) OSx tips. Many of these tips don’t address the Keyboard shortcuts … on the newer Macbooks first tip is always press the Fn key to access function keys in the top row.
Best tip of the day … here’s a long list from Apple of the Keyboard Shortcuts
http://support.apple.com/kb/HT1343</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Virtualbox 3.0.4 Mac OSx How to share folders</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/virtualbox-3-0-4-mac-osx-how-to-share-folders-274/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Aug 2009 20:07:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/virtualbox-3-0-4-mac-osx-how-to-share-folders-274/</guid>
      <description>Virtualbox 3.0.4 is a new update released earlier this month. After updating to this new version file sharing between mac os and the guest windows vista has stopped working.
Something wonderful has happened and there is a new feature that has been added … Under the Devices Menu there is a new entry for “Sharing Folders” – you can now create shared folders in realtime
However to make the shared folders work you still must use the old method of mapping a network drive and remember to type your shared folder name as</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google Wave will it change SMS Texting and Instant Messaging</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/google-wave-will-it-change-sms-texting-and-instant-messaging-195/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Aug 2009 14:45:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/google-wave-will-it-change-sms-texting-and-instant-messaging-195/</guid>
      <description>Will Google Wave change SMS texting and instant messaging? Most likely … but that’s about the best answer right now. Google will have to find partners to help ‘aggregate’ chat and email and address Internet infrastructure issues in a number of countries.
Thanks to Googles reach, Wave can launch and get a good penetration into its addressable Gmail base. It’s all looking good with a Public Beta? of 100,000 invites due to be sent out in September.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tip from a Windows Convert: Office for Mac &amp;#8211; Excel Keyboard Shortcut</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/tip-from-a-windows-convert-office-for-mac-excel-keyboard-shortcut-269/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Aug 2009 12:12:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/tip-from-a-windows-convert-office-for-mac-excel-keyboard-shortcut-269/</guid>
      <description>I’ve been using keyboard shortcuts for Microsoft Office on Windows for years. So here I am now using Mac Office on a Macbook Pro and still trying to figure out how to get around the keyboard.Tip of the Day – Windows Excel Alt+Enter and in Mac Office Excel keyboard shortcut is Fn+Ctrl+Alt
This adds a carriage return within the current cell and its great for doing long text entry in 1 cell.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Comparison of Digital Music Retailers in Europe</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/comparison-of-digital-music-retailers-in-europe-246/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Aug 2009 17:28:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/comparison-of-digital-music-retailers-in-europe-246/</guid>
      <description>Comment: There are a number of digital music retailers working around Europe, here is Damien Saunders’ summary of a few of the bigger services (catalogue greater than 1 million tracks).
&amp;lt;td width=&amp;quot;75&amp;quot;&amp;gt; Countries &amp;lt;/td&amp;gt; &amp;lt;td width=&amp;quot;75&amp;quot;&amp;gt; MP3 to buy &amp;lt;/td&amp;gt; &amp;lt;td width=&amp;quot;79&amp;quot;&amp;gt; Subscription &amp;lt;/td&amp;gt; &amp;lt;td width=&amp;quot;75&amp;quot;&amp;gt; Catalogue Size &amp;lt;/td&amp;gt; &amp;lt;td width=&amp;quot;75&amp;quot;&amp;gt; 3rd Party API &amp;lt;/td&amp;gt; &amp;lt;td width=&amp;quot;75&amp;quot;&amp;gt; PC Software &amp;lt;/td&amp;gt;  &amp;lt;td width=&amp;quot;75&amp;quot;&amp;gt; UK &amp;lt;/td&amp;gt; &amp;lt;td width=&amp;quot;75&amp;quot;&amp;gt; Yes &amp;lt;/td&amp;gt; &amp;lt;td width=&amp;quot;79&amp;quot;&amp;gt; No &amp;lt;/td&amp;gt; &amp;lt;td width=&amp;quot;75&amp;quot;&amp;gt; 3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Content Providers &amp;amp; Digital New Media Players</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/content-providers-digital-new-media-players-242/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Aug 2009 10:27:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/content-providers-digital-new-media-players-242/</guid>
      <description>Content Providers, Content Partners, Service Providers or Content Delivery – there is a long list of terms that you can be searching for on the internet to get you a list … but is there a consolidated list of whos who in the industry? Here’s just a few:
Arvato– (Europe)
Buongiorno– (Europe)
Fonestarz– (Head office is based in the UK)
Fox Mobile– (Germany) aka Jamba&amp;amp; Jamster
mmCHANNEL (Spain)
Musiwave– (France)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2 must have Android Apps to manage wifi</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/2-must-have-free-android-apps-to-manage-wif-219/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jul 2009 15:30:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/2-must-have-free-android-apps-to-manage-wif-219/</guid>
      <description>Have you just got a new HTC Magic? or waiting for the HTC Hero to come out? Here are 2 must have apps to get for free from the Android Market to manage your wifi and data connections
Wefi – Manage your battery life and wi-fi connectivty
Turn it on to see if there are free networks around you – once its found somewhere, it will login if its free or tell you it needs a password.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2 Must have Android Apps from Google</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/2-must-have-android-apps-from-google-for-your-htc-magic-or-g1-226/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2009 18:11:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/2-must-have-android-apps-from-google-for-your-htc-magic-or-g1-226/</guid>
      <description>Looking for somewhere to go …. Maybe you need to waste some time or want to find something else to try on your Google Android G1 or HTC Magic.
Google obviously has embedded a lot things into the phone – but here are 2 apps that were not installed on the Android phone when you open the box.
Places DirectoryPrice FREE Downloads &amp;gt;250,000
updated — 21 Sept –– Even before augmented reality became a buzzword … Google Places Directory was already bringing Google Maps together with GPS / Location Based Services.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Upgrading to Virtualbox 3.0 and Mac OSx hosts</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/upgrading-to-virtualbox-3-0-and-mac-osx-hosts-222/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2009 14:45:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/upgrading-to-virtualbox-3-0-and-mac-osx-hosts-222/</guid>
      <description>Assuming you have been using Virtualbox before, then the upgrade process to Virtualbox 3 is going to be easy and smooth sailing.
For first time users of Virtualbox or in fact virtualisation who are using a Mac OSx then you should read my earlier posts on how to get going. These are:
  15 minute guide to running Windows 7 RC on a Mac and
  How to install Virtualbox on a Mac using Windows TinyXP</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blow out the candles &amp;#8211; Happy 1st Birthday Apple Apps Store</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/blow-out-the-candles-happy-1st-birthday-apple-apps-store-213/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jul 2009 20:55:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/blow-out-the-candles-happy-1st-birthday-apple-apps-store-213/</guid>
      <description>So its Happy Birthday to Apple and its App Store – 1 year old. Its created a new industry and probably will change the way everyone digests content – now that everything has an app or a widget you dont need to browse for it.
Except for Search – Apple and the Apps store has changed how mobile phone manufacturers think about content like Nokia, RIM and Sony Ericsson all launched (or launching) app stores in the past 3 months.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>In the future (avoiding trends) and how to write about it</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/in-the-future-avoiding-trends-and-how-to-write-about-it-198/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jun 2009 12:21:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/in-the-future-avoiding-trends-and-how-to-write-about-it-198/</guid>
      <description>when writing about or thinking about the future start by writing these words ‘in the future’ or maybe ‘Wouldn’t it be cool, if in the future’.
Remember back at school doing free writing or projects on people in space. Teachers would always get you to write about the future and using the phrase ‘in the future’ sets you directly to writing about that.
So thinking about the future is not about tomorrow, next month or next year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Aging music lovers what happens when we are 80?</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/aging-music-lovers-what-happens-when-we-are-80-191/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 May 2009 15:26:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/aging-music-lovers-what-happens-when-we-are-80-191/</guid>
      <description>In a few years time, many of us will want to retire … what’s going to happen to us and our communities we live in if suddenly todays 20 and 30 somethings are 80? What music or digital entertainment will there be? Remembering also that as we start ‘age’ we will have to work later in life beyond today’s retirement age.If, the aging population is bigger than the younger generation – does that mean nightclubs, discos and places like Ibiza will become the place for the 70+ age group?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>15 minute guide to Virtualbox Windows 7 RC1 and your Mac</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/15-minute-guide-to-running-windows-7-rc1-on-a-mac-180/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 May 2009 20:05:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/15-minute-guide-to-running-windows-7-rc1-on-a-mac-180/</guid>
      <description>So this follows an earlier post of mine about Virtualbox and running Windows XP on a Macbook Pro. Virtualbox is a great piece of software for running virtual operating systems on another machine (like runing Windows 7 on a Mac OSX).Today’s guide shows that you can be up n running with Windows 7 RC in about 15 minutes … thats got to be good ??
So Grab your Windows 7 RC1 ISO file from the Windows website, grab a copy of Virtualbox for Mac and get going.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Decline of the music industry &amp;#8230; is there a decline?</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/decline-of-the-music-industry-is-there-a-decline-177/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 May 2009 13:57:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/decline-of-the-music-industry-is-there-a-decline-177/</guid>
      <description>.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>shhh &amp;#8211; HTC Magic just lacks the Volume for a music phone</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/shhh-htc-magic-just-lacks-the-volume-for-a-music-phone-172/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 May 2009 11:27:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/shhh-htc-magic-just-lacks-the-volume-for-a-music-phone-172/</guid>
      <description>The HTC Magic came out recently, so far its a exclusive to Vodafone. As a phone it has all the features you could desire, but its music player needs an over hall – first problem is the volume, its just too quiet.In a crowded room, on the London Tube or just working out at a gym the volume from the HTC Magic’s is just a whisper of what it should be – or am I going deaf?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Android Market Best of Apps you must have</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/android-market-best-of-apps-you-must-have-166/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Apr 2009 21:23:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/android-market-best-of-apps-you-must-have-166/</guid>
      <description>29 Sep 09: This is the better post to read: http://damien.co/2009/08/11/10-best-android-apps-for-your-phone/
Ok I’ve been using an HTC Magic for a few days now and I’m loving it … I’m so hooked I could almost get myself kicked out of the house, or have my ‘beautiful &amp;amp; precious’ phone smashed 🙁Here’s what you too should try there are so many free Apps in the Android Market that you can’t get bored. Given how much I use a phone and my focus on the mobiles and music, heres a choice selection</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We are watching you and reading your texts and emails</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/we-are-watching-you-and-reading-your-texts-and-emails-95/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Apr 2009 20:13:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/we-are-watching-you-and-reading-your-texts-and-emails-95/</guid>
      <description>The UK for along time has been a country full of honours and award systems — the most CCTV cameras comes to mind and from today it seems that the UK Government believes that for your safety, they will need to record details and the contents of every SMS, email, voicemails and phone calls.
How afraid are we all becoming?
source: http://www.guardian.co.uk/commentisfree/libertycentral/2009/apr/27/surveillance-data-protection</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nokia S60 Symbian Best Apps you should have</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/nokia-s60-symbian-best-apps-you-should-have-162/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Apr 2009 13:40:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/nokia-s60-symbian-best-apps-you-should-have-162/</guid>
      <description>I’ve been using Nokia’s for a while now – N95, N95 8Gb and the E71
Here’s the top apps I put on any phone when I set it up
Vodafone Last.fm Scrobbler – gee I ‘made’ this .. but I love it so. Scrobble what you listen to while out n about, underground or overseas, check your charts and what your friends are up to. This s60 app is fuly symbian signed and tested on a number of Vodafone networks – and its the only scrobbler for the Nokia 5800 so far.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tips on Changing Settings for Virtualbox on a Mac Laptop</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/tips-on-changing-settings-for-virtualbox-on-a-mac-laptop-159/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Apr 2009 20:12:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/tips-on-changing-settings-for-virtualbox-on-a-mac-laptop-159/</guid>
      <description>This covers basic settings on a Mac Laptop Intel running osx … Running Virtualbox, the freeware virtualisation software on any computer can be easy – and there are a number of internet based support forums. Getting your head around the settings for Virtualbox can be a bit harder.
Virtualbox is configurable from its GUI interface and also has a larger set of command line options, which are all covered in the userguide on the Virtualbox download site</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Datz makes downloading unlimited DRM free music hard</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/datz-makes-downloading-unlimited-drm-free-music-hard-110/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2008 10:36:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/datz-makes-downloading-unlimited-drm-free-music-hard-110/</guid>
      <description>Comment: Datz music lounge has come out for Xmas in the UK with a £99.99 unlimited music DRM free offer. So whats the hooks … plenty even before you get going.
So Datz announced unlimited DRM Free music downloads (legally) this week … the service has an upfront fee of £99.99 – probably too steep for most people to consider – but maybe Sainsburys thinks it will be a last minute stocking stuffer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bill Gates &amp;amp; Jerry Seinfeld &amp;#8211; everyones blogging that video</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/bill-gates-jerry-seinfeld-everyones-blogging-that-video-101/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2008 18:34:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/bill-gates-jerry-seinfeld-everyones-blogging-that-video-101/</guid>
      <description>You can try to avoid watching this advert all you want – but you just got to know what it is that Bill and Jerry cooked up here in the Shoe Circus – Windows Vista advert
.
Really does the ad say much – No … Does it try to convince you to switch – No … but maybe its a brand ad and not a product ad
Lots of talk of quality, runs tight, last, endurance and other words in the ad – so maybe you’ll see them more in the ‘product ads’ when they come out?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sony Ericsson does chunky retro Walkman W902</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/sony-ericsson-does-chunky-retro-walkman-w902-99/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2008 13:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/sony-ericsson-does-chunky-retro-walkman-w902-99/</guid>
      <description>I’ve had a look at the Sony Ericsson new Walkman W902 with retro chunky buttons much like a those on a casette walkman.
The phone’s not retro though – Clear Crystal Audio for your listening pleasure and a 5.0 mega pixel camera is a great feature. I think its also got a really good speaker to annoy Grannies on the bus with.
I hope it comes out with more than a 1Gb of memory!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ill move to Linux thanks Amarok</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/2008-08-14-ill-move-to-linux-thanks-amarok/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2008 09:06:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/2008-08-14-ill-move-to-linux-thanks-amarok/</guid>
      <description>Damien says, one of the biggest problems with Linux has always been a lack of strength in its media players. Amarok v2 is now in the pipe and its looking great.
The Amarok 1 client which most Linux users had to use (it was the best option) really lacked in its options for managing artists, albums, compilations as it relied on a database driven columns view. I never found that easy to use.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Whats your media player?</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/whats-your-media-player-88/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Aug 2008 20:18:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/whats-your-media-player-88/</guid>
      <description>I’m starting a reader survey on Media Players – as there are a few assumptions I wanted to prove or understand.
  If you have an iPod, iPhone or iTouch you use iTunes
  You use Winamp casue you don’t want to use iTunes or WMP
  you use windows media player as its the only thing you know or its the only one on your PC / Laptop</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Music file sharing on the up and up</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/music-file-sharing-on-the-up-and-up-81/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2008 15:28:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/music-file-sharing-on-the-up-and-up-81/</guid>
      <description>Damien Saunders says -research shows continued growth in file-sharing and downloading of mp3s is now common place. This survey supports the view that prosecuting the mass population is not the right approach by the labels and rights associations.
British Music Rights research shows that file-sharing is done by a large number of people and even more are downloading music.
Music week reports these findings:
42% of those surveyed say they have uploaded files.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apple stops forced install of Safari web browser for windows</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/apple-stops-forced-install-of-safari-web-browser-for-windows-72/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Apr 2008 08:54:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/apple-stops-forced-install-of-safari-web-browser-for-windows-72/</guid>
      <description>Apple has changed its tactics – a few weeks ago it launched Safari as a part of an update for iTunes users. Safari will now be changed from an update to new software not installed.
Many people rightly pointed out that this was a shady tactic to get software on peoples computers.
source: http://blog.wired.com/monkeybites/2008/04/apple-appeases.html</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BBC iPlayer steams ahead with internet usage</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/bbc-iplayer-steams-ahead-with-internet-usage-70/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jan 2008 10:51:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/bbc-iplayer-steams-ahead-with-internet-usage-70/</guid>
      <description>Comment: Internet traffic to the iPlayer site is growing rapidly supported by outside advertising posterboards as well as reminders during TV advertising. However a lot of internet traffic seems to be sucked up by their kservices P2P network which aims to share the downloaded files with other iPlayer users.
 UK Internet traffic to the BBC’s iPlayer website increased 14-fold between the week ending 8 December 2007 and the week ending 5 January.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apple to standardise iTunes prices in Europe</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/apple-to-standardise-itunes-prices-in-europe-69/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jan 2008 15:08:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/apple-to-standardise-itunes-prices-in-europe-69/</guid>
      <description> comment: The reason that Apple charges different retail prices in each market is due to the differences in wholesale prices charged in each market by the major labels. Apple could use this as leverage against the labels to lower their prices in all major EU markets
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UK album retail sales dip 11% for 2007</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/uk-album-retail-sales-dip-11-for-2007-68/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jan 2008 12:14:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/uk-album-retail-sales-dip-11-for-2007-68/</guid>
      <description>Album unbundling, copyright theft and difficult retail conditions contributed to a drop in album sales of 10.8% in 2007 say the British Phonographic Industry.The continued growth of download sales helped the singles market grow by 29.3% during 2007, which became the third biggest year on record for the format.Change = -10.8%Source: BPI website</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pandora to block UK music streaming services</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/pandora-to-block-uk-music-streaming-services-67/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jan 2008 12:05:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/pandora-to-block-uk-music-streaming-services-67/</guid>
      <description>Comment: Pandora has been around for some time and grown in reputation as a free music discovery service. This is becoming a niche space because of the impact of internet radio or streaming licencing costs.
 In an email to users, Pandora founder Tim Westergren wrote:
“After over a year of trying, this has proved impossible. Both the PPL (which represents the record labels) and the MCPS/PRS Alliance (which represents music publishers) have demanded per track performance minima rates which are far too high to allow ad supported radio to operate and so, hugely disappointing and depressing to us as it is, we have to block the last territory outside of the US.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UK Digital sales grow by 50% in 2007</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/uk-digital-sales-grow-by-50-in-2007-66/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Jan 2008 11:12:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/uk-digital-sales-grow-by-50-in-2007-66/</guid>
      <description>The British Phonographic Industry, which represents the British recorded-music business, said total music download sales for the year topped 77 million, a 50 percent increase over 2006.
2.94m online music tracks were downloaded in the UK in the last week of 2007, according to the BPI, a record industry body. The figure is double that for the same time in 2006, when 1.47m tracks were downloaded, and nearly three times that for the same week in 2005, when only 1m songs were downloaded.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Happy New Year and welcome 2008</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/happy-new-year-and-welcome-2008-65/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2008 17:45:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/happy-new-year-and-welcome-2008-65/</guid>
      <description>My role as music product manager in a global organisation does allow for some time out .. today is the first official day back in the office … so happy new year.
A few interesting stories that I will certainly be watching
 Warner and Amazon announced DRM Free for their USA store – I wonder how long before Amazon launches in the UK Fox announces video content on Itunes – but its still DRM’d Billboard says 2008 will be the year we get digital album artwork as part of our online purchases – great news!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>O2 Sells 8000 iPhones on first night</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/o2-sells-8000-iphones-on-first-night-63/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2007 13:43:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/o2-sells-8000-iphones-on-first-night-63/</guid>
      <description>O2 sent an email to stores an hour after the launch, claiming that 2,000 customers who bought iPhones from O2 stores had registered their devices at 7:02pm. That figure soared to 8,000 by the end of the night.
Sales vary considerably from store to store, with anecdotes of disinterest from some, disbelief at the price tag from others and customers queuing in the snow at O2’s Aberdeen store.
Source: http://www.mobiletoday.co.uk/content/17234.asp?men=2&amp;amp;sub=1</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Musiwave sold to Microsoft for 50m</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/musiwave-sold-to-microsoft-for-50m-62/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2007 11:36:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/musiwave-sold-to-microsoft-for-50m-62/</guid>
      <description>Microsoft is closing its acquisition of Musiwave, the French mobile music company, for USD46m in cash and USD4m in debt. The price is less than half what Musiwave’s California-based owner Openwave paid when it bought the firm for USD117m in Jan 2006.
The deal is important for Microsoft as it gives it a foot in the door for mobile content delivery to consumers … as well Musiwave still works with a lot of the leading mobile operators.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>200000 iPhones to be sold by O2 UK by end of year</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/200000-iphones-to-be-sold-by-o2-uk-by-end-of-year-61/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Nov 2007 11:20:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/200000-iphones-to-be-sold-by-o2-uk-by-end-of-year-61/</guid>
      <description>O2 UK expects to sell around 200,000 iPhones by the start of the New Year. Sales will start on 9 November, and Matthew Key, CEO of O2’s UK business, told the Financial Times he expected “a couple of hundred thousand” iPhones to be sold in the first two months.
O2 has ordered “hundreds of thousands” of iPhones from Apple for its stores and online outlets as well as shops run by Carphone Warehouse.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google and others to open social networks taking on Facebook</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/google-and-others-to-open-social-networks-taking-on-facebook-60/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2007 06:35:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/google-and-others-to-open-social-networks-taking-on-facebook-60/</guid>
      <description>The New York Times writes that an alliance of companies led by Google plans to begin introducing a common set of standards to allow software developers to write programs for Google’s social network, Orkut, as well as others, including LinkedIn, hi5, Friendster, Plaxo and Ning. Facebook opened up its network for 3rd parties to develop their own applications earlier this year and this has resulted in a mass of new developments for everything from ‘super-poke’ to free sms.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Facebook valued at $15 billion &amp;#8211; thanks Microsoft</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/facebook-valued-at-15-billion-thanks-microsoft-59/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Oct 2007 08:24:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/facebook-valued-at-15-billion-thanks-microsoft-59/</guid>
      <description>Today WSJ writes that Microsoft has brought a minority stake in Facebook that would value the social network site at $15 billion. This ends month of speculation if it would be Google or Microsoft that would get a share.
Read/Write/Web goes on to suggest this will be a plus for the Microsoft adnetwork to help spread its presence in key sites.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apple iPhone for Europe partnering with Vodafone, t-Mobile &amp;amp; Carphone Warehouse?</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/apple-iphone-for-europe-partnering-with-vodafone-t-mobile-carphone-warehouse-57/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jul 2007 09:23:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/apple-iphone-for-europe-partnering-with-vodafone-t-mobile-carphone-warehouse-57/</guid>
      <description>On the rumour mill for some weeks has been the story that Vodafone and t-Mobile were in discussions about sole distributorship rights for a European iPhone. But now Gizmodo, have suggested that an announcement is due today and that both operators will win, leveraging the successes of both networks in different countries.
This would be great news for GSM users globally, a non-exclusive agreement would have far reaching appeal to mobile phone users than the American AT&amp;amp;T arrangement.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Turkey&amp;#039;s Avea Mobile Operator Goes 2.0?</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/turkeys-avea-mobile-operator-goes-20-56/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jun 2007 07:52:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/turkeys-avea-mobile-operator-goes-20-56/</guid>
      <description>In the last week new media marketing sites reported on a portal being developed Avea in Turkey. Secretly named GenCinSan (young people in Turkish) the site was launched this week as www.patlican.com.tr (patlican is eggplant/aubergine and a play on ‘it will explode’)
The new site is a reminder of early telco portals from the dotcom error and features include news, reviews, video, with a mix of traditional telco products and services.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Turkey delays 3G licence auction for lack of interest</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/turkey-delays-3g-licence-auction-for-lack-of-interest-55/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 May 2007 09:46:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/turkey-delays-3g-licence-auction-for-lack-of-interest-55/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Turk Telecom gets in &amp;#039;dirty ads&amp;#039; fight about mobile number portability</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/turk-telecom-gets-in-dirty-ads-fight-about-mobile-number-portability-54/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Apr 2007 07:14:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/turk-telecom-gets-in-dirty-ads-fight-about-mobile-number-portability-54/</guid>
      <description>On Monday Türk Telecom announced it will take legal action against all illicit advertisements and presentations targeting Türk Telecom and its new tariff. Competition among the companies in the telecommunications sector is becoming brutal and the announcement gave the competition a whole new dimension.
Meanwhile, Avea’s general Manager Cüneyt Türktan accused Turkcell of being inconsistent for heading to the court for the annulment of the number portability, after supporting it first.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Turkey launches tender for 4 3G licences</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/turkey-launches-tender-for-4-3g-licences-53/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Apr 2007 07:09:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/turkey-launches-tender-for-4-3g-licences-53/</guid>
      <description>Turkey has announced plans to offers for third-generation (3G) mobile phone licenses — Short-listed bidders then enter a second-round bid. The minimum bid prices range from 140 million euros ($189 million) to 252 million euros ($340 million). The Turkish mobile market is currently home to three operators, Turkcell, Vodafone-Telsim and Avea.
Transportation Minister Binali Yıldırım was speaking at the Independent Industrialists and Businessmen’s Association’s (MÜSİAD) traditional Thursday talks. Yıldırım said he was expecting interest from the existing three GSM operators in Turkey — Turkcell, Vodafone (formerly Telsim) and Avea — in the investigation of feasible price studies for 3G licenses.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mobile Jamming in Malaysian Government Buildings</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/mobile-jamming-in-malaysian-government-buildings-52/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Apr 2007 07:01:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/mobile-jamming-in-malaysian-government-buildings-52/</guid>
      <description>Reuters reports that Malaysia has banned mobile phones and installed electronic jamming devices in key parts of its administrative capital to block spying on official discussions.“The widespread use of these devices, especially handphones with camera facilities, has serious implications on security,” the Star newspaper quoted Malaysia’s top bureaucrat, Mohamed Sidek Hassan, as saying in a recent message to officials.
Mohamed Sidek also asked department heads to designate areas where official matters are discussed as “information security zones,” the paper added.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Turkey Mobile Number Portability challenged in Courts</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/turkey-mobile-number-portability-challenged-in-courts-50/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Apr 2007 12:47:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/turkey-mobile-number-portability-challenged-in-courts-50/</guid>
      <description>Turkey’s officials announced at the start of 2007 the introduction of mobile number portability (MNP) for its 3 mobile operators, Vodafone, Turkcell and Avea. MNP allows customers to change carriers and keep their number, referred to as porting.
There is an element of prestige in Turkey about what your prefix number is, so allowing people to port will open up competition more, however Turkey’s largest mobile operator, Turkcell, has now filed a lawsuit calling for the cancellation of MNP.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Turkcell-im WAP service registers 6.5 million customers</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/turkcell-im-wap-service-registers-65-million-customers-51/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Apr 2007 13:30:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/turkcell-im-wap-service-registers-65-million-customers-51/</guid>
      <description>More than 6.5 million Turkcell subscribers have started using mobile Internet since the introduction of Turkcell-im, a web-based platform in which all of the company’s value-added services are offered together.
Turkcell Assistant General Manager Cenk Serdar said the Web site has been visited by 56 million people since it was launched seven months ago. The visitors have download multimedia content for their phones such as music, videos, pictures and games. While the number of copies of song albums sold in 2006 was 15 million, the number of songs downloaded from Turkcell-im exceeded 10 million, said Parlak.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vodafone Turkey unit adds 1 million customers, finishes brand migration</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/vodafone-turkey-unit-adds-1-million-customers-finishes-brand-migration-48/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Apr 2007 08:09:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/vodafone-turkey-unit-adds-1-million-customers-finishes-brand-migration-48/</guid>
      <description>Turkish unit said on Friday it had added over one million new customers in Turkey in the first quarter taking its total customer base to 13.8 million. “This increase demonstrates that Vodafone is successfully bringing its global standards and expertise to the Turkish market and customers are responding by joining us in very significant numbers,” the unit’s Chief Executive Attila Vitai told a news conference.
Vitai said from March 31 Telsim-Vodafone would complete its brand transition and would be known only as Vodafone.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SMS sending suspended because of Elections in Cambodia</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/sms-sending-suspended-because-of-elections-in-cambodia-47/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Apr 2007 07:54:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/sms-sending-suspended-because-of-elections-in-cambodia-47/</guid>
      <description>“Mobile-phone text messaging in Cambodia has been suspended for the weekend,so that users are not bombarded with political texts during an election,”the BBC reports.”The National Election Committee has asked phone networks to turn off the service until after the polls have closed in Sunday’s local elections.Human-rights and opposition activists have criticised the move,calling the action unnecessary.
With no little irony,users were informed of the move by text message”.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Telsim Vodafone Network campaign &amp;amp; Turkcell Internet ad</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/telsim-vodafone-network-campaign-turkcell-internet-ad-46/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Mar 2007 08:38:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/telsim-vodafone-network-campaign-turkcell-internet-ad-46/</guid>
      <description>Here’s a couple of ads from competing networks in Turkey currently being aired around the country.
Turkcell’s internet ad features the ‘cellbuddy’ with crazy head gear and a yellow suit demonstrating search to a child doing her homework in the dark as there is no power.
The Cellbuddies feature in all their campaigns some times as kids in bumblebee costumes othewise drawn as a bug with funny antenna … most people don’t seem sure what they are?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Can a Brand improve the handset user experience?</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/can-a-brand-improve-the-handset-user-experience-45/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jan 2007 20:02:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/can-a-brand-improve-the-handset-user-experience-45/</guid>
      <description>Comment: Terminal manufacturers are developing new applications and intergrating the user experience of other brands. Can this be a harmonious relationship with operators own portals?
With a selection of mobile phones from Christmas 2006 sitting on my desk from several big names its apparent that 3rd parties are now working with the terminal suppliers directly to port their web experience to phone apps. You can see this happening in Europe primarily with Google for blogging and search, but in the US, Helio has had success with its brand phone and social-networking tools.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Location Specific Mobile Solutions</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/location-specific-mobile-solutions-44/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Oct 2006 16:15:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/location-specific-mobile-solutions-44/</guid>
      <description>Summary: Location Based Services (LBS) were thought to be a killer app for 3G, next is the GPS chip in your phone. What mobile and location services are there right now?
Some of us still remember the early days when 3G business cases were built on the success of LBS’s – everyone was going to make a killing. By far the best ‘LBS’ service on any portal are:
 live train timetables (is my train on time) traffic cameras (where is that jam) mobile operator concierge service (for those unusal location requests)  So does throwing a GPS chip in a phone help you?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>6 months in Turkey</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/6-months-in-turkey-42/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2006 12:37:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/6-months-in-turkey-42/</guid>
      <description>You might have begun to think I had dropped off the blogosphere. You might be right … a good blog has to be kept updated daily and have something new. I started this when I had a lot of spare time and was looking to go back to contracting. It’s proved very useful.
I’m actually off to Turkey for 6 months for work, but hope in between all of that to find the time to get this going again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Soonr: Your mobile PC application</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/soonr-your-mobile-pc-application-41/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2006 11:59:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/soonr-your-mobile-pc-application-41/</guid>
      <description>Up until now getting access to documents, music files or photos or your calendar when you are away from your office or home PC has been limited to a mess of cables, WIFI or datacards. SoonR seems to have hit the nail on the head, with a smooth interface and more features than you can throw a dog at.
While not all the word is as mass mobile as I am, and it could be a long way before many want this service, which Soonr has solved already …</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Operators to face Adult Content Restrictions</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/operators-to-face-adult-content-restrictions-38/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2006 11:46:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/operators-to-face-adult-content-restrictions-38/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The Australian communications minister Helen Coonan plans to introduce to parliament legislation to extend the current safeguards that apply to content delivered over the internet or television to content delivered over convergent devices such as mobile phones.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This will include prohibition of content rated X18+ and above, as well as requirements for consumer advice and age-restrictions on access to content suited only to adults. This has impact across the board as for most people the internet is seen to be ‘open’ and attempts to block porn are like trying to plug holes in a leaking dam. Operators have also argued they should be treated like ISP’s and can’t be held responsible for what customers do with their phones&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Manage a diverse range of handsets, don&amp;#039;t just stop selling them</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/manage-a-diverse-range-of-handsets-dont-just-stop-selling-them-37/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2006 09:36:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/manage-a-diverse-range-of-handsets-dont-just-stop-selling-them-37/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;It seems only yesterday that operators were switching off their analogue mobile networks, yet now its the turn of the retailer to make to turn off the switch. Online retail brand Dixon’s &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.brandrepublic.com/bulletins/digital/article/581379/end-era-dixons-drops-analogue-radios/&#34;&gt;reports&lt;/a&gt; they will stop selling analogue radios and that the death is imminent also for portable stereos and CD players. I guess the portable tapeplayer and VHS are already ‘dead’ by their reckoning. For mobile operators, the problem is confounded by the need to actually support all this old tech stuff.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SMS pricing initiatives</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/sms-pricing-initiatives-34/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2006 14:04:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/sms-pricing-initiatives-34/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Summary: Operators are competing with large bundles of ‘free’ text messages. This pricing prevents text over IP or other apps taking off, but there is still a long way to go to grow data usage.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There is still alot of work to be done to grow data usage across the business and consumer base. One of the challenges is working out pricing. In Ireland, they are trialling €49 per month unlimited plan. In T-mobile UK they have a £7.50 unlimited data plan but services like Skype are barred.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>There&amp;#039;s a light</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/theres-a-light-33/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2006 14:36:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/theres-a-light-33/</guid>
      <description>In the news today, seven of the big name operators are forming an industry organisation to create a common 4G mobile phone network standard. The group is tentatively called Next Generation Mobile Networks (NGMN).
The networks include KPN Mobile, T-Mobile, Orange, Sprint Nextel, Vodafone, China Mobile and NTT Docomo. They plan to establish a non-profit company in the US by the end of July. I’m not sure why they picked the US – are they getting a tax free status if they can sort out the existing networks?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What&amp;#039;s in a disconnect?</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/whats-in-a-disconnect-32/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2006 14:01:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/whats-in-a-disconnect-32/</guid>
      <description>summary: customer care can only go so far, when the customer’s relationship starts to fail with an operator, people will look for new solutions.
I’ve just moved flat and am stuck between two operators. The old place had BT and the existing place is still with Bulldog – with the old tenants vanished overseas, no one will disconnect the line. Thanks to local loop unbundling, I can’t even get a POTS lines connected.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advertising on your mobile</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/advertising-on-your-mobile-30/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2006 10:46:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/advertising-on-your-mobile-30/</guid>
      <description>Summary: We still have a long way to go to accept adverts on your mobile. While Europeans have said yes to Mobile TV and no to paid for advertising, the US is talking up one-second adverts called &amp;lsquo;Blinks&amp;rsquo;.
Clear Communications is talking to media buyers and agenices about blinks – one-second adverts that allow just enought time to recognise the brand by its gingle. You can imagine that two syllable Danone or perhaps the McDonalds &amp;lsquo;I&amp;rsquo;m Loving it&amp;rsquo; … or maybe you&amp;rsquo;ll hear someone shout out &amp;lsquo;Drink Pepsi&amp;rsquo; in a sudden and startling manner.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HSDPA rollout tops 100 Networks</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/hsdpa-rollout-tops-100-networks-28/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2006 22:04:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/hsdpa-rollout-tops-100-networks-28/</guid>
      <description>An article on http://3g.co.uk reports that the number of HSDPA networks (known as 3G Broadband) has now topped 100. That&amp;rsquo;s either commercially available or in deployment. This new survey confirms that 30 HSDPA networks have commercially launched services in 23 countries/territories, delivering the full broadband experience to subscribers. We expect the number of commercial HSDPA networks will more than double to 63 by end 2006. All WCDMA networks are expected to activate the HSDPA upgrade.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Some thoughts on the BBC Creative Future</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/so-reactions-to-the-bbc-creative-future-26/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2006 08:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/so-reactions-to-the-bbc-creative-future-26/</guid>
      <description>So the BBC have released their Creative Futures report yesterday looking at the future of the Beeb. While it will take some time to digest and come to comprehend what this means to our viewing and reading habits, take a minute to think about how this impacts our industry??
 All content made &amp;lsquo;&amp;lsquo;&amp;lsquo;FREELY&amp;rsquo;&amp;rsquo;&amp;rsquo; available on a website starting today going back to 1937  and other recommendations include:
• Relaunching the BBC&amp;rsquo;s website to include more personalisation, richer audio-visual and user generated content</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Take Note of your Customer Care</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/take-note-of-your-customer-care-25/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Feb 2006 14:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/take-note-of-your-customer-care-25/</guid>
      <description>Opinion: There are many online services that customers will turn to for support when your customer service goes bad – be on top of what is going on. It may even save you money.
More than 40 percent of online chat about UK mobile operators is related to customer service issues. Not only is customer care the most common topic of discussion, it also attracts the most negative sentiment, with only one UK operator, Orange, scoring positively, reports WaveMetrix.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gmail for your mobile</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/gmail-for-your-mobile-24/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2005 10:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/gmail-for-your-mobile-24/</guid>
      <description>Google has created a special version of its Gmail e-mail service that provides mobile phone users with quick access to their e-mail. Point your mobile to http://m.gmail.com.
The service allows you to view attached files such as images or download documents if supported by your handset.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What&amp;#8217;s the problem with depth of catalogue?</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/whats-the-problem-with-depth-of-catalogue-23/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2005 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/whats-the-problem-with-depth-of-catalogue-23/</guid>
      <description>It’s like trying to sell ice creams to eskimos – do you go for depth and variety of your content catalogue or stick to the sickly seasonal or monthly favourites … you can be damned either way.
What I’m thinking is that most mobile content sales via WAP were dominated by the operator portals, but you invariably find that top downloads page will have the Star Wars March, Axel F and something from Guns n Roses (AC/DC).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RSS to SMS for your mobile</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/rss-to-sms-for-your-mobile-22/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2005 13:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/rss-to-sms-for-your-mobile-22/</guid>
      <description>Think about this carefully – any RSS stream sent free to your mobile by SMS … you’ve got your blackberry, you’ve got your live news alerts and weekly MMS updates – but who tells you about that other stuff you’re really really interested in? Talk about giving away the baby and the bath water – but maybe this is just a crazy idea with some sense behind it.
As part of an update to its alerts feature, Yahoo added a feature that allows users to get RSS results via SMS.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mobile Blogging Reduces Churn</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/mobile-blogging-reduces-churn-21/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2005 09:55:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/mobile-blogging-reduces-churn-21/</guid>
      <description>MocoNews.net: mobile content news: &amp;ldquo;Mobile Blogging generates an immediate reduction of up to 70% in the propensity of a user to churn.&amp;rdquo;
Results of a 12-month survey of two million subscribers on four operators which were using NewBay&amp;rsquo;s Software FoneBlog mobile blogging and multimedia album solution have been released.
According to NewBay the result comes from increased loyalty – based on personal content on the moblog. What is obvious here is if you have personal content and you can&amp;rsquo;t move/download it simply, then there is a barrier to change.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>US findings from Content Survey</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/us-findings-from-content-survey-20/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2005 09:39:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/us-findings-from-content-survey-20/</guid>
      <description>interesting global research on mobile phones from a US university.
57% of all users say they&amp;rsquo;re willing to spend no more than $5 per month on mobile data services — including text messages, and the most important factor in choosing a mobile service is cheap voice calls. That&amp;rsquo;s backed up by another piece of research this week that says it&amp;rsquo;s cheap voice plans, not fast data driving 3G.
More than a third of users worldwide have cameraphones, up from 21% last year, and 59% have color screens, up from 44%.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rude Food &amp;#8211; National Vegie Week</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/2005-05-20-rude-food-national-vegie-week/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2005 10:25:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/2005-05-20-rude-food-national-vegie-week/</guid>
      <description>Rude Food sex and food won’t ever seem the same again!
If sex sells then I guess this is how to stimulate the eat 7 a day mob (fruit and veg that is)
I just wonder what the fruit/veg is in the last scene — the one that looks like dripping … ????</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Coen Brothers, Kaufmann and more &amp;#8230;</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/2005-05-13-coen-brothers-kaufmann-and-more/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 May 2005 13:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/2005-05-13-coen-brothers-kaufmann-and-more/</guid>
      <description>I actually wasn’t sure what to expect never being to a sound play / radio play before. I then heard it was only going to be an hour (sob sob). But for starters — 200m in front of me (roughly) were some of the best actors on stage and NOT ON A SILVER SCREEN. Real breathing people, like wow! and collectively you also have 2 plays written and produced by !</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AUSTRALIA GETS DRUNK, WAKES UP IN NORTH ATLANTIC</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/2005-05-12-australia-gets-drunk-wakes-up-in-north-atlantic/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2005 13:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/2005-05-12-australia-gets-drunk-wakes-up-in-north-atlantic/</guid>
      <description>Tired of Being Isolated and Ignored, Continent Isn’t Bloody Moving
Sydney, 800 miles S. of Nova Scotia (SatireWire.com) — After what witnesses described as an all night blinder during which it kept droning on about how it was always being bloody ignored by the whole bloody world and would bloody well stand to do something about it, Australia this morning woke up to find itself in the middle of the North Atlantic.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>26 Thoughts to Get You Through a Crisis</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/2005-05-07-26-thoughts-to-get-you-through-a-crisis/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2005 18:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/2005-05-07-26-thoughts-to-get-you-through-a-crisis/</guid>
      <description>Indecision is the key to flexibility. You can’t tell which way the train went by looking at the track. There is absolutely no substitute for a genuine lack of preparation. Happiness is merely the remission of pain. Nostalgia isn’t what it used to be. Sometimes too much drink is not enough. The facts, although interesting, are irrelevant. The careful application of terror is also a form of communication. Someone who thinks logically is a nice contrast to the real world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Last Sightings of Turkey</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/2004-08-15-last-sightings-of-turkey/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Aug 2004 16:12:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/2004-08-15-last-sightings-of-turkey/</guid>
      <description>so it was back to getting up early! well 630am! before a short ride to the port of Kusadasi and then goodbye to Turkey. The authorities are not organised and a tour operator (official) collects your passports and arranges the ferry boarding passes. Next time dont arrive early for the ferry or you get your passport back LAST!.
Saying goodbye to Neil in Samos I decided to go to Paros and maybe then on to Athens.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Turkey Pammukale</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/2004-08-14-turkey-pammukale/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Aug 2004 22:54:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/2004-08-14-turkey-pammukale/</guid>
      <description>Tukery 2004 – Pammukale .. the calcium rich water comes up to the surface creating these amazing terraces</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thoughts on Turkey</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/2004-08-14-thoughts-on-turkey/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Aug 2004 16:16:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/2004-08-14-thoughts-on-turkey/</guid>
      <description>All Turkish men shave there armpits .. weird .. dont ask me why!!
The land looks really hard and barren but they produce so much … limes, apricots, melons, sunflower seeds/oil
I’d go back to Istanbul in a sec … something about it appeals // perhaps its the age? or perhaps its just the bustling city?
Turkey is trying damn hard to move up in the world – and join the EU … so will watch it and maybe come back!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>