<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Marketing Strategy on Damien Saunders</title>
    <link>http://damien.co/tags/marketing-strategy/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Marketing Strategy on Damien Saunders</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2013 11:22:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://damien.co/tags/marketing-strategy/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Why I use WordPress?</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/2013-03-06-why-i-use-wordpress/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2013 11:22:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/2013-03-06-why-i-use-wordpress/</guid>
      <description>Why use WordPress and Compare WordPress features sound like pretty SEO friendly keywords. Right? And if you&amp;rsquo;re new to WordPress, you’ll probably see many articles focus on three words - Free, Simple &amp;amp; Easy. These words tell you nothing about WordPress and so this is to help you decide to choose WordPress.
I started using WordPress in 2003 and I still have my hosted account London.WordPress.com. I switched to standalone or self-hosted in 2009 and from 2010, I&amp;rsquo;ve been running WordPress network or WordPress multisite.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rule #2 - Social Media Marketing - Crucial for Sales &amp;#038; Marketing</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/social-media/rule-2-social-media-marketing-crucial-sales-marketing-7361/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jun 2012 16:00:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/social-media/rule-2-social-media-marketing-crucial-sales-marketing-7361/</guid>
      <description>Social Media marketing - using Twitter, Facebook, LinkedIn, Foursquare, Google+ … needs to form part of any marketing plan across the marketing mix. Do you really need a Digital Marketing Plan? And if your business needs a plan … why does it have to included social media?
Why Digital Marketing &amp;amp; Social Media? Every business - big, small, startup or established brand needs a digital marketing strategy. It&amp;rsquo;s crucial for your marketing and sales plan (even if you don&amp;rsquo;t have one) to include digital marketing and social media.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>4 reasons to choose Google Analytics for your business</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/marketing-consultant-2/4-reasons-to-choose-google-analytics-for-your-business-4932/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2011 16:13:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/marketing-consultant-2/4-reasons-to-choose-google-analytics-for-your-business-4932/</guid>
      <description>Google Analytics is one of the web’s most popular tools for reporting on activity and trends for just about any website. Your online and offline marketing activities need meaningful analytics data to create actionable insights. In summary, website analytics has benefits for sales, marketing and product development - in fact most areas of your business.
Why Choose Google Analytics? It&amp;rsquo;s easy to see why Google Analytics is so popular, because it&amp;rsquo;s free, but here are my top 4</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3 point plan for Agile Marketing</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/marketing-consultant-2/3-point-plan-for-agile-marketing-4667/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2011 09:45:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/marketing-consultant-2/3-point-plan-for-agile-marketing-4667/</guid>
      <description>Can you tell the difference between Agile, Guerilla or Real Time Marketing? Does it really matter? You need a 3 point plan for Agile marketing - or is it just your boss asking for a quicker turn-around?
What&amp;rsquo;s Agile marketing? Agile marketing is similar to real time marketing. So what makes it agile or is it a catchphrase?
Agile marketing is a bit of a new catchphrase, you’ll see it in the press and hear it around the offices.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Start a Social Media Marketing Plan – why you need to use social media?</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/social-media/start-a-social-media-marketing-plan-why-you-need-to-use-social-media-1119/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jul 2010 09:00:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/social-media/start-a-social-media-marketing-plan-why-you-need-to-use-social-media-1119/</guid>
      <description>Starting your plan for social media marketing in a small or big business should be driven by a need or a reason
Why use Social Media - because your customers are using it! First step in your social media marketing plan is to open powerpoint or write on a flipchart the reason why you need to use social media, some good reasons include:
 most of our target audience use social media (no brainer), or because visits to your brand or company website are down as our customers spend more time on social media sites (better) to deliver a sales &amp;amp; marketing programme using online &amp;amp; social media  There are probably plenty of other good reasons you can think of.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Where to start building mobile apps for large screens - mobile agencies beware</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/2010-01-28-where-to-start-building-mobile-apps-for-large-screens-mobile-agencies-beware/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jan 2010 15:28:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/2010-01-28-where-to-start-building-mobile-apps-for-large-screens-mobile-agencies-beware/</guid>
      <description>Where to start with building a mobile app or going mobile has been a popular topic for some time. Many FMCG brands and agencies are requesting only quotes for mobile apps - forgetting the less popular java app or branded mobile game. At the expense of budget - haha - focusing on a mobile app can be a costly exercise starting from about 10k to 100k plus.
Marketing Agencies and their Brands need to go and reconsider their mobile strategy - and if you&amp;rsquo;ve already built a mobile app - you maybe disappointed how it looks on the larger screen devices.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>