<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Facebook on Damien Saunders</title>
    <link>http://damien.co/tags/facebook/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Facebook on Damien Saunders</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Jun 2012 14:22:59 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://damien.co/tags/facebook/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Social Gaming is on the decline? Blame cannibalisation by mobile and OTT</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/insights-blog/why-social-gaming-decline-blame-cannibalisation-mobile-ott-7316/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jun 2012 14:22:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/insights-blog/why-social-gaming-decline-blame-cannibalisation-mobile-ott-7316/</guid>
      <description>Social Gaming is on the decline - not terminal decline, just platform cannibalisation. Well mostly. Some Social Gamers just go off and play other newer games. The big reason for the decline in social game, I believe is the rise of free games in App Stores like Android Play and iTunes App Store. These App Stores provide a direct to user channel for promotion of games.
5 reasons Social Gaming is on the decline There are 5 reasons this is happening</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Comment is Free (again) thanks to Facebook</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/2011-06-08-comment-is-free-again-thanks-to-facebook/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jun 2011 10:52:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/2011-06-08-comment-is-free-again-thanks-to-facebook/</guid>
      <description>Recently I moaned about the state of comments and spam - and I hinted that comments would be enabled across my website again.
My interests in social media do extend to &amp;lsquo;the Facebook&amp;rsquo; - but my expertise is definitely not with that network. Given a limited number of hours in each day, I have enough social media stuff to do.
Facebook Comments Only a few months back, Facebook launched their own comments system allowing external websites an easy way to integrate with Facebooks own commenting system.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Are you following me ( on Twitter )</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/promo/follow-me-on-facebook-3117/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 May 2011 13:33:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/promo/follow-me-on-facebook-3117/</guid>
      <description>Did you know that social media is more than just blogs and RSS feeds? Well I hope so.
I have a following on Twitter that is &amp;lt;— this BIG —&amp;gt; which is a lot for little ol&amp;rsquo; me. Maybe you prefer Twitter because you can dip in to the Twitterstream - maybe you should try following me.
What does Damien Saunders have to share on Twitter? Damien&amp;rsquo;s Twitter account is kept updated 24/7 with the latest headlines from across my Internet websites.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You can like me on Facebook too</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/promo/you-can-like-me-on-facebook-too-3121/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 May 2011 13:46:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/promo/you-can-like-me-on-facebook-too-3121/</guid>
      <description>Did you know that social media is more than just blogs and RSS feeds?
If you’ve heard of Facebook - you might like to know that I have a fan page - so if you can like my page that would be great.
By liking me — you’ll have daily updates from the latest news and stuff that is published on my website and you&amp;rsquo;ll be letting me know how much you like Facebook.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Facebook Wants your Homepage</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/social-media/facebook-wants-your-homepage-2811/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Mar 2011 07:05:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/social-media/facebook-wants-your-homepage-2811/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m not one to always login to Facebook … It&amp;rsquo;s a good week if I don&amp;rsquo;t log in at all. But for about 500 million people Facebook is pretty important.
As if Facebook really needed to tell you to bookmark their site if you already go there - but this bookmarket / on-site advertising is a fresh change to the usual page prompting you to login from your mobile.
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Using Social Media takes 20% of your Australian day</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/social-media/using-social-media-takes-20-of-your-australian-day-2786/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2011 09:25:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/social-media/using-social-media-takes-20-of-your-australian-day-2786/</guid>
      <description>Australians spend 1 in 5 minutes using social media sites. Social Networking usage was about 22% in December 2010 says comScore.
The statistics reveal that Facebook, Twitter, LinkedIn are some of the most popular destinations. If you add into this instant messaging then the total rises to 35% - which is probably a more realistic definition of social networking.
There is a presentation you can download with really good insights on internet usage across Australia.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>50 Completely Useful stats for social media &amp;amp; mobile marketing</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/2010-05-31-50-completely-useful-stats-for-social-media-mobile-marketing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 May 2010 16:27:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/2010-05-31-50-completely-useful-stats-for-social-media-mobile-marketing/</guid>
      <description>To understand more about Social Media and Mobile Marketing its important to get a few facts together on current trends and insights. 50 completely useful stats for social media does just that.
Why do this? well it helps to create some drive … and helps to understand why anyone or any business needs to do more in social media and mobile marketing.
50 completely useful stats for social media &amp;amp; mobile marketing</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>