<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>youth on Damien Saunders</title>
    <link>http://damien.co/tags/youth/</link>
    <description>Recent content in youth on Damien Saunders</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 18 Aug 2010 10:30:49 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://damien.co/tags/youth/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Lithuania Youth love Basketball</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/lithuania-youth-love-basketball-1411/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Aug 2010 10:30:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/lithuania-youth-love-basketball-1411/</guid>
      <description>Lithuania is a basketball crazy nation – which may seem odd if you know little about this newer European Union state. Lithuania has had a long history with basketball even in the days of the Soviet Union (USSR).
Lithuania will also be hosting the Mens European Championships in summer 2011. Something to look forward too. I guess as the days grow darker and colder, indoor team sports like Basketball are good for the fans and the players.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vilnius Youth in Lithuania get up to no good</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/2010-08-12-vilnius-youth-in-lithuania-get-up-to-no-good/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Aug 2010 11:00:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/2010-08-12-vilnius-youth-in-lithuania-get-up-to-no-good/</guid>
      <description>In Vilnius, the capital city of Lithuania its youth get up to no good. Just like all young people do! Here’s a few photos from the last week to prove how bad these youngsters can be.
Vilnius main drag @4pm on the HOTTEST day (ever) is deserted cause word had got around that 2 skate boarding youth were taking over the town.
Vilnius main tourist attraction is its iconic cathedral and separate bell tower, in this shot the youth of today are street dancing!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lithuanian Youth love their mobiles</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/2010-08-11-lithuanian-youth-love-their-mobiles/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Aug 2010 11:00:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/2010-08-11-lithuanian-youth-love-their-mobiles/</guid>
      <description>In Lithuania mobile penetration is almost at 150% – so is this all from younger people sim swapping?
Mobile Youth in Lithuania (16-24 yo) are all using multi-sims for the best deals and free calls. The 3 main operators are Omnitel, Bite and Tele2. Freedom of choice means that handsets are not subsidised very much and customers have to pay full price for a phone. Even the the ‘popular’ iPhone is over priced and still exclusive with one operator and on a 24 month contract.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lithuanian Youth love to use the Internet</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/lithuanian-youth-love-to-use-the-internet-1383/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Aug 2010 10:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/lithuanian-youth-love-to-use-the-internet-1383/</guid>
      <description>In Lithuania the usage of the internet is reaching saturation point. A 2009 official report shows 95% of young people aged 16-24 with internet access**.**
Lithuania has one of the highest per capita access to broadband ratios due to small land mass and population of just under 4 million. It’s also atypical of ‘westernised’ European markets and the Lithuanian youth are no different – wanting mobile phones, good clothes, good education and a future with a good job (most likely in London).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What kids do online: UK Internet Usage</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/2010-02-07-what-kids-do-online-uk-internet-usage/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Feb 2010 12:56:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/2010-02-07-what-kids-do-online-uk-internet-usage/</guid>
      <description>Recent indepth report from New Media Age in the UK focused on the internet usage habits of kids.
Kids research is hard – the age group is from 7 – 13. They are already exposed to a lot of marketing, aware of trends and ‘peer pressure’, but still very much aware of having to please their parents all of the time. It’s also very difficult to ask questions about anything anti-social, illegal due to the young age and formative, questioning minds.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>