<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Webdev on Damien Saunders</title>
    <link>https://damien1.github.io/tags/webdev/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Webdev on Damien Saunders</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2011 12:11:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://damien1.github.io/tags/webdev/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Google Analytics &amp;#8211; Event tracking is great for customer engagement</title>
      <link>https://damien1.github.io/marketing-consultant-2/google-analytics-event-tracking-is-great-for-customer-engagement-5132/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2011 12:11:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien1.github.io/marketing-consultant-2/google-analytics-event-tracking-is-great-for-customer-engagement-5132/</guid>
      <description>Google Analytics provides a number of extra tools for the adventurous to improve tracking and provide valuable insights. Event tracking should be used throughout the user journey to better understand customer engagement.
Why Google Analytics? Google Analytics is one of the web’s most popular tools for reporting on activity and trends for just about any website. Your online and offline marketing activities need meaningful analytics data which creates actionable insights. In summary, website analytics has benefits for sales, marketing and product development – in fact most areas of your business.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Migrating your company website to WordPress Self Hosted</title>
      <link>https://damien1.github.io/wordpress/migrating-your-company-website-to-wordpress-self-hosted-697/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Nov 2011 23:04:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien1.github.io/wordpress/migrating-your-company-website-to-wordpress-self-hosted-697/</guid>
      <description>WordPressis one of the most popular solutions for blogging. What people don’t know is that WordPress self hosted is the best solution for building a standalone B2B or SME company website. We recently finished the migration of the mmCHANNEL company website from an in-house developed website (using PHP, etc) to single install, self hosted WordPress installation.
There were a few times when I felt that maybe WordPress wasn’t right, but overall it’s going great and the results are visible!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Review] The Smashing Book 2 Is Available &amp;#8211; Smashing Magazine</title>
      <link>https://damien1.github.io/blog/review-the-smashing-book-2-is-available-smashing-magazine-2659/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Feb 2011 16:52:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien1.github.io/blog/review-the-smashing-book-2-is-available-smashing-magazine-2659/</guid>
      <description>So I got my copy of the new ****The Smashing Book 2. Smashing Magazine is for anyone into design, web development and new media. It is one of many websites I follow on a weekly basis.
 The book came nicely (over) packaged and was immediately opened. It is a resource in itself and provides 10+ essays on topics from mobile app design to self-publishing – all new and not available on the website.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>