<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Mobile Internet on Damien Saunders</title>
    <link>https://damien1.github.io/tags/mobile-internet/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Mobile Internet on Damien Saunders</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Oct 2012 13:20:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://damien1.github.io/tags/mobile-internet/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>What&amp;#8217;s the Best Strategy for making a mobile version of an existing site?</title>
      <link>https://damien1.github.io/blog/2012-10-01-whats-the-best-strategy-for-making-a-mobile-version-of-an-existing-site/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Oct 2012 13:20:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien1.github.io/blog/2012-10-01-whats-the-best-strategy-for-making-a-mobile-version-of-an-existing-site/</guid>
      <description>In WordPress going mobile is easy … you could actually find that your website theme is already Responsive, so maybe ‘doing nothing’ is a valid answer.
What are your choices to mobilise a WordPress Website? You have 4 choices
 Choose a Responsive Theme for your site (Responsive adapts for different screen sizes) most work from WooThemes is now responsive. Choose a plugin (such as WPTouchPro– which is both plugin and theme) Build a second site which you access at m.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HOW TO: View your WordPress Website on iPhone or Android Mobiles</title>
      <link>https://damien1.github.io/blog/2012-06-17-how-to-view-your-wordpress-website-on-iphone-or-android-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Jun 2012 16:00:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien1.github.io/blog/2012-06-17-how-to-view-your-wordpress-website-on-iphone-or-android-2/</guid>
      <description>WordPress is a very comprehensive all-round tool for websites – and its not just for blogs. If you’re starting out with WordPress and need your site to look smooth on a mobile phone like the iPhone or iPad or any Android mobile then you’ll need a plugin for this.
The best plugin for WordPress that handles any mobile device is easily WPtouch iPhone Theme. Once the plugin is installed and activated its working for you straight away.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to make your website mobile</title>
      <link>https://damien1.github.io/mobile-marketing/how-to-make-your-website-mobile-3772/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jun 2011 11:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien1.github.io/mobile-marketing/how-to-make-your-website-mobile-3772/</guid>
      <description>Smart phones are driving the usage of mobile internet and that’s not just the growth in mobile apps. Having a mobile version of your website or a mobile web app is becoming critical as your customers and potential new business use mobile search to hunt for any business.
There are 3 easy steps to get your website ready for the mobile internet:
 Make your website mobile now Assess your mobile customer’s needs Improve your mobile customer experience to generate leads  Make your website mobile today It’s easy for any brand or business to enable a mobile version of your website.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HOWTO: Fix no mobile internet after Cyanogenmod install</title>
      <link>https://damien1.github.io/blog/android/howto-fix-no-mobile-internet-after-cyanogenmod-install-2822/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Apr 2011 21:04:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien1.github.io/blog/android/howto-fix-no-mobile-internet-after-cyanogenmod-install-2822/</guid>
      <description>Here’s a simple fix to problems of no Mobile Internet after installing Cyanogenmod rom on your Android. If you’re new to rooting your Android or just forgotten how complicated it can be to get online with your mobile phone – you might think this is a really useful tip.
 Check your APN Settings After you root your phone and install CyanogenMod you can find your have no wifi and no wireless internet connection.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>5 Essential tips for promoting your charity or cause using mobile marketing</title>
      <link>https://damien1.github.io/mobile-marketing/essential-tips-promotions-charities-mobile-451/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Feb 2010 07:44:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien1.github.io/mobile-marketing/essential-tips-promotions-charities-mobile-451/</guid>
      <description>For non-profit organisations, charities and cause related marketing the mobile can provide the best integrated marketing solution for campaigns. There are a number of tools and techniques which can be used to promote your cause or help to raise donations.
1. SMS Premium Text Donations Making donations using your mobile is as simple as sending a text to a special number. For the not so concerned and the lazy its a quick way to send a few dollars, euros or pounds to a worthy cause.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to use Competitions &amp;amp; Social Media to grow your mobile marketing</title>
      <link>https://damien1.github.io/mobile-marketing/how-to-use-competitions-social-media-to-grow-your-business-399/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jan 2010 23:18:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien1.github.io/mobile-marketing/how-to-use-competitions-social-media-to-grow-your-business-399/</guid>
      <description>Running competitions using social media is a good way for brands and businesses to create welcome visitors and friends to their sites. You can now take that competition mobile using mobile apps, games or mobile websites and you don’t have to use SMS.
Using Social Media to get your customers discovering you on their mobile Your marketing messages on social media sites like Twitter and Facebook can direct existing customers to discover your mobile website or to download a mobile app.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>