<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Twitter on Damien Saunders</title>
    <link>https://damien1.github.io/categories/twitter/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Twitter on Damien Saunders</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 13 Apr 2012 12:53:32 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://damien1.github.io/categories/twitter/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Twitter &amp;#8211; a few suggested alternatives to CoTweet or Hootsuite</title>
      <link>https://damien1.github.io/social-media/twitter/twitter-a-few-suggested-alternatives-to-cotweet-or-hootsuite-6680/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Apr 2012 12:53:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien1.github.io/social-media/twitter/twitter-a-few-suggested-alternatives-to-cotweet-or-hootsuite-6680/</guid>
      <description>Are you responsible for Twitter and Social Media in your business? Perhaps you’ve been feeling a bit lost after CoTweet closed its free version (shame on them) … here are a few alternatives you can look at
HootSuite
– yes I said alternative to CoTweet – personally, I like to use my own bit.ly Pro URL so this was not an option.
– Hootsuitehas a very reasonably priced premium version and it has clients for pretty much any device</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Popular Posts in Social Media</title>
      <link>https://damien1.github.io/social-media/popular-posts-in-social-media-5515/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2011 16:34:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien1.github.io/social-media/popular-posts-in-social-media-5515/</guid>
      <description>It’s time to catchup on some missed out reading and enjoy the break. So here is a collection of 10 of the best Social Media resources that you love to read.
So I’m not going to second guess these related posts – I’m sure there will be stuff about Twitter, Facebook, Email Marketing and Foursquare.
[related_posts limit=”10″”]</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What do you think of the #newnewTwitter</title>
      <link>https://damien1.github.io/social-media/twitter/what-do-you-think-of-the-newnewtwitter-5243/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2011 18:00:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien1.github.io/social-media/twitter/what-do-you-think-of-the-newnewtwitter-5243/</guid>
      <description>So what do you think of the new look for Twitter? It’s feeling cleaner and the style change adds some freshness.

But is this the first step in the wrong direction for brand pages? Will we all end-up with old-skool MySpace style pages?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tweet Tweet &amp;#8212; WordTwit Pro is here</title>
      <link>https://damien1.github.io/social-media/twitter/tweet-tweet-wordtwit-pro-is-here-3805/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jun 2011 12:33:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien1.github.io/social-media/twitter/tweet-tweet-wordtwit-pro-is-here-3805/</guid>
      <description>Tweet Tweet — bang bang
WordTwit Pro is here … this could be the best new tool for Twitter &amp;amp; WordPress
 If you want to find out how to enable WordPress and Twitter then get in contact.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting Twitter Tools to work with MarsEdit</title>
      <link>https://damien1.github.io/social-media/twitter/getting-twitter-tools-to-work-with-marsedit-2870/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Apr 2011 20:13:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien1.github.io/social-media/twitter/getting-twitter-tools-to-work-with-marsedit-2870/</guid>
      <description>Just wondering if this works — I’m trying to make MarsEdit work with a plugin that I love called TwitterTools
If you know about this plugin and using external editors then let me know.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Twitter my recommendation don’t Auto Follow</title>
      <link>https://damien1.github.io/social-media/twitter/twitter-my-recommendation-dont-auto-follow-1863/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Nov 2010 09:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien1.github.io/social-media/twitter/twitter-my-recommendation-dont-auto-follow-1863/</guid>
      <description>Results Prove Dont Auto Follow I have not Auto-Followed Twitterers for some time – as I try to focus on building some relationship (!!!) with people who I choose to follow. If I follow you, it’s cause I’m interested in what you do or who you are.
In the screenshot below from CoTweet (my favourite Twitter Tool) – this is just a few of the Auto-DM messages I have been receiving and most are from Twitter Pyramid Plan Selling people trying to skim a few bits of cash from me clicking on their message or buying in to their marketing scheme.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UPDATED: Twitter Tools &amp;#8211; CoTweet best for your business</title>
      <link>https://damien1.github.io/social-media/twitter-tools-cotweet-best-for-your-business-1549/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Sep 2010 11:00:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien1.github.io/social-media/twitter-tools-cotweet-best-for-your-business-1549/</guid>
      <description>CoTweet provides the easiest way for your business to start managing your company or brand on Twitter. If you already are using HootSuite or Tweetdeck you should stop for a minute and check you are doing the right thing for your business. CoTweetis designed for the multi-user / multi-site (!!) environment with assignment, archiving and other management tools – this means you’ll never lose a tweet again (or have to share the computer with your boss).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Are Twitter Followers better than Fans?</title>
      <link>https://damien1.github.io/social-media/twitter/are-twitter-followers-better-than-fans-1538/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Sep 2010 11:00:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien1.github.io/social-media/twitter/are-twitter-followers-better-than-fans-1538/</guid>
      <description>Are Twitter Followers better than Facebook Fanswas a topic discussed on emarketer recently. It’s a question I get asked all the time – relatively speaking – Which is the best social network to start social media marketing? The thing is you need to try them both at the same time.And here is the problem every social network has its pro’s and cons – and here is the answer. If you were a criminal, on trial in the Old Bailey, the prosecution’s job is to prove you had the intention of committing a crime, so it was just an accident.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>