<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>mobile apps on Damien Saunders</title>
    <link>https://damien.co/tags/mobile-apps/</link>
    <description>Recent content in mobile apps on Damien Saunders</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2012 13:12:03 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://damien.co/tags/mobile-apps/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Get Results from an Android Mobile Marketing Strategy</title>
      <link>https://damien.co/mobile-marketing/get-results-from-an-android-mobile-marketing-strategy-5885/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2012 13:12:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien.co/mobile-marketing/get-results-from-an-android-mobile-marketing-strategy-5885/</guid>
      <description>Android Mobiles are taking over the world … and that seems to be supported by the latest statistics or _trends. _If you’re thinking about mobile marketing .. and wondering ‘what is all the fuss about Android’, then this presentation is for you.
Only the latest Android Insights and Statistics  10 billion app downloads (December 2011) 200 million activated devices (November 2011) 400,000 Android Apps (December 2011)  We can only wait for the next Google I/O conference to confirm how these numbers are growing!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Customer Service via Web &amp;#038; Email &amp;#8211; Who didn&amp;#8217;t test your web mail form O2</title>
      <link>https://damien.co/mobile-marketing/customer-service-via-web-email-who-didnt-test-your-web-mail-form-o2-3109/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2011 11:40:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien.co/mobile-marketing/customer-service-via-web-email-who-didnt-test-your-web-mail-form-o2-3109/</guid>
      <description>Well hello Customer Service and Customer Management consultants … who here is reading this and is building a business case for improved customer service by moving customers to self care tools such as web forms and e-mail? Most of you reading this are probably think about it constantly. THEN DON’T DO IT unless you’ve gone and tested it and got it right.
I recently got an iPad 2 – an upgrade from my first iPad … Some nice marketing product person at O2 figured out an email with a link to reset the iPad MAC address so I can continue to use free wifi would be helpful.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[video] Online Shopping with Swedish Twist &amp;#8211; 3 LiveShop</title>
      <link>https://damien.co/strategy/video-online-shopping-with-swedish-twist-3-liveshop-3039/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2011 10:09:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien.co/strategy/video-online-shopping-with-swedish-twist-3-liveshop-3039/</guid>
      <description>Have you seen this … This has to be the future of customer service and online shopping — say goodbye to messy forms or complicated shopping charts. Those crazy people in Tre Sweden www.tre.se just like to push the envelope here. And maybe some of those other mobile operators or utility providers can do this too.
Once you’ve checked out this promo video – go take a look at the 3 LiveShop – it uses Adobe Flash embed video chat for the fun stuff.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Must have Android Apps for Marketing Consultants</title>
      <link>https://damien.co/marketing-consultant-2/must-have-android-apps-for-marketing-consultants-2866/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Apr 2011 10:33:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien.co/marketing-consultant-2/must-have-android-apps-for-marketing-consultants-2866/</guid>
      <description>What shortcuts or widgets should you save to the desktop of you Anrdoid phone? As a marketing consultant I’ve customised my phone lots (thanks to Cyanogenmod) .. but my desktop stays the same.
I don’t have many widgets as they eat up battery life (and annoyingly want internet connection).
What’s on your Android Desktop? Winamp – best music player for Android
Now that I have a larger long-life battery – I’m back to listening to music on my phone.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Android Market would benefit Developer instead of Apple App Certification?</title>
      <link>https://damien.co/blog/android/android-market-benefits-developer-apples-app-certification-515/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Mar 2010 22:29:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien.co/blog/android/android-market-benefits-developer-apples-app-certification-515/</guid>
      <description>Develop apps for Android or develop mobile apps for Apple, some days its hard to figure out just what to do. On this website I’ve written a lot on Android phones and apps.Around 6000 apps have been removed from the Apple store recently due to their erotic nature. It’s not that Android Market has no quality control – Adult or Erotic does not exist as a content category in Android Market but dating apps or other soft-porn apps so far have not shown huge growth (ahem) on Android.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>5 Essential tips for promoting your charity or cause using mobile marketing</title>
      <link>https://damien.co/mobile-marketing/essential-tips-promotions-charities-mobile-451/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Feb 2010 07:44:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien.co/mobile-marketing/essential-tips-promotions-charities-mobile-451/</guid>
      <description>For non-profit organisations, charities and cause related marketing the mobile can provide the best integrated marketing solution for campaigns. There are a number of tools and techniques which can be used to promote your cause or help to raise donations.
1. SMS Premium Text Donations Making donations using your mobile is as simple as sending a text to a special number. For the not so concerned and the lazy its a quick way to send a few dollars, euros or pounds to a worthy cause.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Foursquare Best Location Based Social Networking for Android UK Users</title>
      <link>https://damien.co/social-media/foursquare-best-location-based-social-networking-455/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Feb 2010 18:56:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien.co/social-media/foursquare-best-location-based-social-networking-455/</guid>
      <description>Android mobile owners in the UK will be pleased to know that location based social networkingapps have begun to improve and increase in the number of users. In the past few weeks, top location based social networks such as Brightkiteand Foursquarehave really improved the quality and details of UK locations.**
**
It is a problem of user experience that meant many of these services had few UK users and no UK points of interest.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Where to start building mobile apps for large screens &amp;#8211; mobile agencies beware</title>
      <link>https://damien.co/mobile-marketing/where-to-start-building-mobile-apps-for-large-screens-mobile-agencies-beware-422/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jan 2010 15:28:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien.co/mobile-marketing/where-to-start-building-mobile-apps-for-large-screens-mobile-agencies-beware-422/</guid>
      <description>Where to start with building a mobile app or going mobile has been a popular topic for some time. Many FMCG brands and agencies are requesting only quotes for mobile apps – forgetting the less popular java app or branded mobile game. At the expense of budget – haha – focusing on a mobile app can be a costly exercise starting from about 10k to 100k plus.
Marketing Agencies and their Brands need to go and reconsider their mobile strategy – and if you’ve already built a mobile app – you maybe disappointed how it looks on the larger screen devices.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gartner Says Consumers Will Download 4,500,000,000 Mobile Apps in 2010</title>
      <link>https://damien.co/general/gartner-says-consumers-will-download-over-4-billion-mobile-apps-in-2010-420/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Jan 2010 14:33:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien.co/general/gartner-says-consumers-will-download-over-4-billion-mobile-apps-in-2010-420/</guid>
      <description>This week Gartner reported that consumers will spend a headline figure of £3.8 billion pounds ($6.2 billion USD) in mobile apps during this year. The forecast estimates total downloads to be 4,500,000,000. The numbers are eye wateringly large.
Gartners forecast goes on to mention that 82 per cent of downloads would be free apps … leaving 18 per cent of downloads to come up with cash.
4.5 billion downloads is quite staggering – even if Apple is set to announce its about to hit its 3 billionth download.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vote in my Mobile Marketing and Mobile Apps Poll</title>
      <link>https://damien.co/mobile-marketing/vote-in-my-mobile-marketing-and-mobile-apps-poll-379/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Dec 2009 13:59:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien.co/mobile-marketing/vote-in-my-mobile-marketing-and-mobile-apps-poll-379/</guid>
      <description>Take a vote … what do you do for mobile marketing and have you tried any mobile apps?
http://polls.linkedin.com/p/69091/tbhgt</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>