<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Web stats on Damien Saunders</title>
    <link>http://damien.co/tags/web-stats/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Web stats on Damien Saunders</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2013 20:39:24 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://damien.co/tags/web-stats/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>2012 Website Statistics &amp;#8211; Content Strategy is not buzz words like SEO</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/2012-website-statistics-awesome-8541/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2013 20:39:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/2012-website-statistics-awesome-8541/</guid>
      <description>2012 was the biggest year to date for web site visitors – and with good reason! So Thank You to everyone who came, read and left (and came back, again).
55,266 unique visitors clocked up 5.1 million seconds of visit duration but more importantly pages / visit and average visit duration also grew.
 So what happened in 2012? Search Engine Optimisation (SEO) didn’t work out … but having a content strategy did.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>4 reasons to choose Google Analytics for your business</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/marketing-consultant-2/4-reasons-to-choose-google-analytics-for-your-business-4932/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2011 16:13:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/marketing-consultant-2/4-reasons-to-choose-google-analytics-for-your-business-4932/</guid>
      <description>Google Analytics is one of the web’s most popular tools for reporting on activity and trends for just about any website. Your online and offline marketing activities need meaningful analytics data to create actionable insights. In summary, website analytics has benefits for sales, marketing and product development – in fact most areas of your business.
Why Choose Google Analytics? It’s easy to see why Google Analytics is so popular, because it’s free, but here are my top 4</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Where did all those Stats Go?</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/where-did-all-those-stats-go-2814/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2011 20:02:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/where-did-all-those-stats-go-2814/</guid>
      <description>Where did all my stats go!
That’s a very good question – apparently I’ve been suffering from a problem that Google no longer likes my domain name. This is a very nasty problem – even more so because the error message offers very little hope.
  The site “http://damien.co” has not been registered.
  My site is registered with Google Webmaster, I use Google Apps for my Domain — what else is there that needs to be Google-ified?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>