<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>lbs on Damien Saunders</title>
    <link>https://damien.co/tags/lbs/</link>
    <description>Recent content in lbs on Damien Saunders</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 07 Jul 2010 09:00:10 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://damien.co/tags/lbs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Foursquare most popular location checkin game in London</title>
      <link>https://damien.co/social-media/foursquare-most-popular-location-checkin-tool-in-london-1173/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jul 2010 09:00:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien.co/social-media/foursquare-most-popular-location-checkin-tool-in-london-1173/</guid>
      <description>Foursquare is still the UK’s most popular location based check-in game to play on your mobile. I’ve said it before that Foursquare would come out on tops over Gowalla and Brightkite.
These maps (thanks to Checkin Mania) indicate the difference in the number of locations that users have submitted to each service. The growth from crowd sourced locations and points of interest reflects in the growth of that services usage (ie the most popular service gets the most contributions from users) The point of reference is London Borough Market – one of the more famous places in London to visit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Foursquare Best Location Based Social Networking for Android UK Users</title>
      <link>https://damien.co/social-media/foursquare-best-location-based-social-networking-455/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Feb 2010 18:56:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien.co/social-media/foursquare-best-location-based-social-networking-455/</guid>
      <description>Android mobile owners in the UK will be pleased to know that location based social networkingapps have begun to improve and increase in the number of users. In the past few weeks, top location based social networks such as Brightkiteand Foursquarehave really improved the quality and details of UK locations.**
**
It is a problem of user experience that meant many of these services had few UK users and no UK points of interest.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2 Must have Android Apps from Google</title>
      <link>https://damien.co/general/2-must-have-android-apps-from-google-for-your-htc-magic-or-g1-226/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2009 18:11:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien.co/general/2-must-have-android-apps-from-google-for-your-htc-magic-or-g1-226/</guid>
      <description>Looking for somewhere to go …. Maybe you need to waste some time or want to find something else to try on your Google Android G1 or HTC Magic.
Google obviously has embedded a lot things into the phone – but here are 2 apps that were not installed on the Android phone when you open the box.
Places DirectoryPrice FREE Downloads &amp;gt;250,000
updated — 21 Sept –– Even before augmented reality became a buzzword … Google Places Directory was already bringing Google Maps together with GPS / Location Based Services.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>