<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>jQuery on Damien Saunders</title>
    <link>https://damien.co/tags/jquery/</link>
    <description>Recent content in jQuery on Damien Saunders</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2013 12:00:13 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://damien.co/tags/jquery/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>How to integrate your own Isotope jQuery plugin with your WordPress</title>
      <link>https://damien.co/blog/2013-04-28-how-to-integrate-your-own-isotope-jquery-plugin-with-your-wordpress/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2013 12:00:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien.co/blog/2013-04-28-how-to-integrate-your-own-isotope-jquery-plugin-with-your-wordpress/</guid>
      <description>I was recently asked if it was easy to integrate Isotope jQuery plugin into a WordPress website. It’s not uncomplicated to add isotope.js to your website – it’s just not as easy as linking a script to your header.
2 Ways to add Isotope jQuery Plugin to WordPress As always, there are (at least) 2 ways to achieve this
 Create a page template for the purpose – with all the code you want Add the code to your themes function.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Isotope &#43; filtrify &#43; WordPress = No Sweat</title>
      <link>https://damien.co/blog/2012-09-08-isotope-filtrify-wordpress-no-sweat/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Sep 2012 16:35:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien.co/blog/2012-09-08-isotope-filtrify-wordpress-no-sweat/</guid>
      <description>I’ve been busy this weekend catching up on some development work for my favourite WordPress plugin Visual Post Layouts which uses Isotope.
Today I’ve integrated filtrifywhich makes it easy to choose your posts by Category.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Using Isotope &amp;#038; masonry with WordPress</title>
      <link>https://damien.co/blog/2012-04-07-using-isotope-masonry-with-wordpress/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Apr 2012 12:56:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien.co/blog/2012-04-07-using-isotope-masonry-with-wordpress/</guid>
      <description>So I have been using Isotope for sometime on my website … I was recently asked why I had stopped using Isotope at which point I discovered that it had stopped working when I changed my theme.
Using jQuery instead of $ for javascript The basic script for isotope is …
[php]
[/php]
However, WordPress reserves the use of $ so you need to change your script to
[php]
[/php]</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A couple more examples of impressive jQuery and JS</title>
      <link>https://damien.co/blog/couple-more-examples-of-impressive-js-jquery-5974/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2012 11:30:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien.co/blog/couple-more-examples-of-impressive-js-jquery-5974/</guid>
      <description>jQuery and Javascript may not be all that bad for you .. or your website.
Recently I’ve been looking into fluid and responsive layouts for web design and I’ve been using a jQuery framework called Isotope on my blog page.
Isotope looks like it can do magical things. If only I had the time to make it work properly.
So here are two more impressive examples of what you can do with .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting started with Isotope &amp;#038; WordPress</title>
      <link>https://damien.co/blog/2011-12-10-getting-started-with-isotope-wordpress/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Dec 2011 15:26:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien.co/blog/2011-12-10-getting-started-with-isotope-wordpress/</guid>
      <description>If you’re interested in customising WordPress then consider building a fluid grid design with a layout that automatically responds as the page is resized.
I’m using Isotope with the latest version of WordPress 3.3 release candidate.
Isotope – An exquisite jQuery Plugin for magical layouts With a few days to spare do check out Isotope from David Desandro. This example uses the periodic table
Have a look as well at Desandro’s examples – click a few of the buttons on the Filter.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>