<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Customer Relationship Management on Damien Saunders</title>
    <link>http://damien.co/tags/customer-relationship-management/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Customer Relationship Management on Damien Saunders</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2011 10:14:49 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://damien.co/tags/customer-relationship-management/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Zoho CRM what is a lead vs contact vs opportunity</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/2011-10-26-zoho-crm-what-is-a-lead-vs-contact-vs-opportunity/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2011 10:14:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/2011-10-26-zoho-crm-what-is-a-lead-vs-contact-vs-opportunity/</guid>
      <description>Zoho CRM is a cloud based SaaS (software as a service) for customer relationship management (CRM). How to setup and manage new and potential business contacts in Zoho raises the question – what is a lead, what is a contact and what is a potential in Zoho ‘Jargon’. Managing Leads, Contacts and Accounts is a critical function of your business and it’s just as important that you understand Zoho’s sales management process.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Customer Service via Web &amp;#038; Email &amp;#8211; Who didn&amp;#8217;t test your web mail form O2</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/mobile-marketing/customer-service-via-web-email-who-didnt-test-your-web-mail-form-o2-3109/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2011 11:40:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/mobile-marketing/customer-service-via-web-email-who-didnt-test-your-web-mail-form-o2-3109/</guid>
      <description>Well hello Customer Service and Customer Management consultants … who here is reading this and is building a business case for improved customer service by moving customers to self care tools such as web forms and e-mail? Most of you reading this are probably think about it constantly. THEN DON’T DO IT unless you’ve gone and tested it and got it right.
I recently got an iPad 2 – an upgrade from my first iPad … Some nice marketing product person at O2 figured out an email with a link to reset the iPad MAC address so I can continue to use free wifi would be helpful.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[video] Online Shopping with Swedish Twist &amp;#8211; 3 LiveShop</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/strategy/video-online-shopping-with-swedish-twist-3-liveshop-3039/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2011 10:09:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/strategy/video-online-shopping-with-swedish-twist-3-liveshop-3039/</guid>
      <description>Have you seen this … This has to be the future of customer service and online shopping — say goodbye to messy forms or complicated shopping charts. Those crazy people in Tre Sweden www.tre.se just like to push the envelope here. And maybe some of those other mobile operators or utility providers can do this too.
Once you’ve checked out this promo video – go take a look at the 3 LiveShop – it uses Adobe Flash embed video chat for the fun stuff.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ZOHO CRM do you use your own custom web form? Then change to https</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/2010-04-21-zoho-crm-do-you-use-your-own-custom-web-from-then-change-to-https/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Apr 2010 14:14:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/2010-04-21-zoho-crm-do-you-use-your-own-custom-web-from-then-change-to-https/</guid>
      <description>ZOHO CRM has some great features including web to lead forms – but they don’t really look too stylish. Especially if you use 3rd party tools for your web forms.
If you use custom web to lead forms you may have to make the change to using the more secure HTTPS connection. After I noticed the web to lead form was not working I checked the standard code from ZOHO.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HOW TO sign-up to Zoho CRM in 4 steps using Google Apps or Gmail</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/social-crm/how-to-sign-up-to-zoho-crm-in-4-steps-using-google-apps-or-gmail-767/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Mar 2010 19:38:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/social-crm/how-to-sign-up-to-zoho-crm-in-4-steps-using-google-apps-or-gmail-767/</guid>
      <description>So you choose to use ZOHO CRM because it’s a great web based solutionfor customer relationship management. There are now 3 ways to sign-up to ZOHO CRMusing Google Appsor a Gmailaddress.  Google Apps – If you are an administrator you can add ZOHO CRM from the Google Apps Marketplace  Google Apps – Sign-up online and create a ZOHO account at the same time
  Gmail – as above, signup online and create a ZOHO account at the same time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zoho CRM best free web based CRM included in Google Apps Marketplace</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/2010-03-14-zoho-crm-best-free-web-based-crm-included-in-google-apps-marketplace/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Mar 2010 23:04:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/2010-03-14-zoho-crm-best-free-web-based-crm-included-in-google-apps-marketplace/</guid>
      <description>ZOHO CRM, which I reckon is the best free CRM for the web or SaaSis now available to add from the new Google Apps Marketplace.
(note if you’re already using ZOHO CRM with Google Apps you are better to leave things as they are for now)
What is CRM? Customer Relationship Management or CRM is really about 3 things:
 Building up knowledge on the people you do with business with or relate to – your clients, customers and the companies they work for Communicating with your customers and managing those ‘relationships’ Selling your stuff, or supporting your clients and staff to sell  In the past business process managers would have focused on Managing Customers as a key process for the Customer Lifecycle.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zoho CRM How to choose a Web Based CRM solution</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/social-crm/zoho-crm-how-to-choose-a-web-based-crm-solution-365/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Mar 2010 00:02:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/social-crm/zoho-crm-how-to-choose-a-web-based-crm-solution-365/</guid>
      <description>Inbound Marketers, Sales managers, customer care, account managers, business development managers – all need a good system for managing diaries, customer details and leads. Managing your sCRM using something like Zoho CRM means you have access to all your customer relationship data anywhere you are. And you don’t have to install anything on your Mac, PC or Linux operating system, just open your favourite web browser.
What is CRM? Customer Relationship Management (CRM) is an art and a science.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mobile Marketing Strategies &amp;#8211; Mobile CRM</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/2010-02-08-mobile-marketing-strategies-mobile-crm/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Feb 2010 09:47:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/2010-02-08-mobile-marketing-strategies-mobile-crm/</guid>
      <description>**Until recently mobile devices were often overlooked by marketing managers in favour of online campaigns or traditional paper-based direct marketing. However, brands, ad agencies and telecoms operators are increasingly using mobile as part of their customer relationship management (CRM) strategy. ** The rapid growth in smartphones spurred by the iPhone, Windows Mobile and Android has given mobile marketing a major boost. The latest devices offer fast and easy web access, often with flat-rate charges.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>