<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>My Blog on Damien Saunders</title>
    <link>https://damien.co/categories/my-blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in My Blog on Damien Saunders</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2014 16:58:19 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://damien.co/categories/my-blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Having a break</title>
      <link>https://damien.co/blog/2014-09-01-having-a-break/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2014 16:58:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien.co/blog/2014-09-01-having-a-break/</guid>
      <description>Hello from Genoa, Italy</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello World Redux</title>
      <link>https://damien.co/blog/hello-world-redux-8723/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2013 09:59:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien.co/blog/hello-world-redux-8723/</guid>
      <description>For the past month (2 or 3 months??) I’ve been more than quiet – I’ve really not been around. So this is just me saying ‘Hello World’ again.
Actually it’s been a crazy time – I’ve spent 6 weeks working in Maastricht in the Netherlands (or Holland if you don’t know better) which was an eye opener of an IT programme. And then … I moved house.
Finally, I changed to working on the deployment of another CRM system for MVNO’s.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>On being quiet – and being busy: impact on web analytics and content strategy</title>
      <link>https://damien.co/blog/on-being-quiet-and-being-busy-impact-on-web-analytics-and-content-strategy-8675/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2013 14:11:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien.co/blog/on-being-quiet-and-being-busy-impact-on-web-analytics-and-content-strategy-8675/</guid>
      <description>You may not have noticed, but I have … I’ve been quiet, and not been adding any new posts or updates to any of my WordPress plugin. I’ve also been busy and there are never enough hours in the day. I want to set out some thoughts on how a content strategy might help or detract.
Google Analytics One interesting Google Analytics trend that pops up when I look at my stats over a long period (try 3 years) is that these busy peaks (at work) also correlate with the downward slumps in visitor numbers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What a difference a year makes - making a fashion statement</title>
      <link>https://damien.co/blog/2013-05-11-what-a-difference-a-year-makes-making-a-fashion-statement/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2013 09:28:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien.co/blog/2013-05-11-what-a-difference-a-year-makes-making-a-fashion-statement/</guid>
      <description>This time last year … almost 12 months now, I was a keen follower of fashion. My wardrobe was made up of some of the best jeans money could buy. I only wore jeans, I&amp;rsquo;d always wear a long sleeve dress shirt and was starting to realise that a black dress shirt is amazing. I&amp;rsquo;d keep my eyes on the fashion rags and was always looking for another cool pair of jeans.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>5 Things that Can Derail Your Freelance Career</title>
      <link>https://damien.co/blog/5-things-that-can-derail-your-freelance-career-8024/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2012 13:45:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien.co/blog/5-things-that-can-derail-your-freelance-career-8024/</guid>
      <description>There actually are many things that can de-rail a successful freelance career and perhaps these 5 should have your attention.
The 2 that I think are important to always beware of are:
 Keeping your eye out for ‘something better’ (such as taking a permanent role) Being too successful and not being able to take on more people  5 Things that Can Derail Your Freelance Career: “There are many things that can turn everything upside down.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WTF! TomTom you make Apple Maps really do suck</title>
      <link>https://damien.co/blog/wtf-tomtom-you-make-apple-maps-really-do-suck-7849/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Sep 2012 08:44:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien.co/blog/wtf-tomtom-you-make-apple-maps-really-do-suck-7849/</guid>
      <description>To me, I used Apple Maps on my iPad to check walking directions. So why is Apple Maps now powered by a Sat nav company like TomTom. Apparently I have to pay tollS to walk 6m to my home … Not just one toll … That&amp;rsquo;s tolls.
And annoyingly all map data is now from some sat nav company so you can&amp;rsquo;t get walking directions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Your favorite apps, with Google Drive (Trello I use every day)</title>
      <link>https://damien.co/blog/your-favorite-apps-with-google-drive-trello-i-use-every-day-7805/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Sep 2012 13:48:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien.co/blog/your-favorite-apps-with-google-drive-trello-i-use-every-day-7805/</guid>
      <description>Google Drive and Google Apps for Business form the core of my ‘enterprise IT’ requirements.
Google Drive is mostly for document storage but I have a few documents that open daily via my Android or iPad. I’ve not been in a business yet that could stomach shared / co-authored documents.
 and Trello is my favourite project management / planner / scrum board / anything app right now.
   “Google Drive is a place where you can create, share and keep all your stuff — so you can live online and get things done in the cloud.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Everything Everwhere Rebrands As EE, Brings “Super-Fast” 4G LTE Service To The UK</title>
      <link>https://damien.co/blog/everything-everwhere-rebrands-as-ee-brings-super-fast-4g-lte-service-to-the-uk-7789/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Sep 2012 21:44:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien.co/blog/everything-everwhere-rebrands-as-ee-brings-super-fast-4g-lte-service-to-the-uk-7789/</guid>
      <description>Get your high speed LTE mobile devices ready to rumble …
So it’s official what everyone has known for some time … EE is no longer just a 2 letter acronym for people who couldn’t be bother to say 2 words … Everything and Everywhere.
The second thing we know is there will be a great range of phones available for sale from ‘soon’ but the court hearings and legal wrangling have yet to ‘stop’ the EE selling these devices.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why You Don’t Need Mac Anti-Virus Software &amp;#8211; Plus What You Do Need</title>
      <link>https://damien.co/blog/why-you-dont-need-mac-anti-virus-software-plus-what-you-do-need-7777/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Sep 2012 15:19:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien.co/blog/why-you-dont-need-mac-anti-virus-software-plus-what-you-do-need-7777/</guid>
      <description>I’ve been using Apple Macbook Pro as my primary work horse since 2008. I’ve always had ClamXav installed as a ‘heuristic’ solution to monitor apps and downloads for virus and malware.
I’m a fan of sandbox for apps, but as I do develop a whole heap of different things, just installing from the Mac App Store is not an option for me.
Now I’m going to look for other software ….</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3 articles to read on Brand Marketing &amp;#038; Strategy</title>
      <link>https://damien.co/blog/3-articles-read-brand-marketing-strategy-7318/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Jun 2012 17:19:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien.co/blog/3-articles-read-brand-marketing-strategy-7318/</guid>
      <description>You’ll love these 3 articles by Mark Ritson who has a weekly opinion piece in Marketing Week. His column is the inside, back page and the first article I read.
Why Graff Diamonds Failed to list on the Hong Kong Stock Exchange (old school luxury brand)
Link &amp;gt; Marketing Week— is this not the same trap for other FTSE100 and multinationals? becoming old-fashioned and lacking brand appeal
Apple’s leadership bios look about as diverse as an Alabama country club circa 1961</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What&amp;#8217;s Hot this Week? Curators Code</title>
      <link>https://damien.co/blog/whats-hot-this-week-curators-code-6977/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 May 2012 11:12:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien.co/blog/whats-hot-this-week-curators-code-6977/</guid>
      <description>Hats Off (HT) to Wired UK for the tip about Curators’s Code. What’s the Curator’s Codeyou might well ask … Actually it’s a great idea to make content attribution easier and recognise that not everything you read on the Internet is new.
Content Attribution is not a licence to use It’s great idea to always attribute and recognise your info sources – I should think it is mandatory if you are aggregatingcontent (which is almost akin to stealing someone else’s work).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I&amp;#8217;m moving &amp;#8211; migrating to a new domain (some glitches)</title>
      <link>https://damien.co/blog/im-moving-migrating-to-a-new-domain-some-glitches-6809/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Apr 2012 13:16:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien.co/blog/im-moving-migrating-to-a-new-domain-some-glitches-6809/</guid>
      <description>Well it had to happen … I’ve found a better domain damien.co and I’ve completed the biggest hurdle to migrate from damiensaunders.com to damien.co
There are a flew glitches which I’m trying to sort out today.
The most obvious one is that sub-domains are not redirecting
so to get to wordpress.damiensaunders.com you need to go to wordpress.damien.co</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I have ADHD</title>
      <link>https://damien.co/blog/i-have-adhd-6622/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Apr 2012 20:23:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien.co/blog/i-have-adhd-6622/</guid>
      <description>I have ADHD … and I have lived with this every day of my life since junior / primary school. As an Adult ADHDer, it’s only now, nearly 5 years after my ‘clinical diagnosis’ that I feel I can say I have ADHD. I’ve preferred to keep it a secret.
I’ve wanted to avoid negative stereotypes We automatically attach labels to people we know and interact with … we do this so we can understand the world we live.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Justinmind &amp;#8211; stop with the spam comments</title>
      <link>https://damien.co/blog/justinmind-stop-with-the-spam-comments-6295/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Mar 2012 19:49:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien.co/blog/justinmind-stop-with-the-spam-comments-6295/</guid>
      <description>Since I first mentioned Axure – about 3 months back, I’ve started being harassed by a creepy socialmedia ‘person’ belonging to Justinmind.
This is what it leaves in my comments
It’s not just one comment – it’s usually 2 in the same day and annoyingly … I have to think that someone at Justinmind is doing this.
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Facebook Deleted</title>
      <link>https://damien.co/blog/facebook-deleted-6279/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Mar 2012 23:11:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien.co/blog/facebook-deleted-6279/</guid>
      <description>I did it … really did it … I deleted my Facebook account … I deactivated it first about 12 months back and then 2 weeks back I did it again. If you know me well enough, you’ll know I’m an over-connected Digital ‘Immigrant’ though I feel like a Native.
So Facebook has been deleted now .. I want to keep in contact with friends and family. Not just read about their lives and make random guesses about what’s going on.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>When done is really done &amp;#8211; Scrum &amp;#038; post it note management</title>
      <link>https://damien.co/blog/when-done-is-really-done-scrum-post-it-note-management-6269/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Mar 2012 22:44:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien.co/blog/when-done-is-really-done-scrum-post-it-note-management-6269/</guid>
      <description>There really is nothing better then looking at your office wall and knowing that done is done.
Post-it Note management has to be one of the easiest and most effective ways to create a wall board – information radiator – which you and your management can all follow.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The latest work &amp;#8211; Virgin Media presents</title>
      <link>https://damien.co/blog/the-latest-work-virgin-media-presents-6205/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2012 16:44:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien.co/blog/the-latest-work-virgin-media-presents-6205/</guid>
      <description>It’s here — your unmissable week ahead
If you’re not with Virgin Media – then you’re missing out.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>30 minutes a day &amp;#8211; every day to write something</title>
      <link>https://damien.co/blog/30-minutes-a-day-every-day-to-write-something-6085/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jan 2012 11:23:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien.co/blog/30-minutes-a-day-every-day-to-write-something-6085/</guid>
      <description>30 minutes a day … every day. That’s how much time I need once I’ve got a concept for an article to publish here. I just need to find the time. Lately, I’ve not had the time for that 30 minutes – too tired, too busy, too many other things to do.
A lot of regular bloggers and social media consultants insist on blogging everyday. But that’s a chore and regular blogging is part of trying to win at SEO and social media optimisation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Website re-design and planning</title>
      <link>https://damien.co/blog/6080-6080/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2012 20:19:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien.co/blog/6080-6080/</guid>
      <description>I’d be lying if I said ‘I never change anything on my website‘. Absolutely lying. Actually I change something on here every week. Bits of code, bits of UE, bits of content. Always be fine tuning and always be tweaking your work is what I think.
In my ‘world’ it’s important to be learning new things and improving existing things. So when you run out of steam and energy … what do you do?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Web server performance &amp;#8211; usage and load</title>
      <link>https://damien.co/blog/web-server-performance-usage-and-load-5987/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2012 22:00:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien.co/blog/web-server-performance-usage-and-load-5987/</guid>
      <description>Web Application Development can seem easy if you’re used to a shared host and WordPress running out of the box. Moving into the world of unmanaged VPS can be daunting at first – or really easy if you’re insane.
If you’ve got access to a terminal or CLI – command line interface then you have here a number of options for checking your website performance. Here’s a few choice one’s I’ve been using lately.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A couple more examples of impressive jQuery and JS</title>
      <link>https://damien.co/blog/couple-more-examples-of-impressive-js-jquery-5974/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2012 11:30:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien.co/blog/couple-more-examples-of-impressive-js-jquery-5974/</guid>
      <description>jQuery and Javascript may not be all that bad for you .. or your website.
Recently I’ve been looking into fluid and responsive layouts for web design and I’ve been using a jQuery framework called Isotope on my blog page.
Isotope looks like it can do magical things. If only I had the time to make it work properly.
So here are two more impressive examples of what you can do with .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcome to 2012 &amp;#8211; You made it!</title>
      <link>https://damien.co/blog/welcome-to-2012-you-made-it-5275/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2012 11:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien.co/blog/welcome-to-2012-you-made-it-5275/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to 2012 … and yes, you made it! There is no point in a retrospective, stuff happened and we learn from it. There is no point on pre-guessing what will happen, stuff happens and we react to it.
However you may want to look at it – we made it this far. It’s a new year, so enjoy it … while it lasts.
Thanks
Damien</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dead Mac Day what a struggle</title>
      <link>https://damien.co/blog/dead-mac-day-what-a-struggle-4218/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jul 2011 08:53:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien.co/blog/dead-mac-day-what-a-struggle-4218/</guid>
      <description>Monday will now be called DEAD MAC DAY – July 4, 2011
I didn’t even have a chance to say goodbye … I just came home to a mac with a flashing folder when I opened the lid.
Lucky for me, it’s my newest mac … Unlucky for me I lost most of a weekends’ work including e nearly finished guide to foursquare.
So that’s actually going to change a heap of plans … The apple store has completed my repair so I just hope it was only a faulty hard drive connector cable.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Back from holidays &amp;#8211; what projects do you need help with?</title>
      <link>https://damien.co/blog/back-from-holidays-what-projects-do-you-need-help-with-4068/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jun 2011 11:33:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien.co/blog/back-from-holidays-what-projects-do-you-need-help-with-4068/</guid>
      <description>So after a several weeks holiday … as of now, I’m a free agent looking for new work and a new project to get stuck into.
 Are you looking for a consultant or marketing manager to help out? If you’re in need of a new product manager, marketing consultant or someone to start pulling together a marketing strategy then get in contact.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>On holiday &amp;#8211; back next week</title>
      <link>https://damien.co/blog/on-holiday-back-next-week-3988/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jun 2011 11:34:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien.co/blog/on-holiday-back-next-week-3988/</guid>
      <description>Hi everyone … I hope your June is going well? I’ve been away on holiday for the past week taking some time to visit colleagues and friends in Madrid.
 While I’ve been away, I’ve been researching and taking notes for a range of new features on social media, marketing strategy and mobile consulting.
 Watch-out from Monday!
 And I hope you’re enjoying your summer / winter
 Cheers</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learning to use Google Adsense</title>
      <link>https://damien.co/blog/learning-to-use-google-adsense-3510/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2011 11:24:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien.co/blog/learning-to-use-google-adsense-3510/</guid>
      <description>Hi … if you’re looking at this in your RSS feed reader will now notice at the bottom of each post there is now a Google Adsense ad.
 Last week I turned on Google Adsense – initially for my RSS feed. The reason I’m doing this is to learn and test different ad formats and learn how to manage and use Google Adsense.
I’ll be better able to advise you on your social media and digital marketing strategy by using products like Google Adsense.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Going Mobile &amp;#8211; I&amp;#8217;m in your face &amp;#8211; I&amp;#8217;m in your phone.</title>
      <link>https://damien.co/mobile-marketing/going-mobile-im-in-your-face-im-in-your-phone-2953/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 May 2011 13:24:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien.co/mobile-marketing/going-mobile-im-in-your-face-im-in-your-phone-2953/</guid>
      <description>Mobilising your web content and cross channel integrated marketing may sound like just a bunch of buzzwords to boost my SEO. But it’s not. So I’m helping you to understand the latest in mobile marketing, tools &amp;amp; techniques.
You can now visit http://damien.mobi from your smartphone and have the best experience a mobile can get. If you’re a fan of the iPad then you can also save this as a web app on your phone.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>damiens.ws &amp;#8211; A new look to Twitter via Bit.ly Pro</title>
      <link>https://damien.co/blog/damiens-ws-a-new-look-to-twitter-via-bit-ly-pro-2909/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Apr 2011 13:02:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien.co/blog/damiens-ws-a-new-look-to-twitter-via-bit-ly-pro-2909/</guid>
      <description>I’ve made a change to my Bit.ly Pro setup and switched to the domain damiens.ws for my URL shortener.
This will benefit me and you – the new domain damiens.ws is registered for 10 years. You’ll continue to get the same great news and views from yours truly if you follow me on Twitter @damiensaunders
You’ll see more changes like this to come – I suggest a single name brand might be one ‘strategy’ that I’m going to follow.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Where did all those Stats Go?</title>
      <link>https://damien.co/blog/where-did-all-those-stats-go-2814/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2011 20:02:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien.co/blog/where-did-all-those-stats-go-2814/</guid>
      <description>Where did all my stats go!
That’s a very good question – apparently I’ve been suffering from a problem that Google no longer likes my domain name. This is a very nasty problem – even more so because the error message offers very little hope.
  The site “http://damien.co” has not been registered.
  My site is registered with Google Webmaster, I use Google Apps for my Domain — what else is there that needs to be Google-ified?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I upgraded to Cyanogenmod 7 on HTC Desire</title>
      <link>https://damien.co/blog/i-upgraded-to-cyanogenmod-7-on-htc-desire-2780/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2011 09:16:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien.co/blog/i-upgraded-to-cyanogenmod-7-on-htc-desire-2780/</guid>
      <description>I just updated my HTC Desire to the new Cyanogenmod 7 rom and it’s been running fine. A part of me does miss the HTC Sense UE overlay .. but … meh. If you have already rooted your phone and been using Clockwork ROM Manager, you just need to go looking for the new Cyanogenmod 7 RC1.
The upgrade process is very simple – but here are a couple of pointers –</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WordPress Catchable Fatal Error &amp;#8211; resolved</title>
      <link>https://damien.co/blog/wordpress-catchable-fatal-error-2751/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Feb 2011 18:38:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien.co/blog/wordpress-catchable-fatal-error-2751/</guid>
      <description>If you’re reading this you would have noticed I’m having problems with my WordPress and I had a Catchable Fatal Error. It’s now on the path to recovery. The issue has been rectified – but not resolved. The problem started after I relied too much on Softaculous which is used by my hosting provider to update all my WordPress sites.
So always keep a backup and a backup of that backup … it makes life easier to recover from.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>London Startup Weekend will be back</title>
      <link>https://damien.co/blog/london-startup-weekend-will-be-back-2701/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Feb 2011 11:04:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien.co/blog/london-startup-weekend-will-be-back-2701/</guid>
      <description>So London Startup Weekend will happen … it has taken a lot longer to get the next weekend event going then we all thought. To be honest, Startup Weekend takes time and patience – patiently working with venue sponsors, helping them to gain internal approval and working through security issues.
Patience takes time .. so the next Startup Weekend will be happening soon. We’ve now got a team of about 6 people to work on London Startup Weekend and hopefully soon we’ll have a venue to really consider.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I have a bug &amp;#8211; Catchable Fatal Error</title>
      <link>https://damien.co/blog/i-have-a-bug-catchable-fatal-error-2733/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2011 08:28:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien.co/blog/i-have-a-bug-catchable-fatal-error-2733/</guid>
      <description>If you are reading this on my website (as opposed to RSS feed) you might notice that I’m suffering from a Catchable Fatal Error
Hopefully Ill be well by the end of the day.
its still being worked on
and its being tested
22.50
and it maybe fixed
i dropped all records and reimported but to the wrong table 🙁 🙁
and it might be broken again
and its fixed i hope</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Review] The Smashing Book 2 Is Available &amp;#8211; Smashing Magazine</title>
      <link>https://damien.co/blog/review-the-smashing-book-2-is-available-smashing-magazine-2659/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Feb 2011 16:52:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien.co/blog/review-the-smashing-book-2-is-available-smashing-magazine-2659/</guid>
      <description>So I got my copy of the new ****The Smashing Book 2. Smashing Magazine is for anyone into design, web development and new media. It is one of many websites I follow on a weekly basis.
 The book came nicely (over) packaged and was immediately opened. It is a resource in itself and provides 10+ essays on topics from mobile app design to self-publishing – all new and not available on the website.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Productivity Tip &amp;#8211; Technical Writing &amp;#038; the Writer&amp;#8217;s Block</title>
      <link>https://damien.co/blog/productivity-tip-technical-writing-the-writers-block-2617/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jan 2011 09:45:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien.co/blog/productivity-tip-technical-writing-the-writers-block-2617/</guid>
      <description>Each week I set aside time to good writing, but its not the same when each day there are technical documents and scrum artefacts to be prepared. I can’t guarantee to get my writing done. It just doesn’t work like that. Good productive writingtakes time, space and zero distractions – even when its a business process or project brief.

Technical Writing &amp;amp; the Writers block You hear about those creative types in marketing, you may know a few entrepreneurs or inventors who have a spark of genius.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Productivity – Clear some time to get writing</title>
      <link>https://damien.co/blog/productivity-%e2%80%93-clear-some-time-to-get-writing-2611/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jan 2011 17:00:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien.co/blog/productivity-%e2%80%93-clear-some-time-to-get-writing-2611/</guid>
      <description>For over a year now, Sunday has been my day to work. On Sundays, I’ve blocked out a few hours for the productive writing process. I’ve been a trained technical writer for more than 10 years now. I know I can write beautiful prose, except it’s the kind of prose worthy of legal contracts and business processes. Nowadays I’m trying to be more faithful to this skill and be creative in my writing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Aperture 3 digital photo software improved integration with Flickr</title>
      <link>https://damien.co/blog/aperture-3-digital-photo-software-improved-integration-with-flickr-2584/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jan 2011 09:04:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien.co/blog/aperture-3-digital-photo-software-improved-integration-with-flickr-2584/</guid>
      <description>I’ve been using Apple Aperture 3 for my digital photography and image processing for a couple of years. It’s great for importing those images for clients and quickly doing all the editing, tagging, grouping and touch-ups.
What I didn’t like about it as a workflow tool – is that it lacks proper integration with Flickr. In the 3.0 version from last year you could publish as a Set of photos to Flickr, but couldn’t just add an image to your photostream.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcome 2011 time for a spring clean</title>
      <link>https://damien.co/blog/welcome-2011-time-for-a-spring-clean-2428/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2011 10:19:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien.co/blog/welcome-2011-time-for-a-spring-clean-2428/</guid>
      <description>Hello 2011 — long may you last! If you’re new to my site … then Hello to you too. It’s time for a spring clean and over the next few days, I’ll be tearing everything apart on the website.
In the first stage, I have taken down the old WordPress website and replaced it with a WordPress Network or Multisite – which means I can make a network of blogs or websites … or more likely microsites for social media marketing campaigns and promotions.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>