<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Development on Damien Saunders</title>
    <link>http://damien.co/categories/development/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Development on Damien Saunders</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2013 12:05:33 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://damien.co/categories/development/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Messing with your Head &amp;#8211; when to use WordPress template parts vs JavaScript</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/2013-09-26-messing-with-your-head-when-to-use-wordpress-template-parts-vs-javascript/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2013 12:05:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/2013-09-26-messing-with-your-head-when-to-use-wordpress-template-parts-vs-javascript/</guid>
      <description>Here I am … I&amp;rsquo;m messing with your head. I wanted to see how easy it is to get my Isotope Visual Layouts plugin for WordPress to change your your homepage. Actually it was too easy and the result is destruction and chaos.
No-No – I&amp;rsquo;m Never Going to Mess with your Head First thing to note – Never do anything with a plugin that &amp;lsquo;you&amp;rsquo; the User doesn&amp;rsquo;t expect. That&amp;rsquo;s bad bad karma.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Git: How to add a submodule in the root of your project - Try Git SubTree instead</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/development/git-how-to-add-a-submodule-in-the-root-of-your-project-try-git-subtree-instead-8665/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2013 13:42:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/development/git-how-to-add-a-submodule-in-the-root-of-your-project-try-git-subtree-instead-8665/</guid>
      <description>This is just a short post and the title says it all … I’ve wanted add submodules to a Git repository but you get an error if you try. So how do you add a submodule to your root folder in your Git project? Easy — Git Subtree Merge is what you need.
Add your 2nd Git Project as a Remote Actually, you start by adding a git remote with the source being the git project you want to pull in.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to integrate your own Isotope jQuery plugin with your WordPress</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/2013-04-28-how-to-integrate-your-own-isotope-jquery-plugin-with-your-wordpress/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2013 12:00:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/2013-04-28-how-to-integrate-your-own-isotope-jquery-plugin-with-your-wordpress/</guid>
      <description>I was recently asked if it was easy to integrate Isotope jQuery plugin into a WordPress website. It’s not uncomplicated to add isotope.js to your website – it’s just not as easy as linking a script to your header.
2 Ways to add Isotope jQuery Plugin to WordPress As always, there are (at least) 2 ways to achieve this
 Create a page template for the purpose – with all the code you want Add the code to your themes function.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Continuous Integration for WordPress Jenkins Selenium Apache Ant</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/2013-04-07-continuous-integration-for-wordpress-plugins-jenkins-selenium-apache-ant/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2013 21:08:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/2013-04-07-continuous-integration-for-wordpress-plugins-jenkins-selenium-apache-ant/</guid>
      <description>I’m no regular WordPress Plugin Developer – I spend most of my day managing projects or other stuff. So when I do develop, I want a trusted, reliable, repeatable workflow setup that is always testing, always building and always telling me whats going on. That’s why I believe in Continuous Integration … and why I’ve turned to Jenkins as my CI Tool and use Apache Ant and Selenium for testing. A bit of background on Continuous Integration and Tools Continuous Integration Continuous Integration is a fundamentally different approach to software development where the project team work to continuously test as you build software.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HOW TO: Install Jenkins-CI on a Mac OS X with Git &amp;#038; Bitbucket</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/development/how-to-install-jenkins-ci-on-a-mac-os-x-with-git-bitbucket-8072/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Dec 2012 13:56:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/development/how-to-install-jenkins-ci-on-a-mac-os-x-with-git-bitbucket-8072/</guid>
      <description>A few notes on getting Jenkins-CI installed on your Mac and setup with Git and Bitbucket for source code management. I’ve been using Git for some time but I had problems / major issues with Jenkins and could never seem to get this working.
Issues with setting up Jenkins and Git on a Mac Here are the issues I was having … the biggest issue was the Error (unable to clone) which showed up when I created a job and added the path to the Bitbucket repo — even after I had added the SSH Key to Bitbucket.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Top Development Tools on my MacBook Pro</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/development/top-development-tools-on-my-macbook-pro-7234/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jun 2012 09:10:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/development/top-development-tools-on-my-macbook-pro-7234/</guid>
      <description>If you wanted to know what I apps and software I use every day then here you go … For starters this is all Mac OSx stuff.
 AxureRP 6.5 – wireframes and interactive prototypes. UX/UI Heaven Terminal – go command line (for SSH and most server stuff like testing with siege) Coda 2 – An all in one IDE – FTP, MySQL database, CSS, Editor and more … Transmit – only if I can’t be bothered to use Coda Firefox (and then only for these 2 extensions) SQLite Manager – SQLite may be the new mySQL … we’ll see Selenium IDE – for browser based testing (but only in Firefox) Sequel Pro – mySQL database manager SourceTree (as it works with Bitbucket)  Other apps to know about  MarsEdit – Best blog tool around for WordPress – but definitely room to improve Scrivener – for writing all that blog stuff Omnigraffle – when you can’t use Axure (and don’t have Visio) Pixelmator – who needs Photoshop Aperture – who needs Lightroom Netnewswire – I do all my RSS reading on the mobile now  Cloud based stuff I use every day  Google.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sequel Pro &amp;#8211; Fastest &amp;#038; best MySQL client for Mac</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/2012-06-07-sequel-pro-fastest-best-mysql-client-for-mac/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jun 2012 12:35:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/2012-06-07-sequel-pro-fastest-best-mysql-client-for-mac/</guid>
      <description>Sequel Prois the fastest and best MySQL client for Mac right now. After a mini disaster yesterday involving Sequel Pro and filename extensions, I thought I’d checkout the competition.
So I did a quick check and downloaded a few other apps that would manage MySQL on a Mac with OS x –
 MySQL Workbench RazorSQL (not free so didn’t try) Navicat  Both MySQL Workbench and Navicat are java based apps.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rackspace - List of CIDR&#39;s for Testing with Blazemeter</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/2012-03-10-rackspace-list-of-cidrs-for-testing-with-blazemeter/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Mar 2012 18:32:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/2012-03-10-rackspace-list-of-cidrs-for-testing-with-blazemeter/</guid>
      <description>I’ve just finished a WordPress multi-server development project which required a scalable deployment setup. We also needed to test the setup under load and ended up using Blazemeter (basically jmeter in the cloud).
If you’re setup in Rackspace has a load balancer, you know you need to allow a number of IP’s by modifying the Access Control. Annoyingly there was no 1 list of the CIDR’s to allow. Blazemeter keeps a list of CIDR’sbut this couldn’t be cut n paste into Rackspace.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>