<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Mobile Marketing on Damien Saunders</title>
    <link>http://damien.co/tags/mobile-marketing/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Mobile Marketing on Damien Saunders</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 18 Jul 2012 15:23:16 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://damien.co/tags/mobile-marketing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Key trends in mobile usage from the UK</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/2012-07-18-key-trends-in-mobile-usage-from-the-uk/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jul 2012 15:23:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/2012-07-18-key-trends-in-mobile-usage-from-the-uk/</guid>
      <description>Mobile usage in the UK is on the increase. That&amp;rsquo;s all sounding good so far.
The latest communications report from Ofcom has shown a year on year growth of 1.6 million mobiles and the biggest growth in postpaid subscribers due to more customers taking out contracts for smartphones.
Want to download this for free? Read to the end of the presentation and copy the discount coupon code.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to start mobile marketing with Foursquare [presentation]</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/social-media/foursquare/how-to-start-mobile-marketing-with-foursquare-presentation-4942/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Nov 2011 09:45:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/social-media/foursquare/how-to-start-mobile-marketing-with-foursquare-presentation-4942/</guid>
      <description>Mobile marketing and Foursquare are two words that are just right for each other. Foursquare has an impressive base of users and is extremely popular in big cities like London - which means it&amp;rsquo;s ideal for any business or brand to get started with mobile marketing and hyper-local search.
Focus your marketing on mobile - integrate offline with online Now that mobile marketing is becoming the focus of all your online marketing activities (if not, why not?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Going Mobile - I&#39;m in your face - I&#39;m in your phone.</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/mobile-marketing/going-mobile-im-in-your-face-im-in-your-phone-2953/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 May 2011 13:24:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/mobile-marketing/going-mobile-im-in-your-face-im-in-your-phone-2953/</guid>
      <description>Mobilising your web content and cross channel integrated marketing may sound like just a bunch of buzzwords to boost my SEO. But it&amp;rsquo;s not. So I&amp;rsquo;m helping you to understand the latest in mobile marketing, tools &amp;amp; techniques.
You can now visit http://damien.mobi from your smartphone and have the best experience a mobile can get. If you&amp;rsquo;re a fan of the iPad then you can also save this as a web app on your phone.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>50 Completely Useful stats for social media &amp;amp; mobile marketing</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/2010-05-31-50-completely-useful-stats-for-social-media-mobile-marketing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 May 2010 16:27:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/2010-05-31-50-completely-useful-stats-for-social-media-mobile-marketing/</guid>
      <description>To understand more about Social Media and Mobile Marketing its important to get a few facts together on current trends and insights. 50 completely useful stats for social media does just that.
Why do this? well it helps to create some drive … and helps to understand why anyone or any business needs to do more in social media and mobile marketing.
50 completely useful stats for social media &amp;amp; mobile marketing</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gowalla? Foursquare open for Business? Who will setup a business team in Europe First</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/2010-05-11-gowalla-foursquare-open-for-business/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 May 2010 08:00:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/2010-05-11-gowalla-foursquare-open-for-business/</guid>
      <description>Foursquare is now open to business and is moving beyond geo-tagging and location based social networking. But is Foursquare really open to business? After trying to claim my business location and setup an offer for visitors its now been 3 weeks without a reply.
In the UK right now, I believe there is an opportunity for Gowalla, Foursquare, etc to setup a small but viable business team to work with digital agencies or mobile marketing specialists here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Mobile? Why Now? – short guide to mobile marketing</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/2010-04-18-why-mobile-why-now-short-guide-to-mobile-marketing/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Apr 2010 16:16:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/2010-04-18-why-mobile-why-now-short-guide-to-mobile-marketing/</guid>
      <description>A short guide to mobile marketing is as short as it can get - and provides just enough insights, trends and key facts to help make the most of mobile marketing. What&amp;rsquo;s included in this is 8 quick suggestions how to include mobile marketing in your marketing strategy.
Why mobile why now</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>b2b Marketing - how to increase your content sales and improve your content</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/mobile-marketing/b2b-marketing-how-to-increase-your-content-sales-and-improve-your-content-812/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Mar 2010 23:29:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/mobile-marketing/b2b-marketing-how-to-increase-your-content-sales-and-improve-your-content-812/</guid>
      <description>A short guide with b2b marketing tips for improving your content sales and improve your content using mmCHANNEL&amp;rsquo;s new API.1. Got an upcoming marketing campaign? Need Content? Now any marketing campaign can include digital content like tones, songs, games from a selection of mmCHANNEL manages.
2. Drive traffic to your website or fanpage You can setup a content shop in your existing website using the mmCHANNEL b2bAPI with no need to build any other platforms</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>5 Essential tips for promoting your charity or cause using mobile marketing</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/2010-02-22-essential-tips-promotions-charities-mobile/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Feb 2010 07:44:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/2010-02-22-essential-tips-promotions-charities-mobile/</guid>
      <description>For non-profit organisations, charities and cause related marketing the mobile can provide the best integrated marketing solution for campaigns. There are a number of tools and techniques which can be used to promote your cause or help to raise donations.
1. SMS Premium Text Donations Making donations using your mobile is as simple as sending a text to a special number. For the not so concerned and the lazy its a quick way to send a few dollars, euros or pounds to a worthy cause.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mobile Marketing Strategies - Mobile CRM</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/2010-02-08-mobile-marketing-strategies-mobile-crm/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Feb 2010 09:47:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/2010-02-08-mobile-marketing-strategies-mobile-crm/</guid>
      <description>**Until recently mobile devices were often overlooked by marketing managers in favour of online campaigns or traditional paper-based direct marketing. However, brands, ad agencies and telecoms operators are increasingly using mobile as part of their customer relationship management (CRM) strategy. ** The rapid growth in smartphones spurred by the iPhone, Windows Mobile and Android has given mobile marketing a major boost. The latest devices offer fast and easy web access, often with flat-rate charges.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Looking for insights on Mobile and Retail Sector?</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/2010-02-06-looking-for-insights-on-mobile-and-retail-sector/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Feb 2010 17:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/2010-02-06-looking-for-insights-on-mobile-and-retail-sector/</guid>
      <description>&amp;lt;div&amp;gt; The Whitepaper, ‘Mobile in Retail’, seeks to identify the potential for mobile to brands and retailers. It highlights 10 areas, including coupons and loyalty, where mobile is deemed to have a particular impact. The executive summary points to a number of areas of potential gain for businesses adopting mobile as a consumer engagement channel. These are increased sales; increased customer satisfaction and loyalty; and additional value to physical products and experiences through digital services.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to include mobile marketing into your advertising</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/mobile-marketing/how-to-include-mobile-marketing-into-your-advertising-409/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jan 2010 18:02:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/mobile-marketing/how-to-include-mobile-marketing-into-your-advertising-409/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s easy to create effective mobile marketing campaigns using apps and games … this short video aims to demonstrate whats possible
Mobile Advertising and Mobile Games</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to use Competitions &amp;amp; Social Media to grow your mobile marketing</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/2010-01-13-how-to-use-competitions-social-media-to-grow-your-business/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jan 2010 23:18:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/2010-01-13-how-to-use-competitions-social-media-to-grow-your-business/</guid>
      <description>Running competitions using social media is a good way for brands and businesses to create welcome visitors and friends to their sites. You can now take that competition mobile using mobile apps, games or mobile websites and you don&amp;rsquo;t have to use SMS.
Using Social Media to get your customers discovering you on their mobile Your marketing messages on social media sites like Twitter and Facebook can direct existing customers to discover your mobile website or to download a mobile app.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vote in my Mobile Marketing and Mobile Apps Poll</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/mobile-marketing/vote-in-my-mobile-marketing-and-mobile-apps-poll-379/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Dec 2009 13:59:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/mobile-marketing/vote-in-my-mobile-marketing-and-mobile-apps-poll-379/</guid>
      <description>Take a vote … what do you do for mobile marketing and have you tried any mobile apps?
http://polls.linkedin.com/p/69091/tbhgt</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Social Media &amp;amp; Marketing Round-up of some good reading</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/mobile-marketing/social-media-marketing-round-up-of-some-good-reading-375/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Dec 2009 16:36:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/mobile-marketing/social-media-marketing-round-up-of-some-good-reading-375/</guid>
      <description>**The problem with doing research on social media and mobile marketing is the overwhelming amount of noise you get from doing searches on Google, Delicious and Twitter.
**
Here are a few links of really useful and easy to consume &amp;lsquo;research&amp;rsquo;
best &amp;lsquo;inspirational&amp;rsquo; video on social media
http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=sIFYPQjYhv8map of social media world
http://www.flickr.com/photos/wasabibratwurst/3128711125/sizes/l/top 100 companies by media spend</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>