<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Android on Damien Saunders</title>
    <link>http://damien.co/categories/android/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Android on Damien Saunders</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 30 Mar 2012 15:00:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://damien.co/categories/android/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Android 4.0 Galaxy Nexus impressive boot animation</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/2012-03-30-galaxy-nexus-impressive-boot-animation/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Mar 2012 15:00:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/2012-03-30-galaxy-nexus-impressive-boot-animation/</guid>
      <description>Have you been impressed by the startup boot animation for Android ICS – I wonder if other Android 4.0 devices have the same startup animation?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Popular Posts in Android</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/android/popular-posts-in-android-5529/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Dec 2011 15:17:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/android/popular-posts-in-android-5529/</guid>
      <description>It’s time to catchup on some missed out reading and get away from the cold. So here is a collection of 10 of the best Android resources that you love to read.
So I’m not going to second guess these related posts – I’m sure there will be stuff about Cyanogenmod, Wifi Settings and some best apps.
[related_posts limit=”10″]
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I just got my Google Galaxy Nexus</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/2011-12-03-i-just-got-my-google-galaxy-nexus/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Dec 2011 00:03:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/2011-12-03-i-just-got-my-google-galaxy-nexus/</guid>
      <description>Looking forward to some Android 4.0 Ice Cream Sandwich now I got me a new phone. The Google Galaxy Nexusarrived today and all I can say is BIG SCREEN.
I think the next year will see me managing projects involving NFC, mobile payments, banking and hoping for some great Internet of Things apps.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Revolutionary &amp;#8211; I just rooted my HTC Sensation</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/android/revolutionary-i-just-rooted-my-htc-sensation-4643/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2011 16:32:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/android/revolutionary-i-just-rooted-my-htc-sensation-4643/</guid>
      <description>Is Revolutionary the easiest tool? (answer – no) If you’ve been keeping up with the world of custom rom’s to root your Android you may have heard about this. Revolutionary doesn’t get much of a mention as it’s still an Alpha release, but it does bring together to great development teams.
Revolutionary is only for Linux or Windows users and really supports the newer range of Android devices like the HTC Sensation</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>4 of the best Android apps for Wifi</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/android/4-of-best-android-apps-for-wifi-1715/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2011 09:00:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/android/4-of-best-android-apps-for-wifi-1715/</guid>
      <description>I’ve been writing about Android for some time now. Here are 4 of the best Android apps for Wifi. These apps allow you to find public wi-fi networks, turn your phone into a wifi hotspot and a bit more.
HTC Wifi Hotspot This app can’t be downloaded from the market – its part of HTC build for Android 2.2 Froyo
I’ve used this loads of times – its great for getting my laptop or iPad on the Internet when needed, but the main point to remember is it kills your battery very fast.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cyanogenmod 7.1 RC1</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/android/cyanogenmod-7-1-rc1-4070/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jun 2011 19:08:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/android/cyanogenmod-7-1-rc1-4070/</guid>
      <description>Have you updated? – the first release candidate for Cyanogenmod v7.1 has been pushed out today. This update adds (more) support for Android 2.3.4 a number of Android devices from Samsung, LG, Motorola and the HTC Incredible.
Here’s a summary of nice features from the changelog:
Common: Support for revoking application permissions
Common: Latest Superuser app
Common: Control brightness by sliding on statusbar
Common: ADWLauncher- Transitions, catalog improvements, bugfixes
Common: Optional GMT correction for SMS/MMS timestamps</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Android 10 best articles you love to read</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/android/android-10-best-articles-you-love-to-read-3986/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2011 10:40:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/android/android-10-best-articles-you-love-to-read-3986/</guid>
      <description>It’s time to catchup on some missed out reading and get out in the sun. So here is a collection of 10 of the best Android resources that you love to read.
So I’m not going to second guess these related posts – I’m sure there will be stuff about Cyanogenmod, Wifi Settings and some best apps.
[related_posts limit=”10″]
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HTC Sensation preorder with Carphone Warehouse</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/2011-06-08-htc-sensation-preorder-with-carphone-warehouse/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jun 2011 14:19:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/2011-06-08-htc-sensation-preorder-with-carphone-warehouse/</guid>
      <description>Have you seen this in your email? The new HTC Sensation is ready for pre-sales orders via Carphone Warehouse starting from £35 per month</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Android apps run full screen on Honeycomb Tablets</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/android/android-apps-run-full-screen-on-honeycomb-tablets-3482/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 May 2011 15:42:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/android/android-apps-run-full-screen-on-honeycomb-tablets-3482/</guid>
      <description>Google recently announced some exciting new features for Android 3.0 Honeycomb. Most notably, Android 3.0 sees tablets and mobile devices merge to the same code base. This is kind of like having one OS for all devices. There are interface design considerations that need to be understood before launching your app on the big screen.
Android Apps run full screen – Interface Design The key point to note is that Android apps run in full screen on tablets.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Android Apps &amp;#8211; 400% growth rate YOY</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/2011-05-17-android-apps-400-growth/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2011 11:57:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/2011-05-17-android-apps-400-growth/</guid>
      <description>Android in numbers – thankfully the Google I/O conference helped out by publishing statistics which give some insight to the growth in adoption of smartphones and also help to provide a hint of reality. But these are BIG BIG BIG numbers.
Android Smartphones, Tablets &amp;amp; Devices  Over 100M Android devices activated worldwide with 400K activations added every day More than 310 Android devices from 36 different manufactures Android cellphones are on more than 216 mobile carriers in 112 countries  Android Market  200,000 free and paid applications available in Android Market 4.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Android &amp;#8211; Best Apps for WiFi &amp;#8211; refreshed for 2011</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/2011-05-09-android-best-apps-for-wifi-refreshed-for-2011/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 May 2011 12:00:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/2011-05-09-android-best-apps-for-wifi-refreshed-for-2011/</guid>
      <description>I’ve been writing about Android for some time now and Best Android Apps for Wifi is a very popular post. So here is a refreshingly new look for 2011 at some of the best wi-fi apps for your smartphone.
Auto Wifi Enabler This was a fav app for a month – til I realised I only ever needed 2 wifi hotspots – the one at work and the one at home.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cyanogenmod &amp;#8211; How to download big apps on your SD Card</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/2011-05-08-cyanogenmod-how-to-download-big-apps-on-your-sd-card/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 May 2011 12:31:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/2011-05-08-cyanogenmod-how-to-download-big-apps-on-your-sd-card/</guid>
      <description>Are you suffering from Android Market download issues? Have you just rooted your Android with Cyanogenmod and found you can’t download Google Maps?
If you can’t download Google Maps it’s because most Android phones have a download cache limited to 3MB and Google Maps is a whooping 5.4MB.
How to Download large files after rooting your Android The answer to your problems is S2E simple2ext – which moves your download cache off the phone to your SD Card.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cyanogenmod 7.0.3 &amp;#8211; have you updated?</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/2011-05-07-cyanogenmod-7-0-3-have-you-updated/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2011 16:38:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/2011-05-07-cyanogenmod-7-0-3-have-you-updated/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Linkage] Today&amp;#8217;s Social Media News Updates for 2011-04-29</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/android/linkage-todays-social-media-news-updates-for-2011-04-29-2922/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Apr 2011 21:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/android/linkage-todays-social-media-news-updates-for-2011-04-29-2922/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cyanogenmod 7.02 have you updated</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/2011-04-28-cyanogenmod-7-02-have-you-updated/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Apr 2011 21:11:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/2011-04-28-cyanogenmod-7-02-have-you-updated/</guid>
      <description>Have you updated? – the latest Cyanogenmod v7.02 has been released. Mostly it fixes bugs and ‘actually’ fixes GPS.
Being a point release its not focused on new features – but if you haven’t updated then you should. As always backup your current Rom before installing this update.
Summary from the changelog:
 Common: Fix issue with missing built-in themes Common: Update bundled ROM Manager to latest version Supersonic: Actually fix GPS Supersonic: Fix proximity and light sensor  You can download it via the Clockwork Rom Manager or manually.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best Android App for technical info Network Info II</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/2011-04-18-best-android-app-for-technical-info-network-info-ii/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Apr 2011 09:40:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/2011-04-18-best-android-app-for-technical-info-network-info-ii/</guid>
      <description>Mobile apps can be fun to use – but during mobile app testing you might need to diagnosing problems and finding bugs can be complicated. At least with Network Info II on your Android you have a pocket-encyclopedia with all the important information you need.
At the basic level – Network Info II reports details on your mobile network connection, IP address, Wi-Fi connection, Bluetooth and details about your device and your sim card.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>z4Root [I just rooted] Samsung Europa Android 2.2.1 (VFUK)</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/android/z4root-i-just-rooted-samsung-europa-android-2-2-1-vfuk-2874/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Apr 2011 12:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/android/z4root-i-just-rooted-samsung-europa-android-2-2-1-vfuk-2874/</guid>
      <description>Is z4root the easiest tool? If you’ve been keeping up with the world of custom rom’s to root your Android you may have heard about this.
z4root doesn’t get much of a mention – its key differentiator is that it is an untethered root tool – eg you run it from your mobile and not from your PC or Mac.
I’ve got a Samsung Galaxy Europa prepay on Vodafone UK – I needed to do screenshots and the only good way to do this involves running root first.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Last.fm Android Live Wallpaper</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/android/last-fm-android-live-wallpaper-2832/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Apr 2011 20:39:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/android/last-fm-android-live-wallpaper-2832/</guid>
      <description>I’ve just discovered the (not official) Last.fm live wallpaper for Android. It’s a brilliant change to my boring background on my HTC Desire.
Last.fm is still there tracking my music listening habits – and doing a good job of that. This live wallpaper has a number of options and the free version allows you to create a wallpaper of your favourite artists for example.
The idea for this (app) is also brilliant – it needs no real user interface – and for a small price you get a premium wallpaper with options for weekly charts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HOWTO: Fix no mobile internet after Cyanogenmod install</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/android/howto-fix-no-mobile-internet-after-cyanogenmod-install-2822/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Apr 2011 21:04:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/android/howto-fix-no-mobile-internet-after-cyanogenmod-install-2822/</guid>
      <description>Here’s a simple fix to problems of no Mobile Internet after installing Cyanogenmod rom on your Android. If you’re new to rooting your Android or just forgotten how complicated it can be to get online with your mobile phone – you might think this is a really useful tip.
 Check your APN Settings After you root your phone and install CyanogenMod you can find your have no wifi and no wireless internet connection.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cyanogenmod 7RC3</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/android/cyanogenmod-7rc3-2808/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Mar 2011 09:20:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/android/cyanogenmod-7rc3-2808/</guid>
      <description>I’ve just updated to the latest Cyanogenmod 7 release candidate 3 … it’s now looking very polished.
Noticeable extras – application shortcut menus have a link to the Android Market.
 What have you noticed?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Android Market has a browser</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/android/android-market-has-a-browser-2709/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Feb 2011 09:16:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/android/android-market-has-a-browser-2709/</guid>
      <description>Android users tend to download fewer apps – and this is because there is no computer application to easily browse and download apps in the same way that iTunes works for iOS devices. A few weeks back the revamped Android Market website was launched. But it still struggles to tie the phone to the computer.
Android Market revamped The Android Market website has been around for a couple of years and generally featured static content.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Autodesk SketchBook Mobile comes to Android</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/2010-12-02-autodesk-sketchbook-mobile-comes-to-android/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Dec 2010 14:00:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/2010-12-02-autodesk-sketchbook-mobile-comes-to-android/</guid>
      <description>SketchBook Mobile recently got a mention here as the best iPad app fro sketches, notes, photos and more … and now its available on Android. I bet if you have a Samsung Galaxy Tab – this should be the first app that really is worth paying for.With so many features – it can be hard to know where to start – so my suggestion is use it to play around with some of your photos.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How smartphone users see each other</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/2010-11-05-how-smartphone-users-see-each-other/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Nov 2010 09:27:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/2010-11-05-how-smartphone-users-see-each-other/</guid>
      <description>Happy Friday everyone … Now go look at yourself in the mirror?
Source: http://androidandme.com/2010/11/news/how-smartphone-users-see-each-other-android-vs-blackberry-vs-iphone-comic/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HOW TO: View your WordPress Website on iPhone or Android</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/2010-07-26-how-to-view-your-wordpress-website-on-iphone-or-android/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jul 2010 16:00:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/2010-07-26-how-to-view-your-wordpress-website-on-iphone-or-android/</guid>
      <description>WordPressis a very comprehensive all-round tool for websites – and its not just for blogs. If you’re starting out with WordPress and need your site to look smooth on a mobile phone like the iPhone or any big screen Androidmobile then you’ll need a plugin for this.The best plugin for WordPress that handles any mobile device is easily WPtouch iPhone Theme. Once the plugin is installed and activated its working for you straight away.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Essential Location Based Apps for Android Mobiles</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/2010-07-12-essential-location-based-apps-for-android-mobiles/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2010 09:00:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/2010-07-12-essential-location-based-apps-for-android-mobiles/</guid>
      <description>Everyone is used to taking their mobile with them, so that means location basedapps for mobiles will start to become more popular. A recent issue of Wired noted that it was thanks to Foursquare&amp;amp; Gowalla, that people are now getting more used to sharing their location. On a fun side, many of the new location based mobile apps have games or allow you to collect rewards for visiting new places. Here’s an essential list of location based apps for Androidmobile.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3 must try Android Apps to manage wifi</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/2010-05-11-3-must-try-android-apps-to-manage-wifi/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 May 2010 13:00:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/2010-05-11-3-must-try-android-apps-to-manage-wifi/</guid>
      <description>Managing wifi on your Android mobile phone can be a hassle, so at least there are now 3 good apps for you to use to make your wifi experience better.
Is the most technical looking of the 3 apps – turning it on was a bit of shock when compared to the user experience of the other 2 apps. WiFinder only has 1 button aptly labelled New Scan. You then press and hold on the WiFi SSID to see the more familar Android Wifi Connect.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HOW TO: Keep your Wifi connection awake on Android</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/android/how-to-keep-your-wifi-connection-awake-on-android-957/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 May 2010 14:00:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/android/how-to-keep-your-wifi-connection-awake-on-android-957/</guid>
      <description>Most people read this post because to find out how to change the Wifi settings on their Android phone. You might be wanting to save battery or figure out how to keep wifi on when your phone screen is off / idle.
It’s very easy to change this setting and I prefer to keep wifi on when the phone is plugged into the mains power, this means your news and rss clients will synced overnight when you’re sleeping.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Android Phones &amp;#8211; product life cycle &amp;amp; how to choose</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/2010-04-19-android-phones-product-life-cycle-how-to-choose/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Apr 2010 16:00:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/2010-04-19-android-phones-product-life-cycle-how-to-choose/</guid>
      <description>What with all the new Android phones, its time to look at the phones to not buy, unless you’re stuck for cash or just want your first touch phone. There are many terminal vendors and operators with Android phones to choose from HTC, Sony Ericsson, Motorolla, T-mobile, Vodafone and Google (HTC).
General Points on Buying a Phone  Why buy a phone on a contract  the total cost of ownership over a 18 month or 2 year contract will be expensive.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Android Market would benefit Developer instead of Apple App Certification?</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/2010-03-04-android-market-benefits-developer-apples-app-certification/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Mar 2010 22:29:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/2010-03-04-android-market-benefits-developer-apples-app-certification/</guid>
      <description>Develop apps for Android or develop mobile apps for Apple, some days its hard to figure out just what to do. On this website I’ve written a lot on Android phones and apps.Around 6000 apps have been removed from the Apple store recently due to their erotic nature. It’s not that Android Market has no quality control – Adult or Erotic does not exist as a content category in Android Market but dating apps or other soft-porn apps so far have not shown huge growth (ahem) on Android.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NewsRob best Android application for Google Reader</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/2010-02-28-newsrob-best-android-application-for-google-reader/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Feb 2010 15:11:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/2010-02-28-newsrob-best-android-application-for-google-reader/</guid>
      <description>Newsrob is my favourite application for Android mobiles, it’s been covered in my 10Best Android Apps** list a few times. **Newsrob** integratess with your account for Google Reader (which allows you to manage and read all your RSS feeds). Newsrob recently turned 1 and celebrated by introducing a Pro version and an Adfunded Free Version.**
What’s fantastic about Newsrob Pro Newsrob Prohas a new feature that is great for any social media or mobile specialist.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Foursquare Best Location Based Social Networking for Android UK Users</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/social-media/foursquare-best-location-based-social-networking-455/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Feb 2010 18:56:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/social-media/foursquare-best-location-based-social-networking-455/</guid>
      <description>Android mobile owners in the UK will be pleased to know that location based social networkingapps have begun to improve and increase in the number of users. In the past few weeks, top location based social networks such as Brightkiteand Foursquarehave really improved the quality and details of UK locations.**
**
It is a problem of user experience that meant many of these services had few UK users and no UK points of interest.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Android Market 3 of the Best Games</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/2010-01-23-android-market-best-games/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Jan 2010 00:43:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/2010-01-23-android-market-best-games/</guid>
      <description>Mobile Games for Android phones are now improving. The Android Market has a number of very good games that will help waste hours of your time. The 3 best and most popular Android mobile games are:
Robo Defense (free and premium) best tower defense game on the Android. Why? because your enemies don’t have a set route to follow. Its kinda like a long rugby or gridiron playing field and you have to stop them from getting to the other end.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>10 things to do with your Android and a Barcode Scanner</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/android/10-things-to-do-with-your-android-and-a-barcode-scanner-304/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Nov 2009 10:30:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/android/10-things-to-do-with-your-android-and-a-barcode-scanner-304/</guid>
      <description>There’s no better sound than the reassuring ‘Beep at the Checkout Register’. So now you have your own Android mobile phone …here’s a few barcode scanning things you can do at home or in the shops.
First you need the best Android Barcode Scanner – which now has integration with Google search on the mobile.
 Add a book to your Amazon Wishlist – just snap the barcode and save to list Catalogue your books at home using Anobiit from Anobii Catalogue your CD’s with Kooaba Look up reviews of that Wine you’ve just been drinking – Wine by the Bar is the perfect app for you Compare prices for that Electrical Gadget – Scan the Barcode and search online for it Create your own Barcode – After installing Barcode Scanner, open your Android Contacts .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DROID takes the Android to a new level</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/android/droid-takes-the-android-to-a-new-level-360/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Nov 2009 08:55:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/android/droid-takes-the-android-to-a-new-level-360/</guid>
      <description>DROID sales in the USA and the robo-promotional ads from Verizon has boosted Android sales, so much so that hits on my blog have started to double since the new phone went on sale.
Stats are good – Top searchs on Best Apps are going to my posts for Top Android Apps and 2 top Android apps from Google.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is Android Lagging Behind in Sales? Not Likely</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/android/is-android-lagging-behind-in-sales-not-likely-338/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Oct 2009 15:10:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/android/is-android-lagging-behind-in-sales-not-likely-338/</guid>
      <description>Recently the blogosphere has gone a bit crazy, excuse my lack of hyperbole about the Android platform. Was this ‘Android’ supposed to do battle with the iPhone?
Just because no operators or manufacturers have openly commented about their smart phone sales figures doesn’t mean its bad news. Looking at the number of Android powered phones out now or due in the next 2 months shows a lot of promise
 HTC Hero – some bloggers say it’s the best Android yet G1 – the funny one with the flip out keyboard, still only with T-Mobile Magic – Vodafone took this and the Android platform global Tattoo – coming out again to Vodafone before xmas Motorola DEXT – a lifesaver for Motorola – probably the phone that saves them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>10 Best Android Apps for your phone</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/2009-08-11-10-best-android-apps-for-your-phone/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Aug 2009 15:14:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/2009-08-11-10-best-android-apps-for-your-phone/</guid>
      <description>Here’s a more up to date list featuring some of the best apps you must get on your Android phone. All of them are free in the Android Market. Some of them also have a freemium paid version. What’s good is that many of these you will use daily, but some of them will just sit on your phone and do what its supposed to do.(update: Nov 21 – Cyrket.com has been offline for some time … but is now around again – but try www.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>