<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Internet on Damien Saunders</title>
    <link>https://damien1.github.io/tags/internet/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Internet on Damien Saunders</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 18 Jan 2014 23:36:48 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://damien1.github.io/tags/internet/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Using a Netgear N600 DGND3700v1 to extend a home network</title>
      <link>https://damien1.github.io/general/using-netgear-n600-dgnd3700v1-extend-home-network-8747/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jan 2014 23:36:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien1.github.io/general/using-netgear-n600-dgnd3700v1-extend-home-network-8747/</guid>
      <description>I’ve brought a brand new Asus RT-AC66U modem/router and decided that to use my old Netgear N600 ADSL modem/router DGND3700v1 to extend my home network and expand my wireless network.
I’ve put the Netgear in a room where there was poor wifi signal strength and used a powerline (ethernet over power) adapter to connect back to the new main connection.
To get the Netgear to behave like a wireless Access Point and extend my existing network should have been easy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Saturday Humour &amp;#8211; Size of blogging [infographic]</title>
      <link>https://damien1.github.io/social-media/saturday-humour-size-of-blogging-infographic-2284/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Dec 2010 21:17:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien1.github.io/social-media/saturday-humour-size-of-blogging-infographic-2284/</guid>
      <description>Saturday’s usual weekly comic has been moved aside this week for something more important.

So its a week to Xmas … and all through the house not a creature was stirring – except for creatives and marketing types publishing their great present gifts for the world to enjoy.
What’s your opinion? do you think this Tree of Blogs sums things up quite nicely? and looking ahead – will the roots generate enough food and support for the future?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Saturday Funny &amp;#8211; a guide to the internet</title>
      <link>https://damien1.github.io/general/saturday-funny-a-guide-to-the-internet-1875/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Nov 2010 10:37:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien1.github.io/general/saturday-funny-a-guide-to-the-internet-1875/</guid>
      <description>So how would you explain the internet to a 19th century Dickensian street urchin. Can you make it through the flowchart without being killed?

Source: FastCompany</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>South Africa &amp;#8230; 5 million online and growing</title>
      <link>https://damien1.github.io/general/south-africa-5-million-online-and-growing-403/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Jan 2010 18:22:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien1.github.io/general/south-africa-5-million-online-and-growing-403/</guid>
      <description>South Africa is one of the fastest growing markets for mobile and internet usage is also growing rapidly. A history of poor international bandwidth / connectivity has meant speeds have remained slow.
South Africa’s internet users grew from 4.6 million to 5.3 million last year, a rise of 15%, according to research by World Wide Worx, a technology and research and strategy organisation, sponsored by Cisco.
The climb follows years of stagnation between 2002 to 2007, when internet penetration in South Africa never rose above 7%.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We are watching you and reading your texts and emails</title>
      <link>https://damien1.github.io/general/we-are-watching-you-and-reading-your-texts-and-emails-95/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Apr 2009 20:13:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien1.github.io/general/we-are-watching-you-and-reading-your-texts-and-emails-95/</guid>
      <description>The UK for along time has been a country full of honours and award systems — the most CCTV cameras comes to mind and from today it seems that the UK Government believes that for your safety, they will need to record details and the contents of every SMS, email, voicemails and phone calls.
How afraid are we all becoming?
source: http://www.guardian.co.uk/commentisfree/libertycentral/2009/apr/27/surveillance-data-protection</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BBC iPlayer steams ahead with internet usage</title>
      <link>https://damien1.github.io/general/bbc-iplayer-steams-ahead-with-internet-usage-70/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jan 2008 10:51:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien1.github.io/general/bbc-iplayer-steams-ahead-with-internet-usage-70/</guid>
      <description>Comment: Internet traffic to the iPlayer site is growing rapidly supported by outside advertising posterboards as well as reminders during TV advertising. However a lot of internet traffic seems to be sucked up by their kservices P2P network which aims to share the downloaded files with other iPlayer users.
 UK Internet traffic to the BBC’s iPlayer website increased 14-fold between the week ending 8 December 2007 and the week ending 5 January.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>