<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>digital sales on Damien Saunders</title>
    <link>http://damien.co/tags/digital-sales/</link>
    <description>Recent content in digital sales on Damien Saunders</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 23 May 2009 15:26:46 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://damien.co/tags/digital-sales/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Aging music lovers what happens when we are 80?</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/aging-music-lovers-what-happens-when-we-are-80-191/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 May 2009 15:26:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/aging-music-lovers-what-happens-when-we-are-80-191/</guid>
      <description>In a few years time, many of us will want to retire … what&amp;rsquo;s going to happen to us and our communities we live in if suddenly todays 20 and 30 somethings are 80? What music or digital entertainment will there be? Remembering also that as we start &amp;lsquo;age&amp;rsquo; we will have to work later in life beyond today&amp;rsquo;s retirement age.If, the aging population is bigger than the younger generation - does that mean nightclubs, discos and places like Ibiza will become the place for the 70+ age group?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apple to standardise iTunes prices in Europe</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/apple-to-standardise-itunes-prices-in-europe-69/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jan 2008 15:08:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/apple-to-standardise-itunes-prices-in-europe-69/</guid>
      <description> comment: The reason that Apple charges different retail prices in each market is due to the differences in wholesale prices charged in each market by the major labels. Apple could use this as leverage against the labels to lower their prices in all major EU markets
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UK Digital sales grow by 50% in 2007</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/uk-digital-sales-grow-by-50-in-2007-66/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Jan 2008 11:12:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/uk-digital-sales-grow-by-50-in-2007-66/</guid>
      <description>The British Phonographic Industry, which represents the British recorded-music business, said total music download sales for the year topped 77 million, a 50 percent increase over 2006.
2.94m online music tracks were downloaded in the UK in the last week of 2007, according to the BPI, a record industry body. The figure is double that for the same time in 2006, when 1.47m tracks were downloaded, and nearly three times that for the same week in 2005, when only 1m songs were downloaded.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>