<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Planning on Damien Saunders</title>
    <link>https://damien.co/tags/planning/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Planning on Damien Saunders</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 Jul 2010 09:00:51 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://damien.co/tags/planning/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Start a Social Media Marketing Plan – why social media?</title>
      <link>https://damien.co/social-media/start-a-social-media-marketing-plan-why-social-media-1113/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jul 2010 09:00:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien.co/social-media/start-a-social-media-marketing-plan-why-social-media-1113/</guid>
      <description>Do you really need a Social Media Marketing Plan? And if your business needs a plan … why does it have to be social media?
Why Social Media Every business – big, small, startup or established brand needs to be using social media – yesterday. I was reading a flyer today which said ‘its critical for every website to include social media’ — its not the website that needs it … its your marketing and sales plan!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Start a Social Media Marketing Plan – don’t leave it to the PR person</title>
      <link>https://damien.co/social-media/start-a-social-media-marketing-plan-dont-leave-it-to-the-pr-person-1108/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jun 2010 09:00:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien.co/social-media/start-a-social-media-marketing-plan-dont-leave-it-to-the-pr-person-1108/</guid>
      <description>Social Media marketing – using Twitter, Facebook, LinkedIn, Foursquare, Google+ … needs to form part of any marketing plan across the marketing mix. Treating Social Media as a separate activity from the rest of your marketing is a No-No … In fact social media should be integrated into every campaign or promotion.
Social Media marketing fits into new customer acquisition, customer retention, CRM, customer loyalty and anything else that customers do and thats true for D2C brands as well as B2B marketers.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>