<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>marketing consultant on Damien Saunders</title>
    <link>http://damien.co/tags/marketing-consultant/</link>
    <description>Recent content in marketing consultant on Damien Saunders</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2011 11:27:33 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://damien.co/tags/marketing-consultant/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>5 reasons why I choose to use WordPress</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/wordpress/5-reasons-why-i-choose-to-use-wordpress-3554/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2011 11:27:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/wordpress/5-reasons-why-i-choose-to-use-wordpress-3554/</guid>
      <description>If you’re reading and researching Why WordPress – you’ll probably see many articles focus on three words – Free, Simple &amp;amp; Easy. These words tell you nothing about WordPress and so I started writing this to help you decide to choose WordPress.
I started using WordPress in 2003 and I still have my hosted account London.WordPress.com. I switched to self-hosted in 2009.
For me, I’ve chosen WordPress because
 WordPress is something I use everyday I recommend WordPress to clients and friends WordPress integrates in a social media marketing strategy WordPress can morph from a blog to a website or a CMS Getting started is hassle-free   WordPress is right to use everydayWordPress, it’s mobile app, plugins and 3rdparty tools are improving – this makes WordPress something I enjoy using every day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Made the switch &amp;#8211; online accounting tools that are easy to use</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/marketing-consultant-2/made-the-switch-online-accounting-tools-that-are-easy-to-use-3097/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 May 2011 11:43:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/marketing-consultant-2/made-the-switch-online-accounting-tools-that-are-easy-to-use-3097/</guid>
      <description>I’ve made the switch to Zoho Books … as an international traveller and marketing consultant, I needed accounting tools that move with me and one that is flexible with invoicing in a number of currencies.
Zoho Invoice has been my friend for some time – but I wasn’t committed to this product – when Zoho Books arrived I jumped ship and have paid up for 12 months.
Zoho Books allows me to</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Must have Android Apps for Marketing Consultants</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/marketing-consultant-2/must-have-android-apps-for-marketing-consultants-2866/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Apr 2011 10:33:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/marketing-consultant-2/must-have-android-apps-for-marketing-consultants-2866/</guid>
      <description>What shortcuts or widgets should you save to the desktop of you Anrdoid phone? As a marketing consultant I’ve customised my phone lots (thanks to Cyanogenmod) .. but my desktop stays the same.
I don’t have many widgets as they eat up battery life (and annoyingly want internet connection).
What’s on your Android Desktop? Winamp – best music player for Android
Now that I have a larger long-life battery – I’m back to listening to music on my phone.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What&amp;#8217;s it like being a social media consultant [humour]</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/social-media/whats-it-like-being-a-social-media-consultant-humour-2798/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Mar 2011 12:51:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/social-media/whats-it-like-being-a-social-media-consultant-humour-2798/</guid>
      <description>Social Media Marketing Consultant Time Management humour</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to choose a good social media marketing consultant</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/2010-11-23-how-to-choose-a-good-social-media-marketing-consultant/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Nov 2010 09:41:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/2010-11-23-how-to-choose-a-good-social-media-marketing-consultant/</guid>
      <description>Social media marketingis no longer a buzzword and many brands and businesses are choosing to recruit full-time staff to develop and deliver the quicksilver successesof the best viral campaigns.What’s the difference between a social media consultant, digital planner &amp;amp; a community manager? If you are looking for an independent social media strategist to come in as a consultant or freelance gig then you need to know why a social media marketing consultant is very different to a digital planner or community manager.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>