<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>seo on Damien Saunders</title>
    <link>https://damien.co/tags/seo/</link>
    <description>Recent content in seo on Damien Saunders</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 Dec 2011 21:07:41 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://damien.co/tags/seo/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>WordPress: 9 Plugins for any new install</title>
      <link>https://damien.co/blog/2011-12-28-wordpress-top-9-plugins-for-any-new-install-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Dec 2011 21:07:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien.co/blog/2011-12-28-wordpress-top-9-plugins-for-any-new-install-2/</guid>
      <description>WordPress is one of the World’s most used web and blog tools – it has 1000’s of plugins that add functionality to your website. Here then is a short list of essential WordPress Plugins from WordPress.org to get you started. The list covers SEO, Spam, Analytics and helps you get started with Google SERP.
Akismet Akismet is included in every installation of WordPress, so that makes it one of the alltime popular plugins.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SEO best practice for using &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt; and &amp;lt;em&amp;gt;</title>
      <link>https://damien.co/social-media/seo-best-practice-for-using-strong-and-em-2695/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2011 09:42:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien.co/social-media/seo-best-practice-for-using-strong-and-em-2695/</guid>
      <description>As more people become aware of HTML5 it’s time to review how tagging written content will impact search engine optimisation. Tags like and are redundant – instead and have been in use for a few years by many blogging and web developer tools. Now the HTML5 standard recognises that and should only be used for visual style.
You can do more with CSS styles If you remember writing HTML back in the 90’s you might be more comfortable using and .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best WordPress plugins for social media marketing</title>
      <link>https://damien.co/wordpress/best-wordpress-plugins-for-social-media-marketing-2319/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jan 2011 09:20:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien.co/wordpress/best-wordpress-plugins-for-social-media-marketing-2319/</guid>
      <description>Social Media Marketing plugins for WordPress – you only need a few to have a powerful integrated marketing website.
WordPress plugins there are millions(?) to choose from and they are so easy to install. I tend to be cutting edge and change my plugins often, but here are some of the best plugins to improve WordPress for social media and digital marketing.
The point here is that writing original content can be easy – but your great works need to be found.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LinkedIn makes it easier to view who viewed your profile</title>
      <link>https://damien.co/social-media/linkedin-makes-it-easier-to-view-who-viewed-your-profile-1777/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Nov 2010 09:07:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien.co/social-media/linkedin-makes-it-easier-to-view-who-viewed-your-profile-1777/</guid>
      <description>LinkedInhas changed its settings so that basic or free users can now find out who actually looked at their profile in the last week. This cool new feature can be found on the LinkedIn website– but you have to first change your own privacy settings from anonymous to share in the benefits of profile stats. I guess its the business persons equivalent of a Facebook poke or like.
Check it out … and while you’re at it – add me as a colleague on LinkedIn</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HOW TO: Google Maps Local claim your business</title>
      <link>https://damien.co/mobile-marketing/how-to-google-maps-local-claim-your-business-930/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 May 2010 08:00:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien.co/mobile-marketing/how-to-google-maps-local-claim-your-business-930/</guid>
      <description>Google Maps is the first site that any business should visit before starting mobile or geospecific marketing. Google Maps Local provides a range of tools to make it easy for anyone to check their details and claim your business.
Why do you need to claim your business on Google Maps? We all know the phenomenon that is searching for something on Google from a Mobile – so as more people have Androidphones or iPhones or other smartphones, more people will use Mobile Internet for Search.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WordPress: 9 Plugins for any new install</title>
      <link>https://damien.co/wordpress/wordpress-top-9-plugins-for-any-new-install-693/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Mar 2010 21:07:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien.co/wordpress/wordpress-top-9-plugins-for-any-new-install-693/</guid>
      <description>WordPress provides a great tool to build and run your own website – it has 1000’s of plugins that add functionality to your website. Here then is a short list of essential plugins to get you started.Akismet Akismet is included in every installation of WordPress and so it make it one of the most popular plugins. There are better spam protectors, this doesn’t stop spam comments. You need a wordpress.com user name so that the plugin can sync over the internet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3 Reasons SMS marketing will die this year</title>
      <link>https://damien.co/mobile-marketing/3-reasons-sms-marketing-will-die-this-year-520/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2010 10:55:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien.co/mobile-marketing/3-reasons-sms-marketing-will-die-this-year-520/</guid>
      <description>Have you had a funny feeling in your pocket lately? Have you noticed a distinct lack of marketing SMS or that you only get SMS from your bank or your mobile operator – no more unwanted SMS. Smart digital agencies and mobile marketing specialists are already moving their clients from this type of communications. There are 3 very good reasons that this year is the year SMS marketing will die. 1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to not impact your SEO and website traffic when changing WordPress Permalinks</title>
      <link>https://damien.co/blog/2010-01-19-how-to-not-impact-your-seo-and-website-traffic-when-changing-wordpress-permalinks-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jan 2010 17:54:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien.co/blog/2010-01-19-how-to-not-impact-your-seo-and-website-traffic-when-changing-wordpress-permalinks-2/</guid>
      <description>Having made some changes to your wordpress permalinks, you can easily protect your web site traffic, SEO and search results from Google. This means you and your visitors get no 404 not found error.
This wordpress plug-in looks at the incoming link URL structure and then redirects on the fly to the correct post with the new permalink structure.
This didn’t make my list of Top 9 WordPress pluginsfor a new install – but if you are migrating a website this is critical.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to not impact your SEO and website traffic when changing WordPress Permalinks</title>
      <link>https://damien.co/wordpress/how-to-not-impact-your-seo-and-website-traffic-when-changing-wordpress-permalinks-406/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jan 2010 17:54:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien.co/wordpress/how-to-not-impact-your-seo-and-website-traffic-when-changing-wordpress-permalinks-406/</guid>
      <description>Having made some changes to your wordpress permalinks, you can easily protect your web site traffic, SEO and search results from Google. This means you and your visitors get no 404 not found error.
This wordpress plug-in looks at the incoming link URL structure and then redirects on the fly to the correct post with the new permalink structure.
This didn’t make my list of Top 9 WordPress pluginsfor a new install – but if you are migrating a website this is critical.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>