<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Strategy on Damien Saunders</title>
    <link>http://damien.co/categories/strategy/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Strategy on Damien Saunders</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 09 Oct 2012 13:11:34 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://damien.co/categories/strategy/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Agile Project Retrospectives the perfect measure</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/2012-10-09-project-retrospectives-the-perfect-measure/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Oct 2012 13:11:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/2012-10-09-project-retrospectives-the-perfect-measure/</guid>
      <description>Seriously … Next time you&amp;rsquo;re running a project retrospective or other review, keep a count of your WTFs/minute.
One very good reason - if you&amp;rsquo;re thinking WTF and something doesn&amp;rsquo;t make sense, then the person next to you is probably thinking the same thing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Piwik Web Analytics best free alternative</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/2012-04-10-piwik-web-analytics-best-free-alternative/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Apr 2012 12:34:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/2012-04-10-piwik-web-analytics-best-free-alternative/</guid>
      <description>Have you tried Piwik yet? If you&amp;rsquo;ve been using Google Analytics and started to wonder what alternative web analytic tools are out there then look no further then Piwik.
Piwikis a web analytics solution that is free and runs on your own server. It provides a lot of similar features to Google Analytics and will run alongside Google Analytics anyway.
Why stick with Google Analytics? Now I love GA and will always implement it as a first choice.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Are you on top of your Social Media Marketing Strategy for 2011?</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/strategy/are-you-on-top-of-your-social-media-marketing-strategy-for-2011-3125/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2011 11:16:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/strategy/are-you-on-top-of-your-social-media-marketing-strategy-for-2011-3125/</guid>
      <description>You&amp;rsquo;re never too late to start your 2011 Social Media Marketing Strategy - This year has gone so fast and I missed starting my Marketing Strategy on 1/1/11. For many marketing people and businesses, developing your strategy is something usually done in the first 3 months of your financial year or calendar year.
If this is the approach your business currently takes, then realise that you&amp;rsquo;re leaving just 75% of the year to deliver 100% of what you set out to achieve.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[video] Online Shopping with Swedish Twist - 3 LiveShop</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/strategy/video-online-shopping-with-swedish-twist-3-liveshop-3039/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2011 10:09:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/strategy/video-online-shopping-with-swedish-twist-3-liveshop-3039/</guid>
      <description>Have you seen this … This has to be the future of customer service and online shopping — say goodbye to messy forms or complicated shopping charts. Those crazy people in Tre Sweden www.tre.se just like to push the envelope here. And maybe some of those other mobile operators or utility providers can do this too.
Once you&amp;rsquo;ve checked out this promo video - go take a look at the 3 LiveShop - it uses Adobe Flash embed video chat for the fun stuff.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Get your message right - Effective Marketing Strategy</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/strategy/get-your-message-right-effective-marketing-strategy-1493/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Sep 2010 11:00:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/strategy/get-your-message-right-effective-marketing-strategy-1493/</guid>
      <description>Creating an effective marketing strategyduring a recession is tough. When you&amp;rsquo;re faced with budget cuts to your marketing spend or trying to figure out what you can do with no budget then you need a plan. The third step to this plan is to get your message rightWhat is your customer telling you? Customers are always looking for 2 things - The right priceor a better offer. Westerners may not be as good at bargaining as some cultures are, but we all want to know we got a good deal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Know your target – Effective Marketing Strategy</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/strategy/know-your-target-effective-marketing-strategy-1475/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2010 16:00:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/strategy/know-your-target-effective-marketing-strategy-1475/</guid>
      <description>Creating an effective marketing strategyduring a recession is tough. when you&amp;rsquo;re faced with budget cuts to your marketing spend or trying to figure out what you can do with no budget then you need a plan. The second step to this plan is to know your target.Picture your ideal potential customer In any business you need to market to three types of customers. The potentials who don&amp;rsquo;t know about you, your existing customers and your lapsed customers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>5 Steps to Effective Marketing Strategy – Know your market</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/strategy/5-steps-to-effective-marketing-strategy-know-your-market-1470/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Sep 2010 11:00:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/strategy/5-steps-to-effective-marketing-strategy-know-your-market-1470/</guid>
      <description>Creating an effective marketing strategyduring a recession is tough. When you&amp;rsquo;re faced with budget cuts to your marketing spend or trying to figure out what you can do with no budget. You need an effective marketing strategy. The first step to this plan is to know your market.
It&amp;rsquo;s a sad fact that if you don&amp;rsquo;t market your product, service or even yourself … Then any potential customers will not find you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>5 steps to create an effective marketing strategy in a downturn</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/strategy/5-steps-to-create-an-effective-marketing-strategy-in-a-downturn-1461/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Sep 2010 11:00:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/strategy/5-steps-to-create-an-effective-marketing-strategy-in-a-downturn-1461/</guid>
      <description>Creating an effective marketing strategyduring a recession is tough. When you&amp;rsquo;re faced with budget cuts to your marketing spend or trying to figure out what you can do with no budget then you need something better than a good plan, you&amp;rsquo;re needing a marketing strategy that leads to success. 
This week, Ill be writing about 5 steps to create an effective marketing plan. All too often we run out of time and take a JFDI attitude towards to planning and strategy.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>