<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Releases on Damien Saunders</title>
    <link>http://damien.co/tags/releases/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Releases on Damien Saunders</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2013 23:28:47 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://damien.co/tags/releases/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Isotope Visual Layouts with Infinite Scroll</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/2013-08-09-isotope-visual-layouts-with-infinite-scroll/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2013 23:28:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/2013-08-09-isotope-visual-layouts-with-infinite-scroll/</guid>
      <description>Isotope Visual Layouts Pro is getting an update … and it’s one that a few of you have been asking for.
Isotope Visual Layouts Pro 1.9 is currently in testing and it will include a shortcode for Infinite Scroll.
I’m also making it safe to use on any page or post so you can really have different layouts (like one with infinite scroll and one with filtrify)
This will be the ‘last’ update for Isotope Visual Layouts Pro … I’m working on something hotter with sorting and drag n drop.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WordPress 3.5.2 is here &amp;#8211; time to update your site</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/2013-06-23-wordpress-3-5-2-is-here-time-to-update-your-site/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2013 16:20:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/2013-06-23-wordpress-3-5-2-is-here-time-to-update-your-site/</guid>
      <description>WordPress 3.5.2 is here … and it’s not to be confused with the 3.6 beta releases. Being a point release, you shouldn’t expect significant changes. WordPress 3.5.2 is a security release, which means it’s critical that you update your site.
What’s in WordPress 3.5.2? The release note for this specifically looks to address a bunch of security related issues:
 Blocking server-side request forgery attacks, which could potentially enable an attacker to gain access to a site.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Teaser &amp;#8211; Visual Layouts Pro (freetile)</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/2013-04-22-teaser-visual-layouts-pro-freetile/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2013 12:11:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/2013-04-22-teaser-visual-layouts-pro-freetile/</guid>
      <description>Development has finished on my next plugin … Visual Layouts Pro (Freetile) plugin.
This takes the Freetile jQuery plugin and mashes it up with Filtrify and Twitter Bootstrap to give you an awesome plugin for a responsive, visual layout …

 Key Features of Visual Layouts Pro  Tags &amp;amp; Category based filters Show / Hide content Show Excerpt Works on posts, pages Includes Twitter Bootstrap with powerful options for CSS and web design Pagination  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Visual Layouts Pro</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/2013-04-09-visual-layouts-pro/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2013 11:27:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/2013-04-09-visual-layouts-pro/</guid>
      <description>I’ve just finished work on the first release of my WordPress plugin Visual Layouts Pro — this features the awesome Freetile jQuery plugin for a responsive visual grid layout.
Visual Layouts Pro, like my other plugins, offers the best features for creating a grid layout framework for your WordPress site – without needing to change your theme!
  Key Features Visual Layouts WordPress plugin  Uses Twitter Bootstrap CSS and grid framework Shortcode for including the excerpt Pagination Works on any post, page or custom post type Options to include featured images – image and text, or text only.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Isotope Visual Layouts Pro plugin for WordPress switches to Twitter Bootstrap</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/2013-03-19-isotope-visual-layouts-pro-plugin-for-wordpress-switches-to-twitter-bootstrap/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2013 11:31:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/2013-03-19-isotope-visual-layouts-pro-plugin-for-wordpress-switches-to-twitter-bootstrap/</guid>
      <description>Isotope Visual Layouts Pro WordPress plugin is easier to use now that it’s using the Twitter Bootstrap framework with great CSS options and features.
Damien’s WordPress plugins have great features that mean you can improve your website and not change your theme. This is ideal for a designer or developer who wants to change the look n feel via custom CSS. Overtime, I’ve come to realise that most people download or buy the plugin on the basis off the look.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Isotope Visual Layouts for WordPress &amp;amp; Twitter Bootstrap</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/2013-03-05-isotope-visual-layouts-for-wordpress-twitter-bootstrap/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2013 09:32:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/2013-03-05-isotope-visual-layouts-for-wordpress-twitter-bootstrap/</guid>
      <description>**teaser**</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Isotope Visual Layouts &amp;#8211; Pro Plugin is here</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/2013-03-04-isotope-visual-layouts-pro-plugin-is-here/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2013 15:00:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/2013-03-04-isotope-visual-layouts-pro-plugin-is-here/</guid>
      <description>Isotope Visual Layouts Pro plugin is here — with many new features. Now you can change your website without changing your theme.
 [wooslider slider_type=”attachments” thumbnails=”true” id=”isotope_pro”]
 Key Features of Isotope Visual Layouts for WordPress  Isotope for stunning visual layouts Featured Image custom sizing choose Thumb, Medium or Large to control your visual layout Click to Resize / zoom effect (jQuery + CSS affect) Infinite Scroll (disabled by default – not needed if you don’t want to use to pagination) Shortcode works on any post or page Shortcode works with posts, pages &amp;amp; custom post types Further ‘add-ons’ available to use with this plugin, like Visual Layouts Filtrify for filtering tags or categories Paging / Pagination option Include the Excerpt option Create as many Visual Layouts as you want Click to Resize / zoom on a grid item, adds / removes a .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Visual Layouts for WordPress turns Pro and gets Twitter Bootstrap</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/2013-03-03-visual-layouts-for-wordpress-turns-pro-and-gets-twitter-bootstrap/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2013 15:45:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/2013-03-03-visual-layouts-for-wordpress-turns-pro-and-gets-twitter-bootstrap/</guid>
      <description>Visual Layouts is the alternative, responsive, animated, grid layout WordPress plugin. It’s similar to adding isotope and masonry jQuery. Visual Layouts for WordPress is another way that you can change your website without changing your theme.
Now Visual Layouts is turning Pro and the first feature I’ll show off is integration with Twitter Bootstrap CSS.
I think that Twitter Bootstrapis an awesome solution for anyone wanting to use good web design concepts – of course, the internet might be pretty ‘bland’ if we all used this framework.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Isotope Visual Layouts lite &amp;#8211; gets an update &amp;amp; a new name</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/2013-02-22-isotope-visual-layouts-lite-gets-an-update-a-new-name/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2013 11:00:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/2013-02-22-isotope-visual-layouts-lite-gets-an-update-a-new-name/</guid>
      <description>WordPress is a great tool for Websites, Blogs, Ecommerce and pretty much anything else … Which is why Isotope Visual Layouts is such a great plugin. Now you can easily change your website without changing your theme.
How to Update / Upgrade Isotope Visual Layouts lite – slightly newer name – has just had an update to v2 and if you already have it installed, you can get an update / upgrade from your Admin Plugin page (see image below).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Just Announced: Isotope Visual Layouts plugin gets Filtrify for tags &amp;amp; filtering</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/2013-02-04-just-announced-isotope-visual-layouts-plugin-gets-filtrify-for-tags-filtering/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Feb 2013 11:55:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/2013-02-04-just-announced-isotope-visual-layouts-plugin-gets-filtrify-for-tags-filtering/</guid>
      <description>Visual Layouts Filtrify is my newest plugin for WordPress and my first plugin to extend Isotope Visual Post Layouts.
What does Visual Layouts Filtrify do?   Add drop-down menus and filtering to your website
  Works with tags and categories (no configuration)
  Works with my Isotope Visual Post Layouts.
  My very, very, very popular Isotope Visual Post Layouts — more than 1,000 downloads so far!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DBC Backup 2 &amp;#8211; WordPress database backup &amp;#8211; Here comes version 2.1</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/2012-07-27-dbc-backup-2-wordpress-database-backup-here-comes-version-2-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jul 2012 16:30:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/2012-07-27-dbc-backup-2-wordpress-database-backup-here-comes-version-2-1/</guid>
      <description>DBC Backup 2for WordPress database backup has just been updated. The new version improves the user experience for managing the plugin as well as fixing minor bugs.
What is in the new release? 
The new release includes:
 A new admin page layout consistent with other WordPress plugins moves the link for DBC Backup to the Tools menu, again consistent with other plugins Fixes a problem where the user options where not deleted if the plugin was deleted Addresses a problem where users forgot to check the Active for the backup schedule Includes new options for social media sharing and getting help &amp;amp; support.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WordPress Security make sure you update today</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/2012-04-23-wordpress-security-make-sure-you-update-today/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Apr 2012 15:42:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/2012-04-23-wordpress-security-make-sure-you-update-today/</guid>
      <description>When ever there is a security updatefor WordPress you should always update your blog and website as soon as possible. According to Kasperskyone of the reasons that the recent Flashback Mac OSx Trojan malware infected 600,000+ computers was due to infected WordPress websites.
So how did this happen? When developers build you a website there typically is no time or budget left over for maintenance and updates. This means websites can be left running on old versions of WordPress with known security issues and these can be exploited by hackers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WordPress 3.3.2</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/2012-04-23-wordpress-3-3-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Apr 2012 11:45:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/2012-04-23-wordpress-3-3-2/</guid>
      <description>WordPress 3.3.2 is here … and it’s not to be confused with the 3.4 beta releases. Being a point release, you shouldn’t expect significant changes.
WordPress 3.3.2 is a security release, which means it’s critical that you update your site. The release notefor this
 Media Upload – the Flash Uploader and the newer Plupload have been updated Vulnerability where a site administrator could deactivate network-wide plugins Cross-site scripting vulnerability when making URLs clickable and in redirects after posting comments in older browsers, and when filtering URLs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WordPress 3.4 beta 3 is here</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/2012-04-22-wordpress-3-4-beta-3-is-here/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Apr 2012 21:31:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/2012-04-22-wordpress-3-4-beta-3-is-here/</guid>
      <description>‘Another week, another beta’ so it seem. WordPress 3.4is on its way … it’s entered public beta, which means you can download it and try it for yourself. This is beta 3 so we can probably expect Release Candidate 1 in a week.
Don’t try this at home if you’re new to WordPress.
WordPress 3.4 does a lot for Themes and Theme Developers As I’ve previously posted, this release is all about themes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WordPress 3.4 enters public beta &amp;#8211; benefits for Themes</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/2012-04-08-wordpress-3-4-enters-public-beta-benefits-for-themes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Apr 2012 18:13:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/2012-04-08-wordpress-3-4-enters-public-beta-benefits-for-themes/</guid>
      <description>WordPress 3.4is on its way … it’s entered public beta, which means you can download it and try it for yourself. Don’t try this at home if you’re new to WordPress.
WordPress 3.4 does a lot for Themes and Theme Developers Basically, WordPress 3.4 is all about themes. Many of the changes are described with a lot of jargon so far.
The release note details a lot of theme changes:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WordPress 3.3 is here &amp;#8230; get updating</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/2011-12-14-wordpress-3-3-is-here-get-updating/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2011 09:11:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/2011-12-14-wordpress-3-3-is-here-get-updating/</guid>
      <description>WordPress 3.3 is here … I’ve been a little slow in posting this as I was busying myself checking a number of websites have all updated ok. But now it’s time. Get updating!
If you haven’t already figured out that something new is happening with WordPress then read … Getting to grips with WordPress 3.3
Should you update now? Yes … update to WordPress 3.3 as soon as possible in order to take advantage of the new features.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting to grips with WordPress 3.3</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/2011-12-05-getting-to-grips-with-wordpress-3-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Dec 2011 14:30:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/2011-12-05-getting-to-grips-with-wordpress-3-3/</guid>
      <description>Now that the first release candidate for WordPress 3.3 is out, we can all plan (hopefully) for the real thing to be out before we take-off for Christmas Holidays in about 2 weeks.
Getting to grips with WordPress 3.3 This is a significant point release but don’t expect ‘major’ new features. Anyway, here are the features you’ll like and a little run-down of each one:
– Fly-out Menus with some responsive design</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WordPress 3.3 release candidate 1 is here</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/2011-12-01-wordpress-3-3-release-candidate-1-is-here/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2011 19:11:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/2011-12-01-wordpress-3-3-release-candidate-1-is-here/</guid>
      <description>The first release candidate for the next version of WordPress 3.3 is here. If you haven’t started testing, now is the time.
 WordPress 3.3 what you can expect WordPress 3.3 has already had 4 beta releases – so this RC is getting close to the finished product.
WordPress 3.3 has some cool features – including re-work on the WordPress Toolbar for logged in users, changes to backend admin pages and minor improvements for multisite admins.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WordPress just updated to 3.2.1</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/wordpress/wordpress-just-updated-to-3-2-1-2-4431/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Jul 2011 23:10:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/wordpress/wordpress-just-updated-to-3-2-1-2-4431/</guid>
      <description>WordPress just released 3.2.1 so that means it’s time to update your WordPress install. This is a minor update and only a week since 3.2 was launched..
What’s in this release?There isn’t much from a user or admin perspective, but you don’t normally expect that in a point release.
The main deliverables in the release are:
•Changes to the default Twenty Eleven theme
•some RTL (right to left) fixes.
• set browser default font to sans-serif.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WordPress just updated to 3.2.1</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/2011-07-17-wordpress-just-updated-to-3-2-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Jul 2011 22:10:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/2011-07-17-wordpress-just-updated-to-3-2-1/</guid>
      <description>WordPress just released 3.2.1 so that means it’s time to update your WordPress install. This is a minor update and only a week since 3.2 was launched..
What’s in this release?There isn’t much from a user or admin perspective, but you don’t normally expect that in a point release.
 The main deliverables in the release are:
• Changes to the default Twenty Eleven theme
• some RTL (right to left) fixes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WordPress 3.2 is here – time to update</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/wordpress/wordpress-3-2-is-here-%e2%80%93-time-to-update-4434/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jul 2011 12:19:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/wordpress/wordpress-3-2-is-here-%e2%80%93-time-to-update-4434/</guid>
      <description>The next version of WordPress is here – it’s going to make the admin section look awhole lot different.
So it’s true – WordPress 3.2 is here and after a couple of months anticipation it’s time to update.
What’s in WordPress 3.2? 
 It has a great new look to the admin section. The whole backend doesn’t look so tired. The admin performance should also be somewhat faster.
 Should you update now?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WordPress 3.2 is here &amp;#8211; time to update</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/2011-07-05-wordpress-3-2-is-here-time-to-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jul 2011 11:19:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/2011-07-05-wordpress-3-2-is-here-time-to-update/</guid>
      <description>The next version of WordPress is here – it’s going to make the admin section look awhole lot different.
So it’s true – WordPress 3.2 is here and after a couple of months anticipation it’s time to update.
What’s in WordPress 3.2? 
 It has a great new look to the admin section. The whole backend doesn’t look so tired. The admin performance should also be somewhat faster.
 Should you update now?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WordPress 3.2 Release Candidate 3</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/wordpress/wordpress-3-2-release-candidate-3-2-4438/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Jul 2011 15:21:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/wordpress/wordpress-3-2-release-candidate-3-2-4438/</guid>
      <description>Improved look n feel / user experience to the Admin pages (after many years) Integrated the admin homepage header (with the WordPress Logo) with the left hand menu Admin bar has changed for single install and network admins Admin left hand menu has changed with big text to collapse / hide Network / Admin menu has been integrated in User menu / dropdown on the top right  Before you update any live site – backup  If you’re still stuck … get in contact and I’ll be happy to help you through</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WordPress 3.2 Release Candidate 3</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/2011-07-02-wordpress-3-2-release-candidate-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Jul 2011 14:21:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/2011-07-02-wordpress-3-2-release-candidate-3/</guid>
      <description>Improved look n feel / user experience to the Admin pages (after many years) Integrated the admin homepage header (with the WordPress Logo) with the left hand menu Admin bar has changed for single install and network admins Admin left hand menu has changed with big text to collapse / hide Network / Admin menu has been integrated in User menu / dropdown on the top right  Before you update any live site – backup If you’re still stuck … get in contact and I’ll be happy to help you through</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WordPress Security Updates Again?</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/2010-12-30-wordpress-security-updates-again-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Dec 2010 13:07:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/2010-12-30-wordpress-security-updates-again-2/</guid>
      <description>Security Updates, I had thought were a thing that only happened to people running Windows operating system. Yet WordPress has issued 3 patches in the last 30 days to address security fixes.
30 November 2010WordPress 3.0.2 was a mandatory security update.
This was the first update in nearly 6 months so it was a surprise that barely a week later we get another update.
8 December 2010WordPress 3.0.3 came out as an update for all previous versions of WordPress.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>