<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>scrum on Damien Saunders</title>
    <link>https://damien.co/tags/scrum/</link>
    <description>Recent content in scrum on Damien Saunders</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 09 Oct 2012 13:11:34 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://damien.co/tags/scrum/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Project Retrospectives &amp;#8211; the perfect measure</title>
      <link>https://damien.co/strategy/project-retrospectives-the-perfect-measure-7937/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Oct 2012 13:11:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien.co/strategy/project-retrospectives-the-perfect-measure-7937/</guid>
      <description>Seriously … Next time you’re running a project retrospective or other review, keep a count of your WTFs/minute.
One very good reason – if you’re thinking WTF and something doesn’t make sense, then the person next to you is probably thinking the same thing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>When done is really done &amp;#8211; Scrum &amp;#038; post it note management</title>
      <link>https://damien.co/blog/when-done-is-really-done-scrum-post-it-note-management-6269/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Mar 2012 22:44:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien.co/blog/when-done-is-really-done-scrum-post-it-note-management-6269/</guid>
      <description>There really is nothing better then looking at your office wall and knowing that done is done.
Post-it Note management has to be one of the easiest and most effective ways to create a wall board – information radiator – which you and your management can all follow.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Productivity Tip &amp;#8211; Technical Writing &amp;#038; the Writer&amp;#8217;s Block</title>
      <link>https://damien.co/blog/productivity-tip-technical-writing-the-writers-block-2617/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jan 2011 09:45:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien.co/blog/productivity-tip-technical-writing-the-writers-block-2617/</guid>
      <description>Each week I set aside time to good writing, but its not the same when each day there are technical documents and scrum artefacts to be prepared. I can’t guarantee to get my writing done. It just doesn’t work like that. Good productive writingtakes time, space and zero distractions – even when its a business process or project brief.

Technical Writing &amp;amp; the Writers block You hear about those creative types in marketing, you may know a few entrepreneurs or inventors who have a spark of genius.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Task Management with Post-It Notes</title>
      <link>https://damien.co/startup/task-management-with-post-it-notes-1832/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Nov 2010 09:56:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien.co/startup/task-management-with-post-it-notes-1832/</guid>
      <description>As I’m a certified Scrum Master and very good at project and task management I can say I enjoy running planning sessions with teams I do work with. Now I’ve started to discover the freedom of the Post-It Note for planning and brainstorming.

Even better, its essential for any startup to be able to focus on what has to be done and avoid distractions like outsiders wanting extra work or changes to scope.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>