<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>mobile seo on Damien Saunders</title>
    <link>http://damien.co/tags/mobile-seo/</link>
    <description>Recent content in mobile seo on Damien Saunders</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2010 10:55:13 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://damien.co/tags/mobile-seo/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>3 Reasons SMS marketing will die this year</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/2010-02-26-3-reasons-sms-marketing-will-die-this-year/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2010 10:55:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/2010-02-26-3-reasons-sms-marketing-will-die-this-year/</guid>
      <description>Have you had a funny feeling in your pocket lately? Have you noticed a distinct lack of marketing SMS or that you only get SMS from your bank or your mobile operator – no more unwanted SMS. Smart digital agencies and mobile marketing specialists are already moving their clients from this type of communications. There are 3 very good reasons that this year is the year SMS marketing will die. 1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mobile SEO &amp;#8211; Google extends click to call to mobile search</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/2010-02-08-mobile-seo-google-extends-click-to-call-to-mobile-search/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Feb 2010 09:11:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/2010-02-08-mobile-seo-google-extends-click-to-call-to-mobile-search/</guid>
      <description>In the next couple of weeks, I’ll be looking closely at Mobile Search and Mobile SEO. This week will be a round up of features on Google Mobile Search
Click to Call
Click to call has been a feature of WAP and mobile portals for sometime, however the mobile phones needed to support this action.
Google has now added Click to Call to Adword Mobile Search Results
Anyone running SEO or Adword campaigns should make sure they have configured the mobile search results as well and to now include the primary phone number for customers or clients to ring in on.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to make mobile part of your marketing strategy</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/2009-11-09-how-to-make-mobile-part-of-your-marketing-strategy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Nov 2009 09:01:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/2009-11-09-how-to-make-mobile-part-of-your-marketing-strategy/</guid>
      <description>Should you be worried that you don’t have an iPhone app? Do you know if you’re website works on a mobile? what about mobile SEO? It is very important for CEO’s and CMO’s to add mobile to their communications and marketing strategy.
The fact that most companies have yet to build a mobile website shows you are not alone and many companies want to know what they should do first.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>