<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>statistics on Damien Saunders</title>
    <link>http://damien.co/tags/statistics/</link>
    <description>Recent content in statistics on Damien Saunders</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 10 Sep 2012 14:06:15 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://damien.co/tags/statistics/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Startup Metrics for Pirates (SeedCamp 2008)</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/startup/startup-metrics-for-pirates-seedcamp-2008-7781/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Sep 2012 14:06:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/startup/startup-metrics-for-pirates-seedcamp-2008-7781/</guid>
      <description>If you’re in a Startup you need to agree quite quickly on some of those performance metrics and here, Dave McClure shares his view.
Sure you can go for the glamour figures — like millions of page views, likes or tweets. But wouldn’t you just prefer some hard cash? or qualified leads?
At the end of the day, the stats you pick, you have to stick with and track over time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Social Gaming is on the decline? Blame cannibalisation by mobile and OTT</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/insights-blog/why-social-gaming-decline-blame-cannibalisation-mobile-ott-7316/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jun 2012 14:22:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/insights-blog/why-social-gaming-decline-blame-cannibalisation-mobile-ott-7316/</guid>
      <description>Social Gaming is on the decline – not terminal decline, just platform cannibalisation. Well mostly. Some Social Gamers just go off and play other newer games. The big reason for the decline in social game, I believe is the rise of free games in App Stores like Android Play and iTunes App Store. These App Stores provide a direct to user channel for promotion of games.
5 reasons Social Gaming is on the decline There are 5 reasons this is happening</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Get Results from an Android Mobile Marketing Strategy</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/mobile-marketing/get-results-from-an-android-mobile-marketing-strategy-5885/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2012 13:12:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/mobile-marketing/get-results-from-an-android-mobile-marketing-strategy-5885/</guid>
      <description>Android Mobiles are taking over the world … and that seems to be supported by the latest statistics or _trends. _If you’re thinking about mobile marketing .. and wondering ‘what is all the fuss about Android’, then this presentation is for you.
Only the latest Android Insights and Statistics  10 billion app downloads (December 2011) 200 million activated devices (November 2011) 400,000 Android Apps (December 2011)  We can only wait for the next Google I/O conference to confirm how these numbers are growing!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Every Important Stat can be drawn in a 2&amp;#215;2 Grid</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/insights-blog/every-important-stat-can-be-drawn-in-a-2x2-grid-2800/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Mar 2011 09:10:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/insights-blog/every-important-stat-can-be-drawn-in-a-2x2-grid-2800/</guid>
      <description>Just to prove a point – the 2×2 grid is the best way to show-off pretty much interesting statistic or insight</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Using Social Media takes 20% of your Australian day</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/social-media/using-social-media-takes-20-of-your-australian-day-2786/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2011 09:25:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/social-media/using-social-media-takes-20-of-your-australian-day-2786/</guid>
      <description>Australians spend 1 in 5 minutes using social media sites. Social Networking usage was about 22% in December 2010 says comScore.
The statistics reveal that Facebook, Twitter, LinkedIn are some of the most popular destinations. If you add into this instant messaging then the total rises to 35% – which is probably a more realistic definition of social networking.
There is a presentation you can download with really good insights on internet usage across Australia.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>20,000 visitors so far this year</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/20000-visitors-so-far-this-year-1995/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Nov 2010 09:29:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/20000-visitors-so-far-this-year-1995/</guid>
      <description>So its mid-November and I’m just looking at the Google Analytics report to see how I’m getting on. Data visualisation is a big thing but raw numbers are also pretty good.20,000 visitors so far this year generated 50,000 page views.
That’s pretty good for a one man marketing guy and his machine.
Alexa’s Web Information also seems interesting – and if you don’t know what Alexa says about your site .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video &amp;amp; Integrated Marketing? Latest Internet Usage Video</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/social-media/video-integrated-marketing-latest-internet-usage-video-562/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Mar 2010 10:46:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/social-media/video-integrated-marketing-latest-internet-usage-video-562/</guid>
      <description>Integrated marketing takes a new turn. This latest viral marketing video focuses on the state of the internetand is essentially a load of stats overlaid with a nice cheesy beat playing. All of the statistics are freely available metrics on social media usage, number of internet users, amount of spam mail. Integrated Marketing Viral Video – State of the Internet You have to watch the video first:
Even if you have watched this video infographic already and love it (yes I love it) watch it again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Social Media &amp;amp; Marketing Round-up of some good reading</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/mobile-marketing/social-media-marketing-round-up-of-some-good-reading-375/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Dec 2009 16:36:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/mobile-marketing/social-media-marketing-round-up-of-some-good-reading-375/</guid>
      <description>**The problem with doing research on social media and mobile marketing is the overwhelming amount of noise you get from doing searches on Google, Delicious and Twitter.
**
Here are a few links of really useful and easy to consume ‘research’
best ‘inspirational’ video on social media
http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=sIFYPQjYhv8map of social media world
http://www.flickr.com/photos/wasabibratwurst/3128711125/sizes/l/top 100 companies by media spend</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UK album retail sales dip 11% for 2007</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/uk-album-retail-sales-dip-11-for-2007-68/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jan 2008 12:14:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/uk-album-retail-sales-dip-11-for-2007-68/</guid>
      <description>Album unbundling, copyright theft and difficult retail conditions contributed to a drop in album sales of 10.8% in 2007 say the British Phonographic Industry.The continued growth of download sales helped the singles market grow by 29.3% during 2007, which became the third biggest year on record for the format.Change = -10.8%Source: BPI website</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UK Digital sales grow by 50% in 2007</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/uk-digital-sales-grow-by-50-in-2007-66/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Jan 2008 11:12:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/uk-digital-sales-grow-by-50-in-2007-66/</guid>
      <description>The British Phonographic Industry, which represents the British recorded-music business, said total music download sales for the year topped 77 million, a 50 percent increase over 2006.
2.94m online music tracks were downloaded in the UK in the last week of 2007, according to the BPI, a record industry body. The figure is double that for the same time in 2006, when 1.47m tracks were downloaded, and nearly three times that for the same week in 2005, when only 1m songs were downloaded.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>