<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>social media reputation on Damien Saunders</title>
    <link>http://damien.co/tags/social-media-reputation/</link>
    <description>Recent content in social media reputation on Damien Saunders</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2011 14:00:39 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://damien.co/tags/social-media-reputation/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Best Tools for Social Media Marketing if you&#39;re just getting started</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/2011-07-26-best-tools-for-social-media-marketing-if-youre-just-getting-started/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2011 14:00:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/2011-07-26-best-tools-for-social-media-marketing-if-youre-just-getting-started/</guid>
      <description>If you&amp;rsquo;re getting started with Social Media marketing then you need at least 1 web based tool to help you.
For most businesses and individuals, social media marketing starts and ends with Tweetdeck. Which provides an all-in-one solution for pushing content direct from your machine. You need better tools for planning and managing your social media marketing.
However browser based tools for social media marketing are better suited for team or office environs - or if you&amp;rsquo;re like me, someone on the road in different offices who can&amp;rsquo;t have Tweetdeck open all the time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Social Media Reputation Management using LinkedIn</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/2010-07-29-social-media-reputation-management-using-linkedin/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jul 2010 11:00:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/2010-07-29-social-media-reputation-management-using-linkedin/</guid>
      <description>Managing your online reputation will be more important over time for everyone - as we grow up the content and material that search engines will collect about us is phenomenal. For many, the CV will cease to exist and be replaced by online reputation, search engine results and specialist business networks like LinkedIn.LinkedIn has managed to hold on to the title of business social network over increasing competition from Facebook and other professional networks like Xing or even Plaxo.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Social Media Reputation Management – Google Profile</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/2010-07-28-social-media-reputation-management-google-profile/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jul 2010 11:00:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/2010-07-28-social-media-reputation-management-google-profile/</guid>
      <description>Did you know that Google has a profile page and that it&amp;rsquo;s similar to a profile page on LinkedIn. Managing your reputation and curating your personal SEO plan is something you should do at least once a year. About Google Profile Google Profilecan be associated with a normal Gmail e-mail address along with Google Apps domains and other addresses. In fact, you&amp;rsquo;ll find that if you use Google your profile comes &amp;lsquo;pre-filled&amp;rsquo; with info on what Google might know about you.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>