<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Marketing Consultant on Damien Saunders</title>
    <link>http://damien.co/categories/marketing-consultant/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Marketing Consultant on Damien Saunders</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 17 Jun 2012 18:47:42 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://damien.co/categories/marketing-consultant/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>41 things to do in 41 days to boost your digital marketing</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/marketing-consultant-2/41-things-to-do-in-41-days-to-boost-your-digital-marketing-7161/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Jun 2012 18:47:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/marketing-consultant-2/41-things-to-do-in-41-days-to-boost-your-digital-marketing-7161/</guid>
      <description>[typography font=”Special Elite” size=”25″ size_format=”px”]Want a quick head start to a digital marketing plan for your brand or business? Here are 41 things you can do … over 41 days.[/typography]
Allow an hour a day (and a bit extra at the end of the week to see how you’re progressing).
 Create an account on Twitter for you and your brand – find some friends to follow Create an account on Facebook Create a social media analytics account on MarketMeSuite to monitor your fans and followers Create a Google Alert to track online mentions of your brand Create a Google Alert for mentions of your product Create a Google Alert for mentions of your competitors Create a Google Alert for mentions of you Find out what Web Analytics Tools you use like Google Analytics &amp;amp; Bit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>JIRA for Project Management &amp;#8211; its not just for Issues</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/marketing-consultant-2/jira-for-project-management-its-not-just-for-issues-6138/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2012 15:51:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/marketing-consultant-2/jira-for-project-management-its-not-just-for-issues-6138/</guid>
      <description>If you’re reading this then you must use JIRA or know of someone who has had a JIRA experience. It seems that JIRA is a bit like a Marmite brand – you love it or you hate it. JIRA can be too much effort for many projects – but thats only cause the project can’t find time to build the value in JIRA.
I think that anything which helps take pain away from managing bugs, issues and tasks is brilliant.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google Analytics &amp;#8211; Event tracking is great for customer engagement</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/marketing-consultant-2/google-analytics-event-tracking-is-great-for-customer-engagement-5132/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2011 12:11:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/marketing-consultant-2/google-analytics-event-tracking-is-great-for-customer-engagement-5132/</guid>
      <description>Google Analytics provides a number of extra tools for the adventurous to improve tracking and provide valuable insights. Event tracking should be used throughout the user journey to better understand customer engagement.
Why Google Analytics? Google Analytics is one of the web’s most popular tools for reporting on activity and trends for just about any website. Your online and offline marketing activities need meaningful analytics data which creates actionable insights. In summary, website analytics has benefits for sales, marketing and product development – in fact most areas of your business.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google Analytics &amp;#038; Event Tracking</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/marketing-consultant-2/google-analytics-event-tracking-4983/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Nov 2011 13:53:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/marketing-consultant-2/google-analytics-event-tracking-4983/</guid>
      <description>Google Analytics provides a number of extra tools for the adventurous to improve tracking and provide valuable insights. There are two types of tracking you can have – event tracking is used to help analyse visitor behaviour onsite. It’s not complicated to do this – but it’s time consuming and complex.
Google Analytics is one of the web’s most popular tools for reporting on activity and trends for just about any website.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>4 reasons to choose Google Analytics for your business</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/marketing-consultant-2/4-reasons-to-choose-google-analytics-for-your-business-4932/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2011 16:13:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/marketing-consultant-2/4-reasons-to-choose-google-analytics-for-your-business-4932/</guid>
      <description>Google Analytics is one of the web’s most popular tools for reporting on activity and trends for just about any website. Your online and offline marketing activities need meaningful analytics data to create actionable insights. In summary, website analytics has benefits for sales, marketing and product development – in fact most areas of your business.
Why Choose Google Analytics? It’s easy to see why Google Analytics is so popular, because it’s free, but here are my top 4</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3 point plan for Agile Marketing</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/marketing-consultant-2/3-point-plan-for-agile-marketing-4667/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2011 09:45:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/marketing-consultant-2/3-point-plan-for-agile-marketing-4667/</guid>
      <description>Can you tell the difference between Agile, Guerilla or Real Time Marketing? Does it really matter? You need a 3 point plan for Agile marketing – or is it just your boss asking for a quicker turn-around?
What’s Agile marketing? Agile marketing is similar to real time marketing. So what makes it agile or is it a catchphrase?
Agile marketing is a bit of a new catchphrase, you’ll see it in the press and hear it around the offices.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best stylus to use with your iPad? (part 1)</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/marketing-consultant-2/best-stylus-to-use-with-your-ipad-part-1-3755/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2011 16:42:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/marketing-consultant-2/best-stylus-to-use-with-your-ipad-part-1-3755/</guid>
      <description>I’ll start by saying I’m a gadget boy — any marketing consultant working on innovation or product delivery has got to know about gadgets. When I got my first iPad last year, I quickly realised that my finger tip was useless for writing. I’ve been collecting styli or styluses and starting to get a good collection.
I have been stopped plenty of times to be asked what’s my preferred tool and over the past 12 months, I’ve used quite a few and thrown out some immediately.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Understand your website visitors with live web stats with GoSquared</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/marketing-consultant-2/understand-your-website-visitors-with-live-web-stats-with-gosquared-3532/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2011 11:02:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/marketing-consultant-2/understand-your-website-visitors-with-live-web-stats-with-gosquared-3532/</guid>
      <description>I just started to use GoSquared this week – If you’ve got a high traffic website (well any website really) and want some real-time web analytics or insights – then you better get started with a FREE GoSquared account today. Using GoSquared I can watch as visitors come and go.
Free Web Analytics &amp;amp; insights  GoSquared monitors and analyses your website’s traffic in real-time – and you can watch all the action in the LiveStats console – which is like a 3 part Heads-Up Display.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Made the switch &amp;#8211; online accounting tools that are easy to use</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/marketing-consultant-2/made-the-switch-online-accounting-tools-that-are-easy-to-use-3097/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 May 2011 11:43:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/marketing-consultant-2/made-the-switch-online-accounting-tools-that-are-easy-to-use-3097/</guid>
      <description>I’ve made the switch to Zoho Books … as an international traveller and marketing consultant, I needed accounting tools that move with me and one that is flexible with invoicing in a number of currencies.
Zoho Invoice has been my friend for some time – but I wasn’t committed to this product – when Zoho Books arrived I jumped ship and have paid up for 12 months.
Zoho Books allows me to</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Redmine for Issues &amp;#038; Bug track &amp;#8211; things I learned</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/marketing-consultant-2/redmine-for-issues-bug-track-things-i-learned-3058/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 May 2011 17:45:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/marketing-consultant-2/redmine-for-issues-bug-track-things-i-learned-3058/</guid>
      <description>Redmine is described as a flexible project management web application SaaS. I’ve been using it for the past 5 months within a mobile marketing agency – where its used for testing, operations, work orders, issue management and its wiki is used for documentation.
Redmine can not be compared to other bug track, issues or fault management systems like JIRA or CRM platforms with helpdesk tools. It’s flexible, but that comes with a price.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Must have Android Apps for Marketing Consultants</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/marketing-consultant-2/must-have-android-apps-for-marketing-consultants-2866/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Apr 2011 10:33:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/marketing-consultant-2/must-have-android-apps-for-marketing-consultants-2866/</guid>
      <description>What shortcuts or widgets should you save to the desktop of you Anrdoid phone? As a marketing consultant I’ve customised my phone lots (thanks to Cyanogenmod) .. but my desktop stays the same.
I don’t have many widgets as they eat up battery life (and annoyingly want internet connection).
What’s on your Android Desktop? Winamp – best music player for Android
Now that I have a larger long-life battery – I’m back to listening to music on my phone.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Marketing Consultants Guide to Business Class Apps for iPad</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/marketing-consultant-2/a-marketing-consultants-guide-to-business-class-apps-for-ipad-2853/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Apr 2011 08:03:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/marketing-consultant-2/a-marketing-consultants-guide-to-business-class-apps-for-ipad-2853/</guid>
      <description>If you haven’t got an iPad or still not convinced you’ll need one – then you’re kidding yourself. As a marketing consultant new gadgets like the iPad need to be purchased, used extensively and then replaced with the next new shiny gadget. Why – you might ask? Because how else can you have an opinion or recommend a solution to your clients.
Today – I’m taking a quick look at the list of apps featured in iTunes under the category ‘business class’.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>