<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Case Study on Damien Saunders</title>
    <link>https://damien1.github.io/tags/case-study/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Case Study on Damien Saunders</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2010 09:30:03 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://damien1.github.io/tags/case-study/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Case Study How to get 100 people in your retail store at the same time</title>
      <link>https://damien1.github.io/resources/case-study-how-to-get-100-people-in-your-retail-store-at-the-same-time-1932/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2010 09:30:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien1.github.io/resources/case-study-how-to-get-100-people-in-your-retail-store-at-the-same-time-1932/</guid>
      <description>Regular followers of my work, will have seen an earlier case study on Foursquare marketing for retail and I’ve recently been updating this. So this week there are a couple of posts on the Swarm Badge Party that was organised in Latvia.Client Brief Bite Latvija just opened a new technical advice and support centre dedicated to questions about mobile broadband, device configuration and helping people get the most from their mobile.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to get more people in your shop with Foursquare a Case Study</title>
      <link>https://damien1.github.io/resources/how-to-get-more-people-in-your-shop-with-foursquare-a-case-study-1723/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Oct 2010 09:00:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien1.github.io/resources/how-to-get-more-people-in-your-shop-with-foursquare-a-case-study-1723/</guid>
      <description>Have you been looking to use social media for marketing? Trying to think of creative ideas to get more people to visit your shops? Foursquare has a number of options for retailers to come up with engaging experiences to get more people in your shops.
Foursquare Swarm Badge Party This social media case study for Bite Latvija, a mobile operator shows how Foursquare was used to launch their new technology support centre – this led to increase customer awareness and customer engagement.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>