<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>iPad on Damien Saunders</title>
    <link>http://damien.co/tags/ipad/</link>
    <description>Recent content in iPad on Damien Saunders</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 25 May 2012 17:42:23 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://damien.co/tags/ipad/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>App Design: Design Museum clean layout &amp;#038; how to deal with scrolling</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/apps-2/app-design-design-museum-clean-layout-how-to-deal-with-scrolling-7148/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 May 2012 17:42:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/apps-2/app-design-design-museum-clean-layout-how-to-deal-with-scrolling-7148/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m a member of the Design Museum here in Londonand so it was nice to see they have a free app with collection of the best pieces. It does remind me of the Phaidon Design Classics book-as-an-app (which still has not been changed since the first iPad).
I like this application and I was researching text overflow and scrolling. Since iPad no longer shows scrollbars then it&amp;rsquo;s up to the user to figure what is scrolling or not.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FREE DOWNLOAD Axure Wireframe &amp;#038; Prototype for iPad</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/resources/free-download-axure-wireframe-prototype-for-ipad-4464/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Oct 2011 11:45:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/resources/free-download-axure-wireframe-prototype-for-ipad-4464/</guid>
      <description>I recently started using Axure for wire framing and creating clickable prototypes. I enjoyed it so much that I started to put together my own project for the Apple iPad with masters and a basic set of wireframes.
FREE Download iPad Axure Project Yes, it&amp;rsquo;s a free download and can be used under Creative Commons - CC-Attribution and you can use it for commercial and non-commercial projects. Just let me know please.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Using Axure for wireframes &amp;#038; user experience</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/resources/using-axure-for-wireframes-user-experience-4430/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Oct 2011 12:57:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/resources/using-axure-for-wireframes-user-experience-4430/</guid>
      <description>Recently I discovered Axure as a tool for mapping user experience - and I have to say it&amp;rsquo;s pretty damn good. Given that its also able to generate clickable prototypes along with documentation like functional specifications this is more then pretty damn good. It&amp;rsquo;s a powerful tool - but if you&amp;rsquo;re building user journeys, wire framing and process flows can be easier to do in other tools.
It&amp;rsquo;s hard to compare Axure to Balsamiq, Visio or Omnigraffle - particularly on price since Axure starts at around $580 per licence.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best stylus to use with your iPad? (part 1)</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/marketing-consultant-2/best-stylus-to-use-with-your-ipad-part-1-3755/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2011 16:42:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/marketing-consultant-2/best-stylus-to-use-with-your-ipad-part-1-3755/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ll start by saying I&amp;rsquo;m a gadget boy — any marketing consultant working on innovation or product delivery has got to know about gadgets. When I got my first iPad last year, I quickly realised that my finger tip was useless for writing. I&amp;rsquo;ve been collecting styli or styluses and starting to get a good collection.
I have been stopped plenty of times to be asked what&amp;rsquo;s my preferred tool and over the past 12 months, I&amp;rsquo;ve used quite a few and thrown out some immediately.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Marketing Consultants Guide to Business Class Apps for iPad</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/marketing-consultant-2/a-marketing-consultants-guide-to-business-class-apps-for-ipad-2853/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Apr 2011 08:03:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/marketing-consultant-2/a-marketing-consultants-guide-to-business-class-apps-for-ipad-2853/</guid>
      <description>If you haven&amp;rsquo;t got an iPad or still not convinced you&amp;rsquo;ll need one - then you&amp;rsquo;re kidding yourself. As a marketing consultant new gadgets like the iPad need to be purchased, used extensively and then replaced with the next new shiny gadget. Why - you might ask? Because how else can you have an opinion or recommend a solution to your clients.
Today - I&amp;rsquo;m taking a quick look at the list of apps featured in iTunes under the category &amp;lsquo;business class&amp;rsquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best iPad App for design and graphics gets better</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/general/best-ipad-app-for-design-and-graphics-gets-better-1857/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Nov 2010 10:59:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/general/best-ipad-app-for-design-and-graphics-gets-better-1857/</guid>
      <description>Sketchbook Pro, in my opinion is the best iPad app for photo editing, graphic and web design. And its new update just makes it better. The new release makes it a great all round tool for note taking, wireframe and web design.
A Power tool for notes, sketches and mockups I like to think I&amp;rsquo;m a pro digital photographer so I like my photo software to do amazing things - even if I cant.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Where to start building mobile apps for large screens - mobile agencies beware</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/2010-01-28-where-to-start-building-mobile-apps-for-large-screens-mobile-agencies-beware/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jan 2010 15:28:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/2010-01-28-where-to-start-building-mobile-apps-for-large-screens-mobile-agencies-beware/</guid>
      <description>Where to start with building a mobile app or going mobile has been a popular topic for some time. Many FMCG brands and agencies are requesting only quotes for mobile apps - forgetting the less popular java app or branded mobile game. At the expense of budget - haha - focusing on a mobile app can be a costly exercise starting from about 10k to 100k plus.
Marketing Agencies and their Brands need to go and reconsider their mobile strategy - and if you&amp;rsquo;ve already built a mobile app - you maybe disappointed how it looks on the larger screen devices.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>