<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>zoho on Damien Saunders</title>
    <link>https://damien.co/tags/zoho/</link>
    <description>Recent content in zoho on Damien Saunders</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2011 15:08:21 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://damien.co/tags/zoho/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Zoho CRM what is a lead vs contact vs opportunity</title>
      <link>https://damien.co/social-crm/zoho-crm-what-is-a-lead-vs-contact-vs-opportunity-799/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2011 10:14:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien.co/social-crm/zoho-crm-what-is-a-lead-vs-contact-vs-opportunity-799/</guid>
      <description>Zoho CRM is a cloud based SaaS (software as a service) for customer relationship management (CRM). How to setup and manage new and potential business contacts in Zoho raises the question – what is a lead, what is a contact and what is a potential in Zoho ‘Jargon’. Managing Leads, Contacts and Accounts is a critical function of your business and it’s just as important that you understand Zoho’s sales management process.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HOW TO get started with ZOHO CRM and load your contacts from Google CSV</title>
      <link>https://damien.co/social-crm/how-to-get-started-with-zoho-crm-and-load-your-contacts-from-google-csv-778/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Oct 2011 16:43:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien.co/social-crm/how-to-get-started-with-zoho-crm-and-load-your-contacts-from-google-csv-778/</guid>
      <description>So you have decided to use ZOHO CRM as your Customer Relationship Management (CRM) solution. You’re first step is to import your contacts into ZOHO. You will have contacts in a number of places and you want to get them all into ZOHO.
This guide applies to single users of ZOHO CRM and the SOHO small business marketing guy like me. I’ll start by focusing on the single user perspective of ZOHO – how to get mycontacts into ZOHO and then I’ll finish by mentioning a few tips for people who want to share ZOHO with others in their team.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Made the switch &amp;#8211; online accounting tools that are easy to use</title>
      <link>https://damien.co/marketing-consultant-2/made-the-switch-online-accounting-tools-that-are-easy-to-use-3097/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 May 2011 11:43:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien.co/marketing-consultant-2/made-the-switch-online-accounting-tools-that-are-easy-to-use-3097/</guid>
      <description>I’ve made the switch to Zoho Books … as an international traveller and marketing consultant, I needed accounting tools that move with me and one that is flexible with invoicing in a number of currencies.
Zoho Invoice has been my friend for some time – but I wasn’t committed to this product – when Zoho Books arrived I jumped ship and have paid up for 12 months.
Zoho Books allows me to</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Essential Startup Resources for Customer Relationship Management</title>
      <link>https://damien.co/startup/essential-startup-resources-for-customer-relationship-management-1053/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jun 2010 13:22:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien.co/startup/essential-startup-resources-for-customer-relationship-management-1053/</guid>
      <description>So here is an essential collection of startup resources to customer relationship management or CRM. When you go into business as a startup or entrepreneur your sales and marketing activities will need to be split 3 ways –
 Customers who are buying from you Nurturing Customers who will buy from you Generating new leads or potential customers  This may seem daunting – so from the day you open your doors or your new web business you’ll want a tool to track all your customers and maybe your suppliers too.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HOW TO: ZOHO CRM empty your Recycle bin to delete accounts &amp;amp; contacts</title>
      <link>https://damien.co/social-crm/how-to-zoho-crm-empty-your-recycle-bin-to-delete-accounts-contacts-922/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 May 2010 22:10:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien.co/social-crm/how-to-zoho-crm-empty-your-recycle-bin-to-delete-accounts-contacts-922/</guid>
      <description>ZOHO CRM is one of the best web based (SaaS) customer relationship management solutions around today and it’s got great features even in its free version.
How to delete your contacts, leads, accounts and is pretty easy thing to manage in ZOHO, but until you empty your Recycle Bin, they are still there (and this can affect some reports and views).
The Empty Recycle Bin icon is at the top of the screen on the right hand side … clicking it will show you whats in your recycle bin and you can then choose to empty it or recover records.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ZOHO CRM do you use your own custom web form? Then change to https</title>
      <link>https://damien.co/social-crm/zoho-crm-do-you-use-your-own-custom-web-from-then-change-to-https-894/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Apr 2010 14:14:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien.co/social-crm/zoho-crm-do-you-use-your-own-custom-web-from-then-change-to-https-894/</guid>
      <description>ZOHO CRM has some great features including web to lead forms – but they don’t really look too stylish. Especially if you use 3rd party tools for your web forms.
If you use custom web to lead forms you may have to make the change to using the more secure HTTPS connection. After I noticed the web to lead form was not working I checked the standard code from ZOHO.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ZOHO CRM adds call logging for leads &amp;amp; contacts</title>
      <link>https://damien.co/social-crm/zoho-crm-adds-call-logging-for-leads-contacts-862/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Apr 2010 16:18:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien.co/social-crm/zoho-crm-adds-call-logging-for-leads-contacts-862/</guid>
      <description>ZOHO CRM a web based (SaaS) customer relationship management solution (CRM) recently added a bunch of new features. For sometime users were able to record events like meetings but now there is an easy way to record daily / regular contact like telephone calls.
****
ZOHO CRM Call Logger The Call Logger button is on the view Contact Detail page
Click on the Add Call button to reveal the call logger screen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ZOHO CRM adds new features</title>
      <link>https://damien.co/social-crm/zoho-crm-adds-new-features-859/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Apr 2010 15:59:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien.co/social-crm/zoho-crm-adds-new-features-859/</guid>
      <description>The team at ZOHO have recently added a bunch of new features to ZOHO CRM. Some of these are going to be useful, but quite a few features are paid for and then only in the enterprise edition.
New Features in ZOHO CRM 1. Log a Call (All Editions)This gives an easy way to record an inbound or outbound call to a contact. When viewing the Contact Detail, scroll down to activities and click on Log Call.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to send an invoice with ZOHO CRM free edition &amp;#038; ZOHO Invoice</title>
      <link>https://damien.co/social-crm/how-to-send-an-invoice-with-zoho-crm-free-edition-zoho-invoice-854/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Apr 2010 16:09:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien.co/social-crm/how-to-send-an-invoice-with-zoho-crm-free-edition-zoho-invoice-854/</guid>
      <description>ZOHO CRMis one of the best web based (SaaS) solutions for day to day contact and customer relationship management. ZOHO CRM free edition doesn’t include features like creating a quote or invoice – don’t worry ZOHO Invoice is the perfect product for this. ZOHO Invoicefree edition allows you to create up to 5 quotes, estimates or invoices every month. ****
How to login to ZOHO Invoice from ZOHO CRM If you are already using ZOHO CRM just go to the homepage for ZOHO Invoice  You’ll have to complete some basic details and then you can create your first quote or invoice.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ZOHO CRM &amp;#8211; create a lead form for your website</title>
      <link>https://damien.co/social-crm/zoho-crm-create-a-lead-form-for-your-website-824/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Mar 2010 14:36:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien.co/social-crm/zoho-crm-create-a-lead-form-for-your-website-824/</guid>
      <description>ZOHO CRM – the best web based customer relationship management (CRM) service has a great tool to make it easy for any website to capture leads with a web form. This ZOHO web to lead form is easy to hack and make beautiful for your website.
**
**
**
**
Why have a web to lead form? Simple – Your website should be working hard to generate leads for you and focusing on inbound marketing techniques is the best way to capture new leads.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ZOHO CRM &amp;#8211; What is Email Opt out</title>
      <link>https://damien.co/social-crm/zoho-crm-what-is-email-opt-out-848/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Mar 2010 12:13:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien.co/social-crm/zoho-crm-what-is-email-opt-out-848/</guid>
      <description>Zoho CRM is one of the best web based customer relationship management services – great features and cheap pricing. Zoho has its own quirks such as Email Opt Out.
What is Email opt-out? unsolicited emails For marketing people, email opt-out would mean the customer or client has chosen to not receive unsolicited emails from your business – this is ususally a good way to stop sending bulk emails to certain customers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HOW TO change tab names in ZOHO CRM &amp;amp; make it easy to manage leads</title>
      <link>https://damien.co/social-crm/how-to-change-tab-names-in-zoho-crm-make-it-easy-to-manage-leads-815/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Mar 2010 11:00:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien.co/social-crm/how-to-change-tab-names-in-zoho-crm-make-it-easy-to-manage-leads-815/</guid>
      <description>ZOHO CRM is a very flexible web based service (SaaS) for customer relationship management. The free version is perfect for managing leads in a small to medium business or startup. Many business processes talk about opportunities, potentials or leads – so its good to know you can easily change ZOHO CRM to fit your business terms or jargon.
**The best part is that ZOHO CRM is so flexible that you won’t need to argue with your boss and you can make this change in 30 seconds.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to record email newsletter signup in ZOHO CRM &amp;amp; add a custom field</title>
      <link>https://damien.co/social-crm/how-to-record-email-newsletter-signup-in-zoho-crm-add-a-custom-field-835/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Mar 2010 21:21:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien.co/social-crm/how-to-record-email-newsletter-signup-in-zoho-crm-add-a-custom-field-835/</guid>
      <description>ZOHO CRM is a very flexible web based (SaaS) solution for customer management. Before starting to use ZOHO CRM for managing leads and communications, its common sense that you should add a custom field to record which contacts and customers agreed to receive marketing communications from you.
How to track email newsletter signup in ZOHO We are going to add a custom field in ZOHO to track newsletter signup – by default we’ll enable this so that all manually entered contacts and leads are already opted in to receive marketing comms.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HOW TO sign-up to Zoho CRM in 4 steps using Google Apps or Gmail</title>
      <link>https://damien.co/social-crm/how-to-sign-up-to-zoho-crm-in-4-steps-using-google-apps-or-gmail-767/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Mar 2010 19:38:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien.co/social-crm/how-to-sign-up-to-zoho-crm-in-4-steps-using-google-apps-or-gmail-767/</guid>
      <description>So you choose to use ZOHO CRM because it’s a great web based solutionfor customer relationship management. There are now 3 ways to sign-up to ZOHO CRMusing Google Appsor a Gmailaddress.  Google Apps – If you are an administrator you can add ZOHO CRM from the Google Apps Marketplace  Google Apps – Sign-up online and create a ZOHO account at the same time
  Gmail – as above, signup online and create a ZOHO account at the same time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zoho CRM best free web based CRM included in Google Apps Marketplace</title>
      <link>https://damien.co/social-crm/zoho-crm-best-free-web-based-crm-included-in-google-apps-marketplace-748/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Mar 2010 23:04:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien.co/social-crm/zoho-crm-best-free-web-based-crm-included-in-google-apps-marketplace-748/</guid>
      <description>ZOHO CRM, which I reckon is the best free CRM for the web or SaaSis now available to add from the new Google Apps Marketplace.
(note if you’re already using ZOHO CRM with Google Apps you are better to leave things as they are for now)
What is CRM? Customer Relationship Management or CRM is really about 3 things:
 Building up knowledge on the people you do with business with or relate to – your clients, customers and the companies they work for Communicating with your customers and managing those ‘relationships’ Selling your stuff, or supporting your clients and staff to sell  In the past business process managers would have focused on Managing Customers as a key process for the Customer Lifecycle.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zoho CRM How to choose a Web Based CRM solution</title>
      <link>https://damien.co/social-crm/zoho-crm-how-to-choose-a-web-based-crm-solution-365/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Mar 2010 00:02:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://damien.co/social-crm/zoho-crm-how-to-choose-a-web-based-crm-solution-365/</guid>
      <description>Inbound Marketers, Sales managers, customer care, account managers, business development managers – all need a good system for managing diaries, customer details and leads. Managing your sCRM using something like Zoho CRM means you have access to all your customer relationship data anywhere you are. And you don’t have to install anything on your Mac, PC or Linux operating system, just open your favourite web browser.
What is CRM? Customer Relationship Management (CRM) is an art and a science.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>