<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Resources on Damien Saunders</title>
    <link>http://damien.co/tags/resources/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Resources on Damien Saunders</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 19 Jun 2012 14:29:49 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://damien.co/tags/resources/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Best tools to start with Social Media Marketing &amp;#8211; 2011 re-cap (where are they now)</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/social-media-marketing-2/best-tools-to-start-with-social-media-marketing-2011-re-cap-where-are-they-now-7192/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jun 2012 14:29:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/social-media-marketing-2/best-tools-to-start-with-social-media-marketing-2011-re-cap-where-are-they-now-7192/</guid>
      <description>[typography font=”Special Elite” size=”25″ size_format=”px”]If you’re just getting started with Social Media marketing then you need at least 1 web based tool to help you.[/typography]
__In 2011, I wrote a great article on the best tools to start with Social Media Marketing. A year later, things have changed, so I wanted to look back at my 2011 suggestions to see where they are now.
Keep track of your social media status and influence, albeit using Klout’s own scoring.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Review] The Smashing Book 2 Is Available &amp;#8211; Smashing Magazine</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/blog/review-the-smashing-book-2-is-available-smashing-magazine-2659/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Feb 2011 16:52:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/blog/review-the-smashing-book-2-is-available-smashing-magazine-2659/</guid>
      <description>So I got my copy of the new ****The Smashing Book 2. Smashing Magazine is for anyone into design, web development and new media. It is one of many websites I follow on a weekly basis.
 The book came nicely (over) packaged and was immediately opened. It is a resource in itself and provides 10+ essays on topics from mobile app design to self-publishing – all new and not available on the website.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Foursquare for writers &amp;amp; bloggers – Slideshare Presentation of the day</title>
      <link>http://damien.co/social-media/foursquare/foursquare-for-writers-bloggers-slideshare-presentation-of-the-day-2349/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Dec 2010 16:29:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://damien.co/social-media/foursquare/foursquare-for-writers-bloggers-slideshare-presentation-of-the-day-2349/</guid>
      <description>Are you geo-location challenged and want to do more with Foursquare and social media marketing? Then take a look at my latest presentation which has been featured on SlideShare under How-To and DIY.

This presentation is perfect for bloggers, writers and journalists who want to use Foursquare– or in fact anyone with a virtual office who writes about interesting places.
Many digital marketers or independent consultants may be thinking they are missing out with social media marketing, but this guide shows how you can build your brand without having to use your own office location.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>